Don't forget to Subscribe for resources and help us
忘れずにリソースを購読してご協力ください
Documentary of back-embrナe
後援者のドキュメンタリー
Feast of knowledge this month we're having a feast of chemistry
知識の饗宴 今月は化学の饗宴を開催します
I am very honored to invite Professor Zhou Bitai from National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学の周碧泰教授をお招きできることを大変光栄に思います
Also our old colleague for many years
私たちの長年の古い同僚でもあります
Later you will see that he is a very, very capable person
後で彼がとてもとても有能な人であることがわかるでしょう
This is also a workaholic, one person can be used by three people
こちらもワーカホリック、1人でも3人でも使えます
his details
彼の詳細
We also saw beautiful pictures
素敵な写真も拝見させていただきました
Please enjoy it later
後ほどお楽しみください
Let me first give a brief introduction to our keynote speaker
まずは基調講演者について簡単に紹介させていただきます
I just said that he is the current chair professor of National Taiwan University
私は彼が現在の国立台湾大学の教授であると言いました。
In fact, when I just ate
実はさっき食べたときに
He did very, very broadly
彼は非常に広範囲にわたってやった
He probably knows everything about chemistry.
彼はおそらく化学についてすべてを知っています。
Then if the National Science Council or the Ministry of Science and Technology has any problems, please ask him to solve them.
それで、国家学術会議や科学技術省に問題があれば、解決してもらってください。
He is also very good at writing
彼は文章を書くのもとても上手です
write fast and long
速くて長く書く
So besides teaching in the Department of Chemistry, he is currently
そのため、彼は現在、化学科で教鞭を執る傍ら、
He is also in charge of National Taiwan University Chemistry
彼は国立台湾大学の化学も担当しています。
National Taiwan University National Taiwan University's technology research center for emerging materials and prospective research
国立台湾大学 国立台湾大学の新興材料および前向き研究のための技術研究センター
This is actually the Nano Research Center
実はここ、ナノ研究センターなんです
This is a soft center in National Taiwan University
ここは国立台湾大学のソフトセンターです
Virtual Center
仮想センター
that's some research topics
それはいくつかの研究テーマです
Then there are some teams in
それから、いくつかのチームがあります
work together on a common interest
共通の利益に向けて協力する
He was Fu Jen Catholic University in 1970
彼は1970年に天主教福仁大学でした
Received the school room in 1989
1989年に教室を譲り受ける
Then in 1985 in
そして1985年に
Ph.D. from Florida State University
フロリダ州立大学博士号取得
that's there
それはそこにあります
South Carolina worked as an assistant professor
サウスカロライナ州では助教授として勤務していた
seven years
七年
87 to 94
87～94
Chung Cheng University
中正大学
recruit back, I remember that time
戻ってきてください、あの時のことを覚えています
National Taiwan University is also looking for you
国立台湾大学もあなたを求めています
at Chung Cheng University
中正大学にて
do 2001
2001年をやる
The Chemistry Department of Chung Cheng University is in his hands
中正大学化学科は彼の手に
also reborn
も生まれ変わる
In 2001 we were honored
2001年に私たちはこの栄誉を受けました
The Chemistry Department of National Taiwan University found it
国立台湾大学化学科が発見した。
Until now, I used to be in the chemistry department
今まで化学科に所属していました
I was also the head of the department anyway.
とにかく私は部門長でもありました。
he did all the hard work
彼はあらゆる大変な仕事をした
Actually Zhou Bitai, I remember that I seemed to be
実際、周美泰はそうだったのを覚えています
you were in berkeley
あなたはバークレーにいました
at Berkeley
バークレーにて
Just when I won the Nobel Prize
ちょうどノーベル賞を受賞したとき
At that time, you and Su Zhiming went to visit
その時、あなたと蘇志明は会いに行きました
he hasn't got it yet
彼はまだそれを持っていません
then 1985
その後1985年
Then he turned out to be physical chemistry
その後、彼は物理化学であることが判明しました
cutting chemistry
切断化学
I just heard that he also does organic synthesis
有機合成もやっていると聞きました
So I say he is versatile
だから私は彼は多才だと言います
Of course, there are countless papers published
もちろん、数え切れないほどの論文が出版されています
And there are quite a lot of important chemical journals
重要な化学雑誌もたくさんあります
this reviewer
この査読者
Anyway, all the domestic awards
とにかく国内の賞は全部
he has it all
彼はすべてを持っています
Course Ministry Academic Awards
コース省学術賞
National Trophy
ナショナルトロフィー
Distinguished Award of the National Science Council, etc.
米国学術会議特別賞など
Internationally
国際的に
he is also
彼も
Royal Society of Chemistry
王立化学会
Rose Society
バラの会
Fellow
仲間
Asia Photochemical
アジア光化学
Achievement Award
功績賞
in Japan
日本で
recently
最近
at this
この時点で
Uncle Van Thieme
ヴァン・ティームおじさん
This is probably currently
おそらく現在はこれです
Top of the line in chemistry
化学の最先端
Journal
ジャーナル
has published his
彼のを出版しました
Authere profile
著者プロフィール
I guess I'll cut the blah blah blah anyway.
とにかくなんとかカットしようと思います。
There are so many medals, so there is no need to go here
メダルがたくさんあるのでここに行かなくても大丈夫
then we'll be fine
それなら大丈夫です
Come and enjoy this chemical feast
ぜひこの化学の饗宴を楽しんでください
I welcome to be a professor
教授になることを歓迎します
thank you thank you
ありがとうありがとう
It's so hard to prepare an academic speech.
学術講演を準備するのはとても大変です。
It's really too difficult because to talk about it is to say
それは本当に難しすぎる、なぜならそれについて話すことは言うことだから
understandable and then another point
理解できました、そして別の点
At least chemically, why would it hold him together?
少なくとも化学的には、なぜそれが彼を結びつけるのでしょうか？
It took days, basically
基本的には何日もかかりました
Then I guess I'm just taking this opportunity
じゃあ、この機会を利用しようかなと思います
Then I would like to talk about some of the people in my laboratory.
次に、私の研究室の何人かの人々について話したいと思います。
i find it interesting
面白いと思います
Then everyone can listen
そしたらみんなも聴けるよ
I mean, what's interesting about chemistry?
化学の何が面白いのですか？
to derive him
彼を導き出すために
So I probably use this today
だから今日はたぶんこれを使う
It means that my lab develops some interesting molecules
それは、私の研究室がいくつかの興味深い分子を開発していることを意味します
some nanomaterials
いくつかのナノマテリアル
Of course I have many, many things that I haven't said
もちろん、言っていないことはたくさんありますが、
Because sorry, it's just two hours
ごめんなさい、2時間だけなので
I can't finish talking for five hours
5時間話しても終わらない
basically speaking
基本的に言えば
so i just pick these
だから私はこれらを選ぶだけです
I think one thing can make you feel like saying
一つ言いたくなることがあると思います
I have learned something to say about this matter
この件について言うべきことを学びました
teacher tell you
先生が教えてください
Just be a teacher
ただ教師になってください
To speak until students understand
生徒が理解できるまで話すこと
that was difficult
それは難しかった
a lot of luggage, that's a completely different one, ok, let's take a look
荷物が多い、それは全く違うもの、分かった、見てみましょう
What about my lab, basically
基本的に私の研究室はどうですか
Sorry, I use Chinese like this, ah, it’s safe, because I can’t translate them into that one by one
ごめんなさい、中国語はこうやって使っています、あ、セーフです、いちいち訳せないから
As for my laboratory, Vice President Wang also talked about it just now
私の研究室については、先ほど王副所長からもお話がありましたが、
Actually, I was born to actually do this
実は私はこれをするために生まれてきたのです
uh, fast ray, laser these
ああ、高速光線、レーザーでこれを
These dynamics, spectral dynamics, OK, so actually I
これらのダイナミクス、スペクトルダイナミクス、OK、それで実際に私は
When I was in Bokri, what did I do in Bokri
ボクリにいたとき、私はボクリで何をしていましたか
In fact, they are all heavy duty, just doing these things
実際、これらはすべて重労働であり、これらのことを行うだけです
How to get the laser and why, so I am very familiar with Li Renzhe's laboratory
レーザーを入手する方法とその理由、つまり李仁哲の研究室についてはよく知っています
Because we're doing this, OK
これをやっているから、OK
Basically speaking, this piece is still my center
基本的には今でもこの作品が私の中心です
It’s laser spotosphate, OK, that’s all about lasers
それはレーザースポットリン酸塩です、OK、レーザーについては以上です
The optical physics block is still my center, but the center has developed
光物理ブロックは今でも私の中心ですが、その中心は発展しています
In fact, based on the current spectral dynamics, it is probably the most chemically
実際、現在のスペクトル力学に基づくと、これはおそらく最も化学的に
The fastest one is our non-bird laser, just 10-15 times
最も速いのは鳥以外のレーザーで、わずか 10 ～ 15 倍です。
To the 10-14th power second, ah, some people say, hey, the Ato laser is faster
10 の 14 乗秒、ああ、Ato レーザーの方が速いと言う人もいます
It is 10-18, which is very difficult to do in chemistry, because
これは 10-18 であり、化学で計算するのは非常に困難です。
Ladies and gentlemen, if you have some physical fundamentals, sea cucumbers are not only there
皆さん、身体の基礎があれば、ナマコだけが存在するわけではありません。
You can tell, when you were ten minus 18, square seconds
あなたが10歳から18歳を引いたとき、平方秒がわかります
Your energy band is already so wide, for me, the state you can explore in chemistry
あなたのエネルギーバンドはすでに非常に広く、私にとっては、化学で探求できる状態です
There are almost none, except you are atomic
あなたが原子であることを除いて、ほとんど何もありません
What ES-Opto, 2S-Opto, can do this
ES-Opto、2S-Opto でできること
In terms of chemistry, we don’t actually discuss these things in Aton.
化学に関して言えば、Aton ではこれらのことについて実際には議論しません。
Our last time Aton, Aton
前回のアトン、アトン
Just atom, atom, try to translate into Chinese for me
アトム、アトムに関しては、中国語に翻訳してみてください
These so-called molecules made of atoms and atoms, OK, we use the molecular state
これらのいわゆる分子は原子と原子でできています。OK、分子状態を使用します。
So this is still my center
だからここが今でも私の中心です
Then after I was in the center, in fact, since I came to South Carolina
それから私が中心部にいた後、実際にはサウスカロライナに来て以来
Then I went back to Zhongzheng and went to National Taiwan University
それから中正に戻り、国立台湾大学に行きました。
In fact, I have been spending and expanding my field along the way
実際、私はその過程で自分の分野を拡大し、費やしてきました
In fact, the most likely is after the National Taiwan University, that is, the ten years
実際、最も可能性が高いのは国立台湾大学の後、つまり 10 年間です。
Probably spread from this place, OK
おそらくここから広がったでしょう、OK
For example, I do a lot of very basic science
たとえば、私は非常に基礎的な科学をたくさんやっています
OK, just now, that is to say
OK、今、つまり
For example, do some straight-to-direct transfer, direct-to-electricity transfer, energy transfer
たとえば、直接から直接の転送、直接から電力への転送、エネルギー転送を実行します。
i do this a lot
私はこれをよくやります
But from this direct transfer, I will tell some development
しかし、この直接転送から、いくつかの展開をお話します
Why is it transferred directly, because there is a relationship between inner clarity and clarity
なぜ直接転送されるのかというと、内なる明晰さと明晰さの間には関係があるからです。
So I started to design the ring
そこでリングのデザインを始めました
What can be kissed and what can be done
キスできること、できること
Do get stuck together with other molecules
他の分子とくっついてしまう
Then do some identification functions
次に、いくつかの識別関数を実行します
so I do a lot of this
だから私はこれをたくさんやります
That's because to do this
それはこうするためだから
You have to work with him on this one
あなたはこの仕事のために彼に協力しなければなりません
But cooperation is sorry
でも協力はごめんなさい
Just now the dean Fang Fuyuan said
今、方福源学部長が言いました。
I am a person who spends more than fifteen hours a day
私は1日15時間以上を過ごす人間です
So no one is following me
だから誰も私をフォローしてない
i really didn't lie to you
私は本当にあなたに嘘をついていませんでした
Absolutely no one is following in my footsteps
絶対に誰も私の足跡をたどらない
so come by yourself later
だから後で一人で来てください
OK, so I'm going to start compositing myself.
さて、自分で合成を始めます。
start with materialization
具現化から始める
start learning how to synthesize
合成方法を学び始める
why do what
なぜ何をするのか
on the way
途中
do some bio recognition
生体認識を行う
How to get to the detection of bio
バイオの検出に至るまでの手順
wait a minute we'll talk about some
ちょっと待ってください、いくつか話します
OK
OK
even just said
たった今言っただけでも
We're going to start developing these
これらの開発を開始します
how to carry these
これらをどうやって運ぶか
how to take these molecules
これらの分子をどうやって摂取するか
What the hell body
一体どういう体なんだ
So we do a lot of nano science
そこで私たちはナノサイエンスをたくさん行っています
basically
基本上
Therefore, in terms of Nami materials
したがって、ナミ素材に関しては、
I will do quite a lot
かなりのことをやります
From 2003 to 2004
2003 年から 2004 年まで
When science in Taiwan and Macao rises
台湾とマカオの科学が台頭するとき
make a lot of glowing materials
光る素材をたくさん作る
The material of this perm energy
このパーマエネルギーの素材は
OK basically
OK 基本上
so you know along the way
だから途中でわかるよ
Dean Wangfu said just now
ディーン・ワンフーが今言いました
I probably cover everything in chemistry
おそらく化学のすべてをカバーします
Basically OK to some extent
基本的にはある程度OK
You said that there is deepening here
ここは深化しているとあなたは言いました
Yes wait a minute I'll talk about deepening OK basically
はい、ちょっと待ってください。深化について話します。基本的には OK
you'll know it when you hear it
聞いたらわかるよ
so but anyway
だから、とにかく
what i'm talking about
私が話していること
very simple is
とてもシンプルです
It's chemistry and light
それは化学と光です
Because light is OK after all
やっぱり光でいいから
That's what you said, that's the light
それはあなたが言ったことです、それは光です
OK, that light is basically for me
OK、その光は基本的に私のためのものです
is my specialty
私の専門です
OK so I've been doing
さて、私はそうしてきました
The so-called mechanism of light and chemistry
いわゆる光と化学の仕組み
OK basically OK
基本的にOK
how from chemistry
化学からどうやって
wait a minute i will bring a lot
ちょっと待ってください、たくさん持っていきます
show mode come over ok basically
ショーモード来て基本的にOK
so that's how to get to the stalls what to do
それで屋台に行く方法は何ですか？
This is probably my basic one
おそらくこれが私の基本的なものです
Center thinking OK in this place
この場所でOKを考えているセンター
Of course one thing is
もちろん一つのことは
so of course one thing
もちろん一つのこと
What I'm going to talk about today is probably molecules
今日お話しするのはおそらく分子についてです
Deepen the molecular ratio of the machine material, which is basically
基本的に機械材料の分子比を深くする
Probably I will cover this inside
おそらくこれを内部でカバーします
What about these areas?
これらの地域についてはどうでしょうか？
I'll probably talk about three of them.
おそらくそのうちの3つについてお話します。
One is OK to talk about these so-called clear-eyed elements
これらのいわゆる明確な要素について話すのは問題ありません
I'll start with the basics OK
基本から始めましょう OK
clear viewer
就是清見分子
Because after all, it's more common sense
結局のところそれが常識だから
Some elements of internal and external clarity
内部および外部の明確さのいくつかの要素
what physical properties it has
どのような物理的特性を持っているか
What are its photophysical properties?
その光物理的性質は何ですか?
What properties does it have when illuminated
光を当てるとどんな性質があるのか
I will talk about this
これについて話します
Then one very important thing is to say
それから、非常に重要なことが 1 つあります。
water is clear
水は透明です
So how to see inside from the clear water
では、透き通った水の中からどうやって中を見るかというと、
go call it
行って電話してください
untie what we want
私たちが望むものを解き放つ
Then I can go and probe the water
それから私は水を調べに行くことができます
This water certainly does not mean our water
この水は決して私たちの水のことではありません
That is to say, the water in biochemical
つまり、生化学における水は、
This is a very important and most urgent development for me
これは私にとって非常に重要かつ緊急の開発です
Also I want to be at Nano Airport
私もナノ空港に行きたいです
some listeners like to listen
聞くのが好きなリスナーもいます
Basically, let me talk about some nano-airports in semiconductors
基本的に、半導体におけるいくつかのナノ空港について話させてください。
Especially now the hardest thing is
特に今一番大変なのは
The entire industry in Taiwan will be defeated
台湾の産業全体が敗北するだろう
These are the so-called frame pains
これらはいわゆるフレーム痛です
quantum dot display
量子ドットディスプレイ
Let me tell you that everyone in Taiwan is panicking now
言っておきますが、台湾のみんなは今パニックになっています
Said that the industry said that this would not leave
業界はこれでは撤退しないと言っていると述べた
Taiwan is probably all cut off
台湾はおそらく全滅するだろう
wait a minute listen
ちょっと待って聞いてください
there's something i'll talk about
話したいことがあります
And Nano Airport
そしてナノ空港
Composite material, OK, basically
的複合材料,OK,基本上
So, what I'm talking about today is probably
それで、今日私が話していることはおそらく
Among the seven or eight fields, these are four fields
7、8分野のうち、これらは4分野です
That's like Solar Energy Cell, or
それは太陽エネルギー電池のようなものです、または
I probably don’t know much about O-ray, so I won’t talk about it
O-ray についてはあまり知らないかもしれないので説明しません
Because I know I've seen the one before you, like
だって私はあなたの前に見たことがあると知っているから
Chen Jindi, what, many people have said this
チェン・ジンディ、何、多くの人がこれを言いました
What kind of luminescent material is used for what, so this place
どのような発光材料が何に使われているのかというと、こちら
I probably won't talk about it, I'll just focus on
たぶんそれについては話さない、ただそれに集中するよ
These few, these four are probably
この数名、この 4 名がおそらく
Molecules of this aspect of Qingjian
Qingjian のこの側面の分子
OK, and then I will talk about some unavoidable materials
さて、それでは避けられない材料について話します
Probably in this place, okay, OK
おそらくこの場所で、OK、OK
So first I will talk about some so-called
そこで最初に、いわゆるいくつかのことについて話します
Seeing Molecules Inside Clearly, This Is Interesting in Photophysics
中の分子がはっきり見える、光物理学の面白さ
It's really interesting, OK, you'll know when you listen to it
すごく面白いよ、聞いてみれば分かるよ
OK, let's talk about the catalysis of water molecules
さて、水分子の触媒作用について話しましょう
OK, from water molecule catalysis, how do I go
OK、水分子の触媒作用から、どうすればいいですか
To measure these water molecules in biochemistry
生化学でこれらの水分子を測定するには
Let me tell you one more thing, I haven’t said it here yet, but I’ll do it too
もう一つ言わせてください、ここではまだ言っていませんが、私も言います
Why do you talk about the Dynamic of Protin?
なぜタンパク質の動態について話すのですか?
Just use it as a protin and have something
プロチンとして使用するだけで何かが得られます
Any transfer in or what to do, look at its Dynamic
転送または何をすべきか、そのダイナミックを見てください
Or do what QuickStore does, I do it in reverse
または、QuickStore と同じことを逆に実行します。
I am using
使っています
Use the water in Protin to detect the activity of Protin
プロチンに含まれる水を利用してプロチンの活性を検出します
OK, so this is a different approach
OK、これは別のアプローチです
This is probably the first in the world, no one has done this before
これはおそらく世界初であり、これまで誰もこれを行ったことはありません
OK, basically, so we'll know when we hear it
OK、基本的には、それを聞けばわかります
OK, so let me start with these few
OK、それではこれらのいくつかから始めましょう
These are the things that you can see
これらはあなたが見ることができるものです
what is its molecule like
その分子はどのようなものですか
Well, I actually did this two months ago
実はこれを2ヶ月前にやったんです
The one who thinks before this so-called commemoration
このいわゆる記念を前に考える人
When I made the list, I talked about some
リストを作成したときにいくつか話しました
OK, but today because it's an hour and a half or more
わかった、でも今日は1時間半以上あるから
OK, so I'll just put a more comprehensive
OK、それではもっと包括的な内容を載せておきます
OK, it's more detailed, I'll put it in the second place
はい、詳しくは 2 番目に記載します
OK, sorry, I can speak English, I can’t help it, it’s still a matter
OK、ごめんなさい、英語は話せます、仕方ないです、まだ問題です
OK, let's take a look, then you have to talk about Qingjian
OK、見てみましょう。それから、Qingjian について話さなければなりません
OK, let's talk about Nei Qingjian, talk about these molecules
OK、内清健について話しましょう、これらの分子について話しましょう
you start pointing now
あなたは今指差し始めます
I won’t go into more about fingering, as fingering has a physical definition
運指には物理的な定義があるため、運指についてはこれ以上説明しません。
Let me tell you that three crackers make one finger, OK
クラッカー3枚で指1本になるって言っておきます、OK
We won't talk about this much, this high-energy physics
この高エネルギー物理学についてはこれ以上は話しません
It seems that several high-energy physics have talked about it here, OK
いくつかの高エネルギー物理学がここでそれについて話しているようです、OK
We don't talk about this thing, we can talk about chemistry or biochemistry
私たちはこのことについて話すのではなく、化学や生化学について話すことができます
Then this is normal, it’s H positive, isn’t it?
じゃあこれは普通、H陽性ですよね？
If H is positive, the most famous one is to tell you about the acid-base of Arrhinius
H が正の場合、最も有名なのはアリニウスの酸塩基について説明することです。
Just tell you that you can release a proton, this is sour
陽子を放出できるとだけ言ってください、これはひどいです
that's basically it, right?
基本的にはそれだけですよね？
If you want to talk about it, that's fine. If you talk about address biochemistry, what about sour fish?
それについて話したいなら、それでいいのですが、アドレス生化学の話なら、酸っぱい魚はどうですか？
That is, proton has sour fish, the formation of mesohalite
つまり、プロトンは酸っぱい魚、メソハライトの形成を持っています
Right, let me tell you in terms of biochemistry, we call it Zhizhi BOM
そうです、生化学の観点から教えてください、私たちはそれを Zhizhi BOM と呼んでいます
OK, this, I only found out this time during the preparation, this is called BOM, OK, basically
OK、これ、今回準備中に初めて知りました、これは BOM と呼ばれるものです、OK、基本的には
Just proton BOMP, POMP
ただのプロトン BOMP、POMP
The promb pump, of course the most famous, is very simple?
もちろん最も有名なのはプロムポンプですが、非常にシンプルです。
That is, if you want to get from the cells inside
つまり、内部の細胞から取得したい場合は、
To pump it out, basically you have energy for it
それを吐き出すには、基本的にエネルギーが必要です
Just turn it into ATP, OK, release a proton
それをATPに変えて、OK、プロトンを放出してください
Basically you just let the energy out, pump it out from here
基本的にはエネルギーを外に出すだけ、ここから汲み出すだけです
If you need energy, it's simple, you make a very simple
エネルギーが必要なら、それは簡単です、非常に簡単なものを作ります。
CAMME Osmosis, is what we call chemical osmosis
CAMME 浸透、いわゆる化学浸透です。
If you just let it go back, you can gain energy
元に戻せばエネルギーが得られる
OK, so proton is in the whole biochemistry or physics or chemistry
OK、陽子は生化学、物理学、化学全体に含まれます。
In fact, its significance is very, very, very important
実際、その重要性は非常に非常に重要です
Then there is proton, one thing we want to talk about next is to talk about Hydrogen BOM
次に陽子についてです。次に話したいのは、水素 BOM についてです。
The Hydrogen BOM, basically
水素 BOM、基本的に
It's the Qing sword, right?
清国の剣ですよね？
Then Qing Jian will tell you one thing, that is
それから Qing Jian が一つだけ教えてくれます。
If we speak in chemistry
化学で言うと
The most famous one is Sharing the Sword
最も有名なのは「Sharing the Sword」
Yes, how long is it built for sharing the sword?
はい、剣を共有するためにどのくらいの期間で構築されていますか？
If with a single sword
一本の剣なら
That's about 1 to 1.5 n cool
それは約 1 ～ 1.5 n クールです
is i
私はですか
It is 10's -8cm
10代-8cmです
10'-10m
10的-10米
right, it's almost that long
そう、ほぼそのくらいの長さです
How do we define Qingjian?
Qingjian をどのように定義すればよいでしょうか?
Generally speaking
一般的に言えば
Here is written OK
ここにOKと書かれています
In fact, the earliest definition of the Qing sword was in 1912
実際、清建の最初の定義は 1912 年でした。
Oh it's so early OK basically speaking
ああ、早いですね、基本的に言えばOKです
OK that's usually a mess
OK、それは通常混乱です
By 2011 IUPEC
2011年までにIUPEC
It's the International Naming Association telling you
国際命名協会が伝えています
how to define don't care
ドントケアを定義する方法
How did we make the Qing sword before?
以前はどのようにして清の剣を作ったのでしょうか？
it's very simple
それはとても簡単です
This so-called highly electronegative
このいわゆる高度な電気陰性度
Right? Follow up what happened
そうですか?何が起こったのか追跡してください
OK, basically it’s called Youqing Sword, right?
OK、基本的にはYouqing Swordと呼ばれていますよね？
That is to say, eggs, sheep
つまり、卵、羊
These things serve again
これらのものは再び役に立ちます
But what about the current basic definition
しかし、現在の基本的な定義はどうでしょうか
just tell you one thing is
ただ一つだけ言っておきます
any chemical bond
あらゆる化学結合
OK as long as there is a follow-up
フォローアップがあればOK
in this kind of
この種の
No matter the geometry, you squeeze it to that place
形状に関係なく、その場所に絞り込む
It doesn't matter what it is, as long as it is 1.5 to 2.2 N pairs
1.5～2.2Nペアであれば何でも構いません。
Basically we just generalize it
基本的にはそれを一般化しているだけです
Something similar to CH can also be seen clearly with other itineraries
CHと同様のものは他の旅程でもはっきりと確認できます
OK, basically let me give you an example, this one was published in the last three months
OK、基本的に例を挙げましょう。これは過去 3 か月間に公開されたものです
OK, both zero and green can produce clear vision
OK、ゼロとグリーンの両方が鮮明な視界を生み出すことができます
Because there are 2.1 N pairs in the middle
真ん中には 2.1 N 個のペアがあるため
OK 2.1 I so say in terms of the modern version of Kiyomi
OK 2.1 現代版のキヨミに関して言えば、
This is called Qingjian, so Qingjian is already what it is
これは清ジャンと呼ばれるものなので、清ジャンはすでにそれです
very very popular
非常非常的popular
OK basically put it this way okay let's see
OK、基本的にはこのように置きます、わかりました、見てみましょう
So in terms of this structure
したがって、この構造に関して言えば、
Let's take a look at one thing, in terms of chemistry
化学の観点から一つのことを見てみましょう
What's going on with Qing Jian?
Qing Jianはどうしたのですか？
About 30 to 100 kcal of energy
エネルギー約30～100kcal
is that it will stabilize you at 30 to 100 kcal
30〜100kcalで安定するということです
We all know that van der Valli is very weak at about 0.1 kcal, OK
ファン デル ヴァリは約 0.1 kcal で非常に弱いことは誰もが知っています。
The energy of the long temperature is also about 0.1 0.5 kcal
長時間のエネルギーも約0.1～0.5kcal
Even the long-term temperature of 298K is very weak.
298Kという長期温度でも非常に弱いです。
The Hydrogen stick is somewhere in between, about 1.2 to 10 kcal
水素スティックはその中間、約1.2～10kcal
OK this different one Kiyomi
OK、これは別のキヨミです
I am listing these relatively strong clear views in the past.
過去にこういった比較的強い明確な見解を列挙させていただいております。
I just kept it, eggs, why can I see it clearly?
飼ってるだけだよ、卵、どうしてはっきり見えるの？
we'll see later
後で見てみましょう
Probably about 1.2 to 10 kcal
たぶん1.2～10kcalくらい
Fu is an exception
フーは例外だ
Because we think that there is ionized clear view
イオン化されたクリアな視界があると思うので
Generally speaking, it is about 1.2 to 10 kcal.
一般的には1.2～10kcal程度です。
then why do you want to see clearly
ではなぜはっきりと見たいのかというと、それは簡単です。
Just to tell you it can also be seen by pedestrians
歩行者からも見えるとだけ言っておきます
can also be what? in a way just take it off
ある意味、ただ脱ぐだけです
able to reformation
改革できる
reformation
改革
what is this ? biochemically it needs
これは何ですか?生化学的に必要です
it needs to be this way
このようにする必要があります
You can't use your words so tightly
そんなにきつく言葉を使うことはできない
So how does it do these metabolisms
では、これらの代謝はどのように行われるのでしょうか
It's the metabolism. It's impossible.
それは代謝です、それは不可能です。
so this is why
だからこれが理由です
Wait a minute we talk about the base pale of DNA
ちょっと待ってください、私たちは DNA のベースペールについて話しているのです
that's what it does, in a way
ある意味、それがやっていることだ
OK
OK
ok, see you in chemistry
はい、化学でお会いしましょう
When it comes to chemistry, I have to talk about this person, right?
化学といえばこの人の話ですよね？
Chemical see these words chemical bound
化学的、これらの単語を参照してください 化学結合
What is this bund for?
この堤防は何のためにあるのでしょうか？
In fact, it is when it is in class
実は授業中のことなんです
It has not been published
公開されていません
I wrote it on the blackboard during class.
授業中に黒板に書きました。
This Berkely professor is called G.N. Lewis
このバークレーの教授は G.N. ルイスと呼ばれています
You know, Lewis acid test
ご存知、ルイス酸検査
you should know right
あなたは正しく知っているはずです
But your G.N. Lewis actually it
しかし、あなたのG.N.ルイスは実際にはそれです
He is not the most famous doctor Lu acid test
彼は最も有名な医師ルー酸検査ではありません
he is the father of thermodynamics
彼は熱力学の父です
is the ancestor of chemical thermodynamics
化学熱力学の祖先です
basically talk
基本的に話す
OK but everyone remembers that he is
OK、でも誰もが彼がいることを覚えています
Doctor Lu acid test
ドクター・ルー酸検査
Basically OK
基本的にOK
That's when he was experimenting in Burkley
彼がバークレーで実験をしていたときのことだ
Speaking of this place
この場所といえば
I have one under here
ここの下に 1 つあります
compare that
それを比較してください
In fact, what are we talking about?
実際、何のことを話しているのでしょうか？
OK let's see one thing
さて、一つ見てみましょう
Right, you can find it from Google
そうです、Google から見つけることができます
Google he recently helped
彼が最近手伝ったGoogle
Do not believe you can now key
これでキーを押すことができるとは信じられません
About 5.7 million B
約570万B
OK but this kind of thing
まあ、でもこういうことは
I think 5 million is enough, right?
500万もあれば十分だと思いますよ？
It's far worse than the entertainment industry
芸能界よりひどいよ
OK entertainment
OKエンターテイメント
Come on, let's see what the next entertainment industry is called
さあ、次のエンターテイメント業界が何と呼ばれるか見てみましょう
What is another stick called?
もう一つの棒は何と呼ばれますか?
Called James Bond
ジェームズ・ボンドと呼ばれる
You see James Bond has 85.8 million
ジェームズ・ボンドの資産は8,580万です
So the answer is still much worse.
したがって、答えはさらに悪いです。
Basically you're like the entertainment industry
基本的にはエンターテイメント業界のようなものです
You see, this kind of stick is equally good, but it’s so much worse.
この種のスティックは同じくらい優れていますが、はるかに悪いです。
OK so there's nothing to say
OK、何も言うことはありません
let's take a look
見てみましょう
Okay, what about the scissors?
さて、はさみはどうですか？
We are role models
私たちはロールモデルです
I just changed this English today
今日この英語を変更したところです
Change to Chinese OK
中国語に変更OK
The answer is that we see
答えは、私たちが見ているということです
ATGC is Adding and Siaming or light and shadow and Sitle Sync
ATGCはAddingとSiaming、または光と影とSitle Syncです
look at this clear
これを見てください
basically the place
基本的にその場所
Published in 2003
2003 年に出版
This JPC publishes
当JPCが発行するのは、
Let me tell you that AT has about -11000 cards
ATには約-11000枚のカードがあると言わせてください
These two cut together have -11000 calories
これら2つを一緒にカットすると、-11000カロリーになります
Then let me tell you Kobrenbaum is 50 to 100
それならコブレンバウムは50から100だと言わせてください
so it's all very
だからそれはすべてとても
about five times ten times weaker than it is
5倍10倍くらい弱い
But basically three are stronger
でも基本的には3人のほうが強い
Just one more, about 20 kilocalories
あと1個で約20キロカロリー
but more than anything
しかし何よりも
than these so-called carpools
いわゆる相乗りよりも
broken tightly
しっかりと壊れた
that's much weaker
それははるかに弱いです
so it can be anything
だから何でもいいよ
Breakdown Reformation
ブレイクダウン改革
Causes of Breakdown Reformation
Breakdown Reformation的原因
OK just need to see clearly
OK、はっきり見えればいいだけです
OK, then you say one is not strong enough
OK、それではあなたは片方が十分に強くないと言います
That's all right
大丈夫です
The whole cassette is strong enough.
カセット全体は十分な強度があります。
If you say something like this you don't believe
こんなこと信じないなら
I want you to always trust Gweaver Organic
常にGweaver Organicを信頼してほしい
right
右
just one line won't work
1行だけでは機能しません
Then tie thousands of threads and you won't be able to move
そうすれば何千もの糸が結ばれる、そうすればあなたは動けなくなるだろう
OK so maybe one thing
OK、それでは 1 つだけかもしれません
it's obvious to tell you
あなたに言うのは明らかです
The biggest advantage of Kiyomi is in this place
Kiyomiの最大の利点はここにあります
OK will obviously give you this kind of sense
OK は明らかにこのような感覚を与えます
good
良い
That's clear
それは明らかです
You said from 1912 to now
1912年から現在までって言ってたね
a hundred years
百年
Exactly 102 years, 103 years
ちょうど102年、103年
But one big thing is still a Hot topic
しかし、まだホットな話題が 1 つあります。
still a very popular
まだ非常に人気のある
For example, the recent ones, look at last year's ones
たとえば、最近のもの、昨年のものを見てください。
let's see this, shall we
これを見てみましょうか
this is a molecule
これは分子です
called A-hydroxyquinoline
A-ヒドロキシキノリンと呼ばれる
leave it alone
ほっといて
Look at this when it's cold
寒いときはこれを見てください
Atomic Force Microscopy FM
原子間力顕微鏡FM
Atomic force microscope you also see
原子間力顕微鏡もご覧いただけます
Seems like Kiyomi is here
キヨミが来たみたいだ
look at this place
この場所を見てください
These are here
これらはここにあります
seems clear
はっきりしているようです
look like this
このように見える
It was published in Science
サイエンス誌に掲載されました
This is the mainland
ここは本土です
It should be Chinese Academy of Sciences
中国科学院のはずだ
basically
基本的
that developed
開発したのは
but after a year or two
でも1年か2年後には
was overthrown after a year
1年後に倒された
this may be problematic
これは問題があるかもしれない
Everyone, if you say it has physics, you will know it.
皆さん、物性があると言えば分かると思います。
because they found out
彼らは気づいたから
you use an atomic force microscope
原子間力顕微鏡を使用します
For example, look at this Compound
たとえば、この化合物を見てください。
this molecule
この分子
You see, this molecule is egg-and-egg
ご存知のとおり、この分子は卵と卵です。
Vice President Wang, look at this
王副総統、これを見てください。
must know better than me
私よりもよく知っているはずです
because he said he was ejaculating
射精してるって言ってたから
You see, the eggs are not clear at all
ご覧のとおり、卵はまったく透明ではありません
egg on egg
卵と卵
egg to egg
卵から卵へ
He still sees this
彼はまだこれを見ています
So answering one thing is that it is difficult
ですから、一つ答えれば、それは難しいということです
ok, he thinks there is a problem with this clear view
OK、彼はこの明確な見解には問題があると考えています
It means don't underestimate
過小評価しないでくださいという意味です
Of course you often see why rigorously choose Weijing
もちろん、Weijing を厳密に選択する理由がよくわかります。
What would you say when you saw glasses on WeChat?
WeChat でメガネを見たら何と言いますか?
What may be the artifact
アーティファクトは何でしょうか
It may be the artifact that it appeared in the experiment
実験で出てきた遺物かもしれない
this is something that is often seen
これはよく見られることです
So I'm telling you to be careful, be careful
だから気をつけろって言ってるんだ、気をつけろよ
Recently because of this post
最近この投稿のせいで
All I know look at AFFM or STM
私が知っているのはAFFMかSTMだけです
are being scrutinized very carefully
非常に慎重に検査されています
Especially if it can be published on the Lianyiqiu series
特にLianyiquシリーズで出版できれば。
will probably be scrutinized
おそらく精査されるだろう
But from here it can be said
しかし、ここから言えるのは、
It's important to call it Hide and Keep on
Hide and Keep on と呼ぶことが重要です
basically
基本的
Generally speaking, what do we think about the topic?
一般的に、このトピックについて私たちはどう思いますか?
That's easy, just watch an ordinary MMA
それは簡単です、普通のMMAを見るだけです
why? let me give you an example
なぜですか？例を挙げましょう
You also know that the clearer the stronger
透明であればあるほど強いこともご存知でしょう
Basically there are fewer electrons on this side
基本的にこちら側の電子は少なくなります
as we call it inside the direct nuclear tool
私たちがそれを直接核ツール内で呼んでいる
it becomes more shift
それはさらにシフトになります
The more when the field shift
フィールドが変わるほど
in this longer place
この長い場所で
outdated place
時代遅れの場所
This molecule is synthesized by us
この分子は私たちが合成したものです
You know there's an inward arrow over here
ここに内向きの矢印があるのはご存知でしょう
There's an inward arrow
内向きの矢印があります
OK, didn't you just say that?
OK、それを言ったばかりではありませんか？
N and OH are stronger
NとOHの方が強い
N, OH and OH are relatively weak
N、OH、OHは比較的弱い
So let's just say, this place is what
それで言っておきますが、この場所は何ですか
This is its protein
これがそのタンパク質です
is its direct point, this is its direct point
はその直接点です、これはその直接点です
So we look at it this way
それで、私たちはそれをこのように見ます
it really has introverted arrows
本当に内向的な矢印がある
Because it exceeds, as long as it exceeds MMA, exceeds 10
超えているからMMAを超えれば10を超える
Probably what the slope of this place should be
おそらくこの場所の斜面はどうなるのだろう
produced by inward arrows
内向きの矢印によって生成される
We look at it in this very simple way
この非常に単純な方法でそれを見ていきます
Well, here is a very special one
さて、ここで非常に特別なものがあります
What about water, water is the most special thing, why
水はどうですか、水は最も特別なものです、なぜですか
One water has several falling arrows, four falling arrows
1つの水には数本の落ちてくる矢があり、4本の落ちてくる矢がある
A word of water, you see
水の一言、わかりますか
It can all form arrows, OK, basically
基本的にはすべて矢印を形成できます
So it's the single molecule that provides the highest arrow density in nature
つまり、自然界で最も高い矢密度を提供するのは単一の分子です
one thing for sure
一つ確かなこと
And look at this place, it's starting to form ice
そしてこの場所を見てください、氷ができ始めています
it's starting to form ice, ok, basically
氷ができ始めています、わかりました、基本的に
It's a calculation, it's starting to form ice
これは計算だ、氷ができ始める
If you look at this place
この場所を見てみると
Generally speaking, we talk about
一般的に言えば、私たちが話すのは、
There should be someone who is making energy water, OK, basically speaking
エネルギーウォーターを作っている人がいるはずです、基本的に言えば
this
これ
Basically, all energy water is
基本的にすべてのエネルギー水は、
It forms different, this is still hexagonal packing
形状が異なりますが、これは依然として六角形のパッキンです
but what makes a difference
しかし何が違いを生むのか
Different from what we call the People's Gang
私たちが人民ギャングと呼んでいるものとは異なります
It forms the principle of different Chinese gangs, ok
それは中国のさまざまなギャングの原則を形成しています、わかりました
Then some people said, ah, why are these different energies?
すると何人かの人々は、ああ、なぜこれらのエネルギーが違うのでしょう、と言いました。
Actually it's all one
実は全部一つなんです
A hexagonal closest packing is actually the same
六方最密充填は実際には同じです
It's different only in what
何が違うのかだけ
It is polycrystalline
多結晶です
How fine is this polycrystalline?
この多結晶はどれくらい細かいのでしょうか？
can give you a different way
別の方法を提供できる
Then tell me, does this have any different energy?
それなら教えてください、これには何か違うエネルギーがあるのでしょうか？
I don't dare to tell you that I do scientific research
私が科学研究をしているとはあえて言いません
But we've been doing this different shape recently
でも、最近は違う形をやっているんです
ok, cause this is under different pressure
大丈夫、それは別のプレッシャーの下でのことだから
you can form different words
さまざまな単語を作ることができます
We found that we hacked our molecules into here
私たちは分子をここにハッキングしたことがわかりました
Its radiance is not quite the same
その輝きはまったく同じではありません
ok, but this has nothing to do with energy water
まあ、これはエネルギーウォーターとは関係ありません
I just want to tell you one thing, that this is actually
一つだけ言っておきたいのは、これは実際にあるということです
It is a so-called polycrystalline
いわゆる多結晶体です
it's so detailed
とても詳しいです
Ok, how fine this is depends on different environments
OK、これがどの程度優れているかは環境によって異なります
it can make a difference, it's true
それは違いを生むことができる、それは本当だ
I admit it
認めます
Does it have any energy? I dare not admit it
エネルギーがあるの? 認められないよ
ok, but because from a scientific point of view, but it does
まあ、科学的な観点から言えばそうだけどね
actually there is a difference
実際には違いがあります
Okay, so let's talk about Chizi and Qingjian
さて、それではChiziとQingjianについて話しましょう
ok now talk about pool transfer
さて、プール送迎について話しましょう
because wait a minute my main
ちょっと待って、私のメインだから
main central idea
主要な中心的なアイデア
ok transfer in pool
OK、プールで移動
what pool transfer
どのようなプール転送
The easiest thing to think about is acid-base neutralization.
最も簡単に考えられるのは、酸塩基の中和です。
Acid-base neutralization you see
酸塩基の中和が見られます
it's a sour
それは酸っぱいです
It's an alkali, right?
アルカリですよね？
Ah, what is acid-base neutralization?
ああ、酸塩基中和って何ですか？
Just throw this acid to
この酸を投げるだけです
Eh, common, if it is the acid of Arrhenius
えー、普通、アレニウスの酸なら
throw it to him
それを彼に投げる
This is what was originally thrown to him at this place
これはもともとこの場所で彼に投げられたものです
ok, this is acid-base neutralization
OK、これは酸塩基の中和です
Isn't acid-base neutralization just to transfer the pool?
酸塩基の中和ってプールを移すだけじゃないの？
This is the same reason, ok, normal
これも同じ理由です、わかりました、普通です
Well this is in all of our modalities
まあ、これは私たちのすべてのモダリティに当てはまります
It's what you call everything you see
目に見えるものすべてをそれと呼ぶのです
No light, no time in this excited state
この興奮した状態では光も時間もありません
ok you see this
わかりました、これを見ました
But when in the excited state
しかし、興奮状態にあるときは、
that's more serious we like
それは私たちが好む深刻なものです
We say that when the pool shifts to an electronically excited state
プールが電子的に励起された状態に移行すると、
more likely to happen
起こる可能性が高くなります
ok this is in this basic state
OK、これはこの基本的な状態です
ok is in the most stable state
OKは最も安定した状態です
This is lighting several examples
これはいくつかの例を明らかにしています
Let's do our part
自分たちの役割を果たしましょう
Oh, but it's your duty to know
ああ、でも知るのはあなたの義務です
But duty is often used
しかし、義務はよく使われます
If you activate H-mea, it will be light, light paper
H-meaを有効にすると軽くて軽い紙になります
illuminate with light
光で照らす
light it up
照らして
What about after the excitation?
興奮した後はどうでしょうか？
very simple thing
とても単純なこと
I'll tell you about chemistry
化学についてお話します
You excite it is to put this electron
あなたが興奮するのはこの電子を置くことです
ok we call Pai Electronics
はい、パイエレクトロニクスに電話します
T to excited state
T から励起状態へ
that's what we call counterintelligence
それが私たちが対諜報活動と呼ぶものです
Shoot Star, Call Anti-Spies
シュートスター、アンチスパイを呼ぶ
Then you also know that we are from the middle school
それから私たちが中学校出身であることも知っています
start learning
学習を始める
ok here if you have kids
子供がいるならここで大丈夫
Sorry, there is no way in middle school
ごめんなさい、中学生では無理です
you can talk
話せます
why would you
なぜそうしますか
there will be this turtle ring
このタートルリングがあるでしょう
That is to conform to the beat electron of 4n plus 2
それは4nプラス2のビート電子に従うことです
I don't mean to say
言うつもりはない
Just 6 beat electrons in this place
この場所にはたった6ビートの電子がある
Is 4n equal to 1?
4nは1に等しいですか?
ok you drop an electron T
はい、電子を落とします T
It becomes unstable when it becomes five beat electrons
5ビート電子になると不安定になる
What to do if it is unstable
不安定な場合の対処法
He needs to hurry up and get an electron into it.
急いで電子を取り込まなければなりません。
where did he get it
彼はどこでそれを手に入れたのですか
If there is an OH here
ここにOHがあれば
Doesn't it have OH itself?
OH自体はないんですか？
There's a so-called lone electron
いわゆる孤立電子があります
Lonely electricity Lone with electrons, quickly fill in the electrons
孤独な電気 電子と孤独 早く電子埋めて
Once filled in
記入したら
this stable
この安定した
But after stabilization
しかし安定してからは
After filling this in
これを記入した後、
After becoming less electron
電子が少なくなってから
This Proton is very sour
このプロトンはとても酸っぱいです
super sour
超酸っぱい
How sour? Let's see
どのくらい酸っぱいですか? 見てみましょう
basically in
基本的には
look
見て
In fact, the duty lies in
実際、その義務は次のとおりです。
At the time of this GroundState
この GroundState の時点で
ok we generally see
わかりました、私たちは一般的に見ます
9.8 is a bit less
9.8はちょっと少ないですね
But in the excited state it is -0.1
ただし励起状態では -0.1
acidic than sulfuric acid
硫酸より酸性
it is more acidic than sulfuric acid
硫酸よりも酸性です
So this H will run away
だからこのHは逃げるだろう
Run away and become O-Fu-H-Zen
逃げてO-Fu-H-Zenになる
We call this acid Photosac
私たちはこれをフォトサックと呼んでいます
When exposed to light, it produces acid that is more acidic than sulfuric acid
光が当たると硫酸よりも酸性の強い酸が発生します。
Because this magnetic paper will be thrown away
このマグネット紙は捨てられるから
Throwing this into the water means throwing it into the water for hydration.
これを水に投げ込むということは、水分補給のために水に投げ込むことを意味します。
If we create an environment
環境を作れば
This environment is after the Proton magnetic paper is thrown away.
プロトン磁性紙を捨てた後の環境です。
There is a pair of scissors
ハサミがあります
in this molecule it can accept it
この分子ではそれを受け入れることができます
that would be fun
楽しそう
Let me give you an example let's look at this
例を挙げてみましょう。これを見てみましょう
OK, so I'll design a random molecule
OK、それではランダムな分子を設計してみます
This molecule is very acidic after being exposed to light.
この分子は光にさらされると非常に酸性になります。
But I have a scissors here
でも私はここにハサミを持っています
This Pyridine is cut
このピリジンはカットされています
N is a scissor
Nはハサミです
So it would have produced a molecular internal clearance in this place
したがって、この場所に分子の内部クリアランスが生じたでしょう
So after you light it, it is very sour, where will it go?
火をつけるととても酸っぱいのですが、どこへ行くのでしょうか？
It's here to cut
カットするのはここです
So after the light was illuminated, the magnetic paper was originally in this place.
つまり、ライトが点灯した後、磁気紙は元々この場所にありました。
it switches to this place
この場所に切り替わります
When you switch to this place, you will know one thing is
この場所に切り替えると、次のことがわかります。
tell you according to organic chemistry
有機化学に従って教えてください
This whole shoot together will be reassembled once again
この撮影全体がもう一度組み立てられます
So it's actually isomers
つまり、実際には異性体です
But this shot is completely different from this shot
しかし、このショットはこのショットとはまったく異なります
So an excitation would have been 330 which is in UV
したがって、励起は UV にある 330 になります。
What happens when it's triggered
トリガーされると何が起こるか
If it becomes different, it emits green light
異なる場合は緑色に発光
will turn into green light
緑色の光に変わります
it's an interesting thing
それは興味深いことです
Then this...
それからこれは...
You said teacher, what are you doing?
先生、何をしているの？と言いました。
You design this thing and we're actually doing spectral dynamics
あなたがこれを設計し、私たちは実際にスペクトルダイナミクスを行っています
Just ask this after the light...
明るくなってから聞いてください...
how fast is this finger
この指の速さはどれくらいですか
OK how fast and what steps to enter
OK、入力する速度と手順
it will move from here to this place
ここからここへ移動します
how fast
どのくらい速いのか
does it have energy
エネルギーはありますか
Why, why, actually we are researching
なぜ、なぜ、実際に私たちは研究しているのです
but today i won't talk
でも今日は話さない
Because of this talk everyone is asleep OK basically
この話だからみんな寝てるよ 基本的にOK
But to tell you one thing is I use an animation to tell you
でも、一つだけ言っておきたいのは、アニメーションを使って伝えたいということです
OK, for example, this lighting
OK、たとえばこの照明
How fast is it? About the same
どのくらい速いですか? ほぼ同じです
almost 55
ほぼ55
It's 5.5% to 10's sub-11 and it will pass in ten seconds
5.5から10サブ11です、10秒で通過します
how did it pass because it was like this
こんな感じだったのでどうやって通ったのか
You see it bends like this
こうやって曲がるのがわかります
Then after getting the same Distance
次に、同じ距離を取得した後、
he came from here
彼はここから来た
OK, you can see it and say
OK、あなたはそれを見て言うことができます
We are researching this
私たちはこれを研究しています
how fast is he
彼はどのくらい速いですか
or is he disabled
それとも彼は障害者ですか
why why
なぜなぜ
just this way
ちょうどこの方法で
I won't talk today, just talk to you
今日は話さないよ、ただ話してください
he has this condition
彼はこの症状を持っています
well, that excites the transfer in the instruction
そうですね、それは命令内の転送を刺激します
in fact, to be honest
実際、正直に言うと
what are you doing now
あなたは今何をしているの
still researching
まだ研究中
And it's a big one
そしてそれは大きなものです
That is to say, last year I organized a
つまり、昨年私は
A meeting in the United States
アメリカでの会合
Please help me with ACS
ACSを手伝ってください
basically speaking
基本的に言えば
Of course this is our design
もちろんこれは私たちのデザインです
I got this from JPCB
JPCBから頂きました
cover award, OK, basically
表紙賞、OK、基本的に
we design a
私たちはをデザインします
You see, after lighting with lightning
ほら、稲妻で照らした後
After lighting, this pro-tom
点灯後、このプロトムは
come here
ここに来て
That's because it's two common
それは2つが共通しているからです
One is me and one is at Georgia Tech
1 人は私、もう 1 人はジョージア工科大学にいます
OK, so from
はい、では、から
Running from Taiwan to Georgia Tech
台湾からジョージア工科大学まで走る
we would have written
私たちは書いただろう
Why are you writing it here?
なぜここにそれを書いているのですか？
Then what is the NPU Logo doing?
では、NPU ロゴは何をしているのでしょうか?
later rejected
後で拒否されました
It was rejected by the mainland, OK, basically speaking
基本的に言えば、本土によって拒否されました。
so this won't work
だからこれはうまくいきません
But it's like this now, ok
でも今はこんな感じです、大丈夫です
basically tell you he is still this
基本的に彼はまだこれだと言います
This was posted last month
これは先月投稿したものです
basically speaking
基本的に言えば
So he is still a big group
だから彼はまだ大きなグループだよ
Especially in Europe doing this
特にヨーロッパではこれを行っています
Fundamental Science的
基礎科学の
so much really
本当にとても
And the functions of Europeans are different
そしてヨーロッパ人の役割は異なります
When we have a meeting, we go outside the door to chat
会議があるとき、私たちはドアの外に出ておしゃべりをします
Why, what, the flash is gone
なんで、なんだ、フラッシュが消えた
the european sits over there
ヨーロッパ人はあそこに座っています
He won't leave from the first day to the seventh day
彼は初日から7日目まで出発しません
This is our different one
これは私たちの違うものです
one by one one by one attitude
一個一個一個一個一個attitude
Nature also uses machine gun bags to indicate transfer
自然はまた、移動を示すために機関銃バッグを使用します
come and see
見に来て
I give the simplest example
最も単純な例を挙げます
same reason
同じ理由
this is called
これは呼ばれます
it's flowering
開花しています
There are many petals in the flower
花にはたくさんの花びらがあります
You only need to see a little yellowish
少し黄色っぽく見えるだけで十分です
slightly yellowish
わずかに黄色がかった
Basically something like this
基本的にはこのようなものです
then why this thing
じゃあなぜこんなこと
come and see
見に来て
This thing is less than 400 in Xiguang
これは西光では400未満です
is UV
紫外線です
About 350 places
約350箇所
can you watch
見てもらえますか
In fact, at 350
実際、350では
OK 400 has not absorbed for so long
OK 400 は長い間吸収されていません
So everyone absorbs UV
つまり誰でも紫外線を吸収するのです
So as long as the sunlight is UV
つまり、太陽光が紫外線である限り、
it absorbs
それは吸収します
After absorbing it, use a very fast speed, how fast?
吸収した後は非常に速い速度で使用します。どのくらいの速度ですか?
OK, let's measure it first, about 60 DENTAL
OK、まずは測ってみましょう、約60DENTAL
It's as fast as -15 seconds at the 60th floor
60階では-15秒という速さです
Don't talk too fast, it will be right soon, OK
あまり早く話さないでください、すぐに決まります、OK
come soon
すぐに来る
Come to this place, the same score is easy to pass, optimistic
ここに来れば同スコアは通りやすい、楽観的
When the light shines, it's very sour here, very sour Proton
光が当たるとここはとても酸っぱい、とても酸っぱいプロトン
Just come over to this Cabernell
このカベルネルのところに来てください
Then come to this place
それならこの場所に来てください
So in this Ground state
したがって、このグラウンド状態では
it doesn't exist
それは存在しません
But it inspires attitude and it stabilizes
しかし、それは態度を刺激し、安定させます
So when it shines it is very
だからそれが輝くとき、それはとても
That energy level is very small
そのエネルギーレベルは非常に小さいです
Probably in the green range OK
おそらく緑の範囲内にあると思います。
So you take UV
それで紫外線を浴びます
Put it here quickly and then it turns green, what does it mean
すぐにここに置くと緑色になります、これは何を意味しますか
Isn't that the same as putting on sunscreen?
日焼け止めを塗るのと同じじゃないですか？
For you to wear sunscreen means
あなたが日焼け止めを塗るということは、
Even the flowers are covered with sunscreen
花も日焼け止め塗ってます
OK after UV up
UVアップ後もOK
If you don’t put UV on, put some green light on it right away
UVをつけていない場合は、すぐに緑色のライトを当ててください
Why put green, it's fine if you don't emit light
なぜ緑を入れるのか、発光しなくても大丈夫です
Our sunscreen, I shine, no
私たちの日焼け止め、私は輝いています、いいえ
why shine
なぜ輝くのか
Reabsorbed by Ye Lishu
Ye Lishuに再吸収される
do it again
再びそれを行う
Just look how smart that natural evolution is
自然の進化がいかに賢明であるかを見てください
Right so natural evolution you have to believe how smart he really is
まさに自然な進化、彼が本当に賢いことを信じなければなりません
so you look at this place in western state
それで西部州のこの場所を見てみると
He shines for such a long time, what should the light normally be?
彼はとても長い間光っていますが、光は通常どのようなものでしょうか？
next to this one in his west light
西の光の中でこの隣に
But he shines in such a long range
しかし、彼は非常に長い距離で輝きます
Western State UV beams on green
ウェストステート州の緑の紫外線ビーム
Okay, I'll take this Kang and let it go today.
さて、このカンを今日は手放します。
Let's see one thing is
一つ見てみましょう
fun thing
楽しいこと
this
これ
Forget it, don't turn it off, let's take a look
忘れて、消さないで、見てみましょう
OK let's take a look at this
はい、これを見てみましょう
Wait a minute, this can is what you see
ちょっと待って、この缶が見えます
this is transparent all transparent
これは透明です 全部透明です
As far as he is in UV, he has nothing at all
UVにいる限り、彼には何もありません
he just isn't visible
彼は見えないだけです
If visible he has color
目に見えるなら彼には色がある
it's all transparent
それはすべて透明です
If it is transparent first, let me see
まずは透明になったら見てみましょう
I didn't fake it, it must be like this
捏造してないよ、きっとこうなんだよ
OK basically speaking
基本的に言えばOK
I use UV light
紫外線ライトを使用しています
But UV light?
でも紫外線は？
Yes it is UV light
そう、紫外線です
I use UV light you see
ご覧のとおり、UVライトを使用しています
it's fully transparent
完全に透明です
OK so of course he is
OK、もちろん彼はそうです
green
緑
And it's green, it's green, it's green
そしてそれは緑です、それは緑です、それは緑です
OK basically
基本的にOK
he does it this way ok
彼はこうやってやります、大丈夫です
to take what
何をとるか
Metabolize these OK basically
基本的にこれらを代謝すればOK
So it's an interesting thought
それは興味深い考えですね
I told you some
いくつか話しました
That is to say, it actually has this function
つまり、実はこんな機能があるのです
Of course, we have many such applications in scientific research.
もちろん、科学研究にはそのようなアプリケーションがたくさんあります。
I give the simplest application
最も簡単なアプリケーションを紹介します
In fact, this app is where you inspire this place
実際、このアプリはあなたがこの場所にインスピレーションを与える場所です
it's coming to this place soon
もうすぐこの場所に来ます
Then it's slow after coming down
そして下りてからが遅い
Down is 10 - 9 is square seconds
ダウンは 10 - 9 は平方秒です
-15 of this 10 is square seconds
この 10 のうち -15 は平方秒です
-9 out of 10 this is fast again
-9/10 これはまた速いです
This is also 10-14-15
こちらも10-14-15
The representative said jump up
代表者は飛び上がって言った
Einstein told you about jumping up
アインシュタインは飛び上がることについてあなたに言いました
Immediately spawn a bunch of
すぐに大量のを生成します
A bunch with this place is no
この場所の束はノーです
produces the so-called population inversion
いわゆる反転分布を引き起こします
called G volume reversal
Gボリュームリバーサルと呼ばれる
After the G quantity is reversed, the laser will come down immediately.
G量が逆転するとすぐにレーザーが降りてきます。
This is why we can see lasers
これがレーザーが見える理由です
Of course I can't show it
もちろんお見せできません
you know my lab is down
私の研究室がダウンしているのは知っていますね
That laser comes out beautifully.
レーザーが綺麗に出ますね。
So it's all lasers
つまり、すべてレーザーです
Basically it's a great laser
基本的には素晴らしいレーザーです
let's take a look
見てみましょう
Is there any red one?
赤いのはありますか？
you said only green
あなたは緑だけと言った
Do you have others?
他にもいますか？
Yes, you can give me an example
はい、例を挙げていただけますか
look at this kang fat
このカンファットを見てください
OK, this Kang Fat is the same
OK、このカンファも同じです
Can you see it?
見えますか？
if you can't see look here
見えない場合はここを見てください
Because it's blocked below OK
以下ブロックされているのでOK
So what can OH and N OK form
それでは、OH と N OK は何を形成できるのでしょうか
Form a Hydrogen Bump OK
水素バンプ形成OK
So it's the same when it's illuminated
点灯時も同様です
this gets sour
これは酸っぱくなる
Wherever you go, you have to go to this place
どこに行っても、この場所に行かなければなりません
How fast? About 60 Fendals
どれくらい速いですか? フェンダル約 60 個
What is the plural of 60 to 10?
60対10の複数は何ですか?
Bump it in this place
この場所にぶつけてください
Then down comes the red light
そして赤い光が降りてくる
If you don't believe me, I'm going to show you this
信じられないなら、これをお見せします
I am more beautiful, OK, let me take a look
私はもっ​​と美しいです、わかりました、見てみましょう
Yes, I'll take a look
はい、見てみます
should be in
入っているはずです
we are bullish
私たちは強気です
This also needs to be transparent.
これも透明である必要があります。
OK you look transparent
わかりました、透明に見えます
Then I will make UVU, this 360 will definitely work
じゃあUVU作るよ、この360は絶対動くよ
red bright red
真っ赤な赤
OK so you look beautiful OK
OK、それではあなたは美しく見えます OK
Basically it's fine
基本的には大丈夫です
Just use this way OK
このまま使えばOK
I put it here when I finish everything
全部終わったらここに置きます
Indicates that I am not cheating OK
不正行為をしていないことを示します。
ok let's see
わかりました、見てみましょう
So one thing for everyone is
そこで、皆さんにとって一つのことは、
you know what to say
あなたは何を言うべきか知っていますか
it really is
本当にそうです
ok say this
わかりました、これを言ってください
What is this for
これは何のため
wait a minute i'll tell you
ちょっと待ってください、教えます
There is a super useful place OK
超便利な場所ありますよ
Everyone, if you listen to
みなさん、聞いていただければ、
You can also go back and try
戻って試してみることもできます
Green fluorescent protein also belongs to the type of direct transfer of G-Pythonite
緑色蛍光タンパク質もG-Pythoniteの直接伝達のタイプに属します
why? ok let's see
なぜ? わかりました、見てみましょう
For example, this is a green fluorescent protein
たとえば、これは緑色蛍光タンパク質です。
a major luminophore
主要な発光団
What is this luminescent group actually related to?
この発光基は実際には何と関係があるのでしょうか?
With H2O, with water, with Amino Acid
H2Oあり、水あり、アミノ酸あり
It is Amino Acid Residue
アミノ酸残基です
what does it produce
それは何を生み出すのか
The so-called complex, a clean complex
いわゆるコンプレックス、きれいなコンプレックス
So when you shine
だからあなたが輝くとき
In fact, the H will drop
実際、Hは下がります
It's so sour, just drop it
とても酸っぱいので、そのまま落としてください
Then go to this place to generate a massong relay called Massong Relay
次に、この場所に移動して、マッソンリレーと呼ばれるマッソンリレーを生成します
This Proton is coming this way
このプロトンがこちらに来ています
So use something like this
したがって、このようなものを使用してください
Actually it is a light
実はライトなんです
After this Proton is dropped
このプロトンが投下された後
Synthesize it to produce a green glow
合成すると緑色に光ります
So what you see is a green glow
つまり、あなたが見ているのは緑色の輝きです
It's actually a Nion's glow
それは実際にはニオンの輝きです
basically you see a glow
基本的には輝きが見えます
But then you pick it up
でもその後、あなたはそれを拾います
you can cut it off
それを切り取ることができます
Because it's three Amino Acids that form this
これを形成しているのは3つのアミノ酸であるため、
after you take it off
それを脱いだ後
It's like this when you pick it up
手に取るとこんな感じ
Take it up and shine it
手に取って輝かせてください
nothing shines nothing nothing
何も輝かない 何もない
but the reason is simple
しかし理由は簡単です
Because inside the protein, it's stuck
たんぱく質の中にくっついているから
stuck in that place, it can't turn
そこに固まって曲がれない
nothing can be done
何もできない
But after a bunch of them pick it up
でも、大勢の人がそれを拾った後、
Like a light, this place is called Vinyl's Glue
光のようなここはVinyl's Glueと呼ばれる
it keeps turning
それは回り続ける
OK, so go up
はい、それでは上がってください
It was supposed to light up, but it kept spinning
点灯するはずだったのに回り続けた
come down in this form
この形で降りてくる
So it doesn't shine, it doesn't shine at all
だから光らない、全く光らない
You see, this quantum yield is a negative thing for a small moment
ご存知のとおり、この量子収量はほんの一瞬だけマイナスになります。
It means that there is nothing to say, and there is no light at all.
それは何も言うことがなく、光がまったくないことを意味します。
OK, what about my lab?
さて、私の研究室はどうでしょうか？
It's very simple, you see how we do it
とてもシンプルです。やり方はわかりますね
We have a very simple thinking
私たちの考え方は非常にシンプルです
OH in this place
ああ、こんなところに
I'll turn it around, turn it over to this place
回してあげるよ、この場所に回してあげるよ
Drawing is very simple, OK
描画は非常に簡単です、OK
It is very difficult to learn to draw
絵を描くことを学ぶのはとても難しい
Just move this OH over here
この OH をここに移動してください
Let's see what it looks like when we move over here
こっちに移動したらどんな感じになるか見てみましょう
Wouldn't it be great if it became like this?
こうなったら素晴らしいと思いませんか？
You see, if you change to OH and change to this place
ほら、OHに乗り換えてここに乗り換えれば
Originally in this place it will turn
もともとこの場所で曲がるだろう
But when there is a clear view here, it will not turn
でもここに視界があれば曲がらない
It turns very little, it's not no turning, but very little turning
ほとんど回らない、回らないわけではないが、ほとんど回らない
OK, so of course it's possible
OK、もちろんそれは可能です
And when I shine, I don't need any water why
そして私が輝くとき、なぜ水は必要ないのですか？
what it sees in itself
それ自体が見ているもの
It will come and produce light
それはやって来て光を生み出すだろう
Is it possible like this?
このようなことは可能でしょうか？
This is what we have done since 2007 and 2008
これは私たちが 2007 年と 2008 年から行ってきたことです
there is a series
シリーズがあります
Probably all of them were developed in our laboratory.
おそらくそれらはすべて私たちの研究室で開発されたものです。
you see it is very simple
とてもシンプルです
This is natural
これは自然なことです
OK man-made we just put this OH
OK、人工物です、これを置くだけです OH
move over here
ここに移動してください
OK once the light is on
OK 一照光以後
become what
何になる
it can shine like that
こんなに輝けるんだ
For example, we can use different substitution machines
たとえば、さまざまな置換マシンを使用できます。
in this place, in this place
この場所で、この場所で
we can go all the way
私たちはどこまでも行くことができます
From yellow, orange, red
黄色、オレンジ、赤から
Even to this unseen Neon Infrared
目に見えないこのネオン赤外線まで
OK can do this
OK、これはできます
We are more powerful recently
最近はさらにパワーアップしてます
We don't think saying a Hide-Age Gold Rod is strong enough
Hide-Age Gold Rod が十分に強いとは思えません
so what do we do
どうしようか
Let's just take this Hide-Age Gold Rod
このHide-Age Gold Rodを持って行こう
LOG it for later
後で使うためにログに記録しておきます
Then use the above synthetic method
次に、上記の合成方法を使用します
LOG it again
もう一度ログに記録してください
If you see this place, put it in the LOG
この場所を見かけたらLOGに書き込んでください
So after LOG live
ということでLOGライブが終わってから
The two LOGs are called Double LOGs.
2 つの LOG をダブル LOG と呼びます。
camera hair
カメラの髪
You see, LASING will be produced immediately
ほら、LASING はすぐに生成されます
ok why
わかりました、なぜ
Because it emits strong light
強い光を発するので
So produce LASING immediately
したがって、すぐに LASING を生成してください
so very very beautiful
とてもとてもとても美しい
what i basically say
私が基本的に言っていること
OK so you see
OK、わかりました
When we shine light, a laser is emitted
光を当てるとレーザーが発せられます
But these two places you can tell it's lasers
でも、この 2 か所はレーザーだとわかります
OK basically a beautiful experiment
OK、基本的には美しい実験です
OK of course you said
OK、もちろんあなたは言いました
Yes, you synthesized this
はい、これはあなたが合成したものです
and see if this is good
そしてこれが良いかどうか見てください
Of course not
もちろん違います
I use one please don't sleep
私はそれを使っています、眠らないでください
I'll talk with one
一人と話します
what the hell are we doing
私たちは一体何をしているのですか
actually what are we doing
実際、私たちは何をしているのですか
we use
を使用しております
Good, for example, our laboratory
いいですね、例えば私たちの研究室です
OK with a 25 minute laser
25分のレーザーでOK
OK 25 minutes is hard to do
OK、25分は大変です
If you are doing physics, you will know
物理をやっている人なら分かると思いますが、
OK, what we can do in chemistry is not easy
そうですね、化学でできることは単純ではありません
You see, after being stimulated
ほら、刺激されてから
OK we are
わかりました、私たちはです
because it's fast
速いから
In fact, it is synchronized here
実はここで同期されているんです
resonate with each other
互いに共鳴する
what do we call this
これを何と呼びますか
called
呼ばれた
called Ostration
オストレーションと呼ばれる
That's it
それでおしまい
we call
私たちは電話します
Someone called Quantum Bit
誰かが量子ビットと呼んだ
OK is the BitBitThing of Quantum
OK は量子の BitBitThing です
OK then from here
はい、ではここから
This is because this is over time
これは時間が経ったからです
You can exchange time for
時間を交換できるのは、
frequency
周波数
OK so use
わかりましたので使用してください
After converting with Fullure
Fullureで変換後
you convert to a 120 WebNumber
120 WebNumber に変換します
This is its OverTone
これがそのオーバートーンです
Just 120 WebNumber
ちょうど 120 ウェブナンバー
what does it mean
どういう意味ですか
In fact, this thing
実は、このことは、
How did the Program come here?
プログラムはどのようにしてここに来たのですか?
actually rely on what
実際に何に依存するか
rely on this
これに頼ってください
One turn and pass
1ターンしてパス
OK so a bend
OK、曲がります
it vibrate
振動する
it goes by, so a vibration
過ぎていくから振動が
Just one vibration and it's gone
たった一度の振動で消えてしまいます
Then you said that the same translation has changed here
それから、同じ翻訳がここで変更されたと言いました
how do you know its structure
その構造をどうやって知っていますか
What are its molecules?
その分子は何ですか?
Very simple, we also make a so-called
非常に簡単ですが、いわゆる
transient IR, this is more difficult to do
一時的な IR、これを実行するのはさらに困難です
Just make an IR, that is, after you type it up
IR を作成するだけ、つまり入力した後に
then do another
それから別のことをする
With an IR, within fintosecond
IR の場合、フィント秒以内
Just put it on the probe
プローブに置くだけ
What can you get?
何がもらえるの？
You all get this is disappearing, this is generated
皆さんもわかりますか、これは消えて、これは生成されます
So the generation is this keytone
だから世代はこのキートーン
This is the place that disappeared
ここは消えた場所だ
so you know the generation disappears
だから世代が消えていくのはわかるだろう
Indeed it has been synonymized
確かに同義語になったな
In fact, we are doing these things
実際、私たちはこれらのことを行っています
Basically, it just shows you
基本的には、ただ表示するだけです
beautiful beautiful is in this place
美しい美しいはこの場所にあります
In fact, we do this thing
実際、私たちはこんなことをしています
so you know it's my lab
だから、ここが私の研究室だということは知っていますね
This is my real laboratory
ここが私の本当の研究室です
Synthesize that, of course I also have
それを合成して、もちろん私も持っています
But basically my lab is like this
でも基本的に私の研究室はこんな感じです
Anyway, it's all optics, so why?
とにかく、すべて光学式ですが、なぜでしょうか？
If you don't believe me, those few
私の言うことが信じられないなら、あの数人は
I also brought here
ここにも持ってきました
basically just the weirdest
基本的にはただ最も奇妙なものです
These are different
これらは異なります
I can produce different colors
さまざまな色を生み出すことができます
For example, just this
たとえば、これだけ
like this
このような
should be very red
とても赤いはずです
look
見て
very orange
とてもオレンジ色
So it just has to be
だからそれはただそうあるべきだ
There is Pronchance
プロチャンスがある
if you want red
赤が欲しいなら
that means i'm cheating
それは私が浮気していることを意味します
put it here
ここに置いてください
won't fall
落ちません
Red is getting harder
赤が難しくなってきた
cheat again
また騙す
Lingjian Village they know
彼らは知っている霊剣村
when you get redder
赤くなったら
the weaker the glow
輝きが弱くなる
but also red
でも赤もある
let's take a look
見てみましょう
just tell you one thing
一つだけ言ってください
If
もしも
any small piece
どんな小さな破片でも
this place
この場所
a lot of optics
たくさんの光学系
a lot of lenses
たくさんのレンズ
per lens
レンズごと
Probably less than 30,000
たぶん30万以下
We spend about five or six million together
私たちは一緒に約500万か600万を費やします
basically
基本的
It cost about five or six million yuan just to change.
変更するだけでも500～600万元くらいかかります。
definitely above ok
間違いなくOK以上です
So you know it costs nothing to say this
だから、これを言うのに何の費用もかからないことはわかります
ok let's see
わかりました、見てみましょう
that can just say
それはただ言える
if today this is sour
今日が酸っぱければ
it will come
それが来ます
then you have an idea
それならあなたにアイデアがあります
the idea is
アイデアは
you can't control it
あなたにはそれをコントロールすることはできません
mutual energy
相互エネルギー
So actually I am in this 20
つまり、実際に私はこの20位に入っています
About 3 years ago 4 years ago
約3年前 4年前
the idea is
アイデアは
just very very just
ただとてもとてもちょうど
can i control it
コントロールできますか
control it to
それを制御して
It was one sided
一方的だった
ok can i turn it into yes
オーケー、それを「はい」に変えてもいいですか
It's a thing called equilibrium
それは平衡と呼ばれるものです
is that it is balanced
バランスが取れているということです
ok actually we were in 2011
はい、実際には私たちは 2011 年にいたのです
also make it really balance
それも本当にバランスをとってください
ok let's not talk more
わかりました、これ以上は話さないようにしましょう
Just talk to you like this Kang Fat
こうやって君に話してよ カン・ファット
after a light
光の後
it can come here
それはここに来ることができます
If you can also ventilate
換気もできれば
it side
それ側
via magnet transfer
マグネット転写による
You can go here, you can go here
ここに行ってもいい、ここに行ってもいい
so you know
そうでしょ
one is 450
1つは450です
one is 600
1つは600です
Adding together is white light
足し合わせると白い光になる
So we can also make white light out
したがって、白色光を消すこともできます
So we are a single molecule
つまり私たちは単一の分子なのです
can make a white light
白色光を作ることができる
not very efficient
あまり効率的ではありません
But last month when we
しかし先月、私たちが
has developed another
別のものを開発しました
wow that game is even better
うわー、そのゲームはさらに良いです
OK
OK
That is pure white light
それは真っ白な光です
Can reach more than 6%
6%以上に達する可能性もある
OK then I won't talk much
わかりました、それ以上は言いません
OK because that hasn't been published yet
まだ公開されてないから大丈夫
so i can't speak
だから話せない
i can only say
私はただ言うことができます
this is absolutely possible
これは絶対に可能です
You see, with this thing a single molecule
ほら、これは単一の分子です
I can do white light
白色光もできるよ
because of the ease of passing
通りやすいから
OK basically
OK 基本上
it's a rare phenomenon
それは珍しい現象です
OK
OK
From this basic point of view
この基本的な観点から
what are we doing
私たちは何をしているのですか
Actually, I have one that is challenging the Invasion Sword
実はインベイジョンソードに挑戦しているのがあるんです
straight transfer limit
ストレート転送制限
what do you mean look
どういう意味ですか、見てください
Just talked about the first example
最初の例についてお話しました
This natural five
このナチュラルファイブ
this is the five rings
これがファイブリングです
i lose to you
私はあなたに負けます
1 2 3 4 5
１ ２ ３ ４ ５
A total of five round papers constitute the Invasion Sword
合計5枚の丸い紙がインベージョンソードを構成します
That this red man just now
この赤い男が今
is 1 2 3 4 5 6 6 rings
1 2 3 4 5 6 6 リングです
OK
OK
The six rings you can be OH and N
OHにもNにもなれる6つのリング
You can also be N
あなたもNになれます
You can also be N and NH
NやNHにもなれる
This is fine, the six rings
これでいいよ、6つの指輪
OK
OK
Seven rings is what I just said
セブンリングは私が今言ったことです
So-called
所謂的
so-called fluorescent proteins
いわゆる蛍光タンパク質
move it OH over here
ああ、ここに移動してください
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, the seven-membered ring
1、2、3、4、5、6、7、7員環
Let's talk about where the limit is
限界がどこにあるのか話しましょう
So we spent a year
それで私たちは1年を費やしました
This session is challenging and fun
このセッションは挑戦的で楽しいです
Basically we make eight-membered rings
基本的には8員環を作ります
The answer is, teacher, how do you do this?
答えは、先生、どうやってやるのですか？
let me tell you okay
大丈夫と言わせてください
In my laboratory is my design
私の研究室には私のデザインがあります
I'll come over after I finish designing
デザインが終わったら来ます
can this be done
これはできるでしょうか
The answer says to start looking for basically
答えは、基本的に探し始めることを示しています
so you know i'm mistaken
だからあなたは私が間違っていることを知っています
But I just talked to Vice President Wang
でも、私は王副総統と話したところです
I have a team dedicated to compositing
合成専門のチームがいます
There are three post stars in charge of this thing
このことを担当するポストスターは 3 人います
just do it
早くやれよ
I design can you do it
私がデザインします、やってもらえますか
In the end, what we made was an eight-membered ring.
最終的にできたのは8員環でした。
The eight-membered ring emits about 700
8員環からは約700個の光が放出される。
Already very weak very weak but it is there
すでに非常に弱い非常に弱いですが、それはそこにあります
Is there a nine-membered ring?
９員環はあるのでしょうか？
In fact, I have already designed it and can't make it.
実は、もうデザインしてしまったのですが、作ることができません。
Then see what you do along the way
その後、途中で何をするか見てみましょう
a few rings
いくつかの指輪
it's an interesting thing
それは興味深いことです
Now we're making eight-membered rings
今、8員環を作っています
The eight-membered ring should be the current limit.
8 員環が現在の限界であるはずです。
basically
基本上
That's what I just said
それが私が今言ったことです
Probably more OH
おそらくもっとOHするでしょう
OK, is there any other Bounding recently?
OK、最近他にバウンディングはありますか?
I just said that N is also okay, right?
先ほどNさんも大丈夫って言いましたよね？
Then why is this important? You see, what we are developing now is more important.
では、なぜこれが重要なのでしょうか? ご存知のとおり、私たちが現在開発しているものの方が重要です。
What is the reason? Just now OH you also know that one O can only have two sticks
理由は何ですか? たった今、あなたも知っていますよね、1 人の O はスティックを 2 本しか持てません
Right, but N is different
そうですね、でもNは違います
If there is an H on the N side, there is an H on this side, you can broaden your horizons
NにHがあればこっちにもHがある、視野が広がる
to do so-called modification, chemical modification
いわゆる修飾、化学修飾を行うこと
This is important because NH2 is not acidic enough
NH2 は十分に酸性ではないため、これは重要です
In fact, NH2 is a bit alkaline and not acidic enough.
実際、NH2 はわずかにアルカリ性であり、十分な酸性ではありません。
So here we design a pull electron
ここでプル電子を設計します
OK pull very strongly, such as Tosio Group
トシオグループなど、非常に強く引っ張るOK
Let's not talk too much, just like this group
このグループのように、あまり話さないようにしましょう
OK is a SOO
OKはSOOです
Like this, this, if this pulls electrons very strongly
こう、これ、これが電子を強く引っ張ったら
After pulling this, what can this place do? It's sour.
これを引いた後、ここは何ができるかというと、酸っぱいんです。
it can do direct transfer
直接転送ができます
So you see we use chemical modification to modify it and we can do it
つまり、化学修飾を使用してそれを変更することができます。
OK basically speaking so you know what to say
OK、基本的には話せますので、何を言えばいいかわかります
How sour or not sour are we doing this way
この方法でどのくらい酸っぱいのか、酸っぱくないのか
Why, why, why, we can tune it to connect with each other
なぜ、なぜ、なぜ、お互いにつながるように調整できます
What can we tune in now? It’s the same as before
今、何をチューニングできますか? 以前と同じです
Better yet, we're rationalizing Tune to white light
さらに良いことに、白色光に合わせて調整することを合理化しています。
So in this way you hear the white light
このようにして白い光が聞こえます
This combines synthetic
これは合成繊維を組み合わせたものです
everything together and apply
すべて一緒に応募してください
So definitely something to do in this place
だから間違いなくこの場所で何かをする必要があります
It can be said that chemistry is actually a family.
化学はまさに家族であると言えます。
It's up to you how to interpret it
それをどう解釈するかはあなた次第です
Basically it's one thing you can do
基本的にやるべきことは一つです
I give an example
例を挙げます
This example lets you examine
この例では、次のことを確認できます。
what am i doing now
私は今何をしているのですか
because of course since
もちろんそれ以来だから
After the National Science Council is changed to the Ministry of Science and Technology, you have to do some applications
国家学術会議が科学技術省に変更された後、いくつかの申請を行う必要があります
Otherwise you will be KO basically speaking
そうしないと基本的にKOされます
Then let me tell you about an application
それでは、アプリケーションについて説明させていただきます
it's fun
楽しいです
what is this application
このアプリケーションは何ですか
we look at one thing
私たちは一つのことを見ます
if today
もし今日なら
The screen we're looking at
私たちが見ている画面
This screen is called the absorption screen
このスクリーンを吸収スクリーンと呼びます
Keep playing a color and let you see the color over there
色を再生し続けて、そこにある色を見てみましょう
right
右
If you imagine this screen
この画面を想像すると
is transparent
透明です
transparent
透明
But there is RGB inside
しかし内部にはRGBがあります
There are Blue and Green and Red
青と緑と赤があります
The dye is in three layers
染料は三層になっている
OK
OK
and then yours
そしてあなたのもの
your this
あなたのこれ
Where's your projector?
プロジェクターはどこにありますか？
actually every color in it
実際にはその中のすべての色
When you load your picture into it
写真を読み込むと
it came out
それが出てきた
according to the diagram
図によると
In fact, there are three UV light
実は紫外線には3種類あります。
This UV light is invisible
この紫外線は目に見えない
call here
ここに電話してください
A light hit is for you blue
軽い打球は君にとっては青い
one light hit one green
一つの光が一つの緑に当たる
a light to red
ライトが赤に変わる
OK
OK
you regulate according to this
あなたはこれに従って規制します
you know what to say
あなたは何を言うべきか知っていますか
In this way, it is a full-color
このようにフルカラーです
Full color transparent screen
フルカラー透明スクリーン
Now it's the hottest
今が一番熱いです
OK basically speaking
基本的に言えばOK
is completely transparent
完全に透明です
but now do so far
しかし今はここまでやります
no
いいえ
what is the reason
理由は何ですか
They all use fluorescent powder
全て蛍光粉を使用しております
Phosphor powder is very unhappy
リン粉は非常に不幸です
very blurred
非常にぼやけた
OK
OK
basic
基本
Now the most famous is the inside of the car
今最も有名なのは車内です
look inside this car
この車の中を見てください
On top of this Winds Shear
このウィンズシアーの上に
Whatever the light-shielding glass is for?
遮光ガラスって何のためにあるの？
These
これらは
OK
OK
is above
上にあります
right here there is one like this
ここにこのようなものがあります
There is a Project
プロジェクトがあります
This Project is a Project
このプロジェクトはプロジェクトです
you see it's all green
全部緑色なのがわかりますか
Why else is it red?
またなぜ赤いのでしょうか？
It can't do full color
フルカラーはできない
Because technically it doesn't work
技術的にはうまくいかないから
OK technically it doesn't work
OK、技術的には機能しません
Why
なぜ
very simple
とてもシンプルな
If you don't show it
それを見せないと
You call Blue, will Blue get Red in this place?
あなたはブルーに電話しますが、ブルーはこの場所でレッドを手に入れることができますか?
meeting
ミーティング
Why? Because you have Red means there will be in Blue
なぜですか? 赤があるということは、青にもあるということです
So you can never get past this level
だからこのレベルを超えることは決してできない
How do you get past this level? Can’t you just talk about it?
このレベルをどうやって乗り越えますか? それについて話すことはできませんか?
Inward direct transfer is absolutely possible
国内直接送金は完全に可能です
Why? Because the direct transfer is released by Cyub in the place of Red and Green
なぜですか? 直接転送は Red と Green の代わりに Cyub によってリリースされるためです。
So I know where to go to find my inner light
だから私は自分の内なる光を見つけるためにどこに行けばいいのか知っています
Then blue is enough to use ordinary blue
それなら青は普通の青で十分です
too much, ok
多すぎます、わかりました
Then this place you see when I fire up in Red
それから、私が赤で燃え上がると見えるこの場所
This place I get is such a long wavelength
私が得たこの場所はとても波長が長い
Right when it was Green I got to be in this place
緑のとき、私はこの場所にいなければならなかった
So this place is not absorbed, so just bypass
ここは吸収されないので迂回してください
i can see three
3つ見えます
Well, if you don't believe me, I just put these two in
信じられないなら、この 2 つを入れただけです
OK, put three layers, you can't see the three layers, but it's transparent
OK、レイヤーを 3 つ入れます。3 つのレイヤーは見えませんが、透明です。
OK, take a look
OK、見てみましょう
I know 380 is Green
380が緑なのは知っています
To 400, this color is not good, OK, it should be Red
400 までは、この色は良くありません、OK、赤にすべきです
to 420 is Blue
420まではブルー
You see, long wavelengths get short wavelengths
ほら、長い波長は短波長になります
Yes, long wavelengths get long wavelengths
そう、長い波長は長い波長になる
Cutting these three together is white light
この3つを切ると白い光になる
OK so don't underestimate it
OK、過小評価しないでください
Maybe I will be the billionaire chairman in the future
たぶん私は将来億万長者の会長になるでしょう
OK this could be
OK、これは可能性があります
just tell you look
ただ見てくださいと言ってください
This is a basic science
これは基礎科学です
But he can use it
でも彼はそれを使える
he can definitely use it
彼は間違いなくそれを使える
just tell you the truth
ただ真実を言ってください
actually i tell you
実は私はあなたに言います
fondamento is really important
フォンダメメントは本当に重要です
OK we're just fondamento
OK、私たちはただのフォンダメメントです
not this far
ここまでではない
so everyone said
それでみんなが言いました
ah why do what
ああ、なぜ何をするのか
you just have to get to a certain point
ある点まで到達する必要があるだけです
In fact, you must be rich
実際、あなたは金持ちに違いない
In fact, we have not reached this point
実際のところ、私たちはまだこの点に達していません
So it's always stuck in this place
だからいつもこの場所に詰まっている
okay, let me tell you
わかった、教えてあげよう
it might be ok
大丈夫かもしれない
then don't forget
それから忘れないでください
Just that grape palm tree
まさにそのブドウヤシの木
What are these things for?
これらは何のためにあるのでしょうか？
Hey, it took more than twenty years
ねえ、20年以上かかりました
right not two months
そうですね、2か月ではありません
not two years
2年ではない
right so of course
そうだね、もちろん
ok let's see
わかりました、見てみましょう
the shift that inspires here
ここでインスピレーションを与える変化
intermolecular
分子間
I give an example
例を挙げます
Just started with five-membered rings
五員環から始めました
It is impossible to make a gold rod with a four-membered ring
四員環で金棒を作るのは不可能
Right, four-membered ring one two three four is impossible
そうだよ、四員環 1 2 3 4 は無理だよ
Impossible to say this H and Z
このHとZを言うのは不可能です
Because of four impossible things
4つの不可能なことのせいで
how it was formed and made a gold rod
どのようにして金の棒が形成され、作られたのか
Hey let's see
ねえ、見てみましょう
It's between Dimer and it's double
ダイマーとダブルの間です
right this and this
そう、これとこれ
You can also see
こちらもご覧いただけます
I won't show once I'm excited, I'll tell you
興奮したら見せないよ、教えてあげる
Once activated, this Proton can come over
一度活性化すると、このプロトンはやって来ることができます
This Proton can come
このプロトンは来ることができます
Two, we call them Double Proton Transmitter
2 つ目は、ダブルプロトントランスミッターと呼ばれます。
Just switch two Protons together
2つのプロトンを一緒に切り替えるだけです
what green light you can get too
あなたもどのような緑色の光を得ることができますか
OK, so why is the Study so hard?
では、なぜ勉強はそんなに難しいのでしょうか?
did that just tell you
それはあなたに言ったばかりですか
look at some of our examples
私たちの例のいくつかを見てください
Let's take a look at the knowledge transfer in the DNA clipping team
DNA クリッピング チームにおける知識の伝達を見てみましょう
Can it happen? And entry produces mutations
それは起こりますか?そして侵入は突然変異を生み出します
This is 40 years, 50 years
これは40年、50年です
Wasn't and Click from this Wasn't
Wasn't とここをクリックしてください Wasn't
everyone is discussing this
みんながこれについて議論しています
OK, is it possible to mutate
OK、変異することは可能ですか
Because these two Proton
なぜならこの2つのプロトンは
OK, these two Protons
OK、この 2 つのプロトン
After hearing this, these two Double Proton
それを聞いてこの二人はダブルプロトン
When Proton comes with Switch, it needs to be flexible and easy to buy.
Proton が Switch に付属する場合、柔軟で購入しやすいものである必要があります。
Then start copying at this place
次に、この場所からコピーを開始します
there is a copy error
コピーエラーがあります
Actually this Wasn't the first to bring it up
実はそれを持ち出したのはこれが最初ではなかった
He said is it possible that
彼は、その可能性はあるのかと言いました
OK, that's easy from here
OK、ここからは簡単です
We want Study to say
スタディに言ってほしい
Is it possible that after the light is
光が当たった後という可能性はありますか？
Let the two ProtonSwitch
2つのProtonSwitchをしましょう
OK, generate Mutation
OK、ミューテーションを生成します
This is also me in 1990
これも1990年の私です
to 19 in about 2001, what about these 10 years
2001年くらいに19歳になったけど、この10年はどうだろう
My focus is very strong in this place
この場所での私の集中力は非常に強いです
I spend almost half of my manpower on this place
私は人的資源のほぼ半分をこの場所に費やしています
Because there were fewer people at that time
その時は人も少なかったので
But half of the people spent in this place
しかし、人々の半分はこの場所で過ごしました
It's a pity to tell you no
ノーと言うのは残念だ
you see why not
なぜそうしないのかわかりますか
I can tell the simplest truth now
私は今、最も単純な真実を言うことができます
after you shine
あなたが輝いた後
If you say this proteon is going to pass
このプロテオンが通過すると言ったら
This proteon is coming
このプロテオンがやってくる
I'm sorry that this synonym is too much
この同義語が多すぎて申し訳ありません
This is also synonymous
これも同義語ですね
Two synonymous transition energy is too high
2 つの同義の遷移エネルギーが高すぎます
impossible
不可能
so why do i know
それでなぜ私が知っているのですか
Because what do we do, it won't work, right?
だって、何をやってもうまくいかないじゃないですか。
But let's take a very simple acid touch
しかし、非常に単純なアシッドタッチを見てみましょう
We stuck acid in this place
ここに酸を突っ込んだ
If you get stuck at Adning
Adning で行き詰まったら
Contact acid can be used to form Diamond
接触酸を使用してダイヤモンドを形成できる
How do you know it's a Diamond
それがダイヤモンドだとどうやってわかるのですか
Because it can be seen from the absorption
吸収でわかるから
I won't draw it
描かないよ
It forms a Diamond with my light
私の光でダイヤモンドを形成します
it produces a green glow
緑色の輝きを生み出します
And red or green shine
そして赤や緑に光る
just tell you one thing is
ただ一つだけ言っておきます
In fact, this can be proteon switch
実際、これはプロテオンスイッチである可能性があります
no problem
問題ない
Then, teacher, what is the difference between here and here?
では、先生、こことここの違いは何ですか？
Where is the difference
違いはどこにありますか
You see, this is the change of both
ほら、これは両方の変化です
This is the subject is the subject, anyway both will change
これは本題と本題ですが、とにかく両方とも変わらなければなりません。
But what about this, if this is the subject of the project?
しかし、これがプロジェクトの主題である場合、これはどうなるでしょうか？
The main body has changed, has the topic changed or not?
本文が変わりましたが、話題は変わりましたか？
Why because COH is still COH
なぜCOHはCOHのままなのか
OK, I didn’t name this one Catalytic Time
OK、これを Catalytic Time と名付けたわけではありません
Actually when I sent out the first one in 1999
実は1999年に最初のものを出したときは
Oh, what about that Propel Jax
ああ、プロペルジャックスはどうですか？
Come back in a week and say incredible
1週間後にまた来て、信じられないほどのことを言ってください
how do you think of such a thing
そのようなことをどう思いますか
Ah, this is, ah, why do you keep talking about 1999?
ああ、これは、ああ、なぜあなたは 1999 年のことを話し続けるのですか?
OK someone over here should know
OK、ここにいる誰かが知っているはずです
Because there were no instruments at that time
当時は楽器がなかったから
And why not after a while because of the big earthquake
そして、大地震のせいでしばらくしてからではないでしょうか？
In Chung Cheng University OK later the instrument was burned
中正大学ではその後器具が焼かれました
So there is nothing, nothing depends on the brain
だから何もない、何も脳に依存しない
Just us, you have nothing to do, just rely on your brain
私たちだけ、あなたは何もすることがない、ただ自分の脳に頼ってください
OK, just think about these things in your head, it's not healthy
OK、これらのことを頭の中で考えてください、それは健康的ではありません
Let's see if it's possible, right? No need for instruments.
それが可能かどうか見てみましょう? 器具は必要ありません。
You can still do it so I'll tell you
まだできるから教えてあげる
Rely on your brain when you have no money
お金がないときは自分の脳に頼る
OK, your brain will always figure it out
OK、あなたの脳は常にそれを理解します
Of course, what Dean Wang said is correct, because I am a workaholic
もちろん、ディーン・ワンの言っていることは正しい、私はワーカホリックだから
So basically I can't learn it, just thinking here OK
基本的には学習できないので、ここで考えるだけで OK
You see, after the big earthquake
ほら、大地震の後
More than a year, published three consecutive days OK
1年以上、3日連続掲載OK
Everything is the simplest concept
すべては最も単純な概念です
I didn't lie to you, it's just a concept
私はあなたに嘘をついていません、それは単なる概念です
Nothing to do, just do the simplest things like this
何もする必要はありません。このような最も単純なことを行うだけです
OK, so we're going to call it Catalyst type
OK、それでは触媒タイプと呼ぶことにします
OK, that's the catalyst, because it doesn't move
OK、それは触媒です、動かないからです
This is not called catalysis, so it won't work
これは触媒とは呼ばれないので、機能しません
it's that simple
それはとても簡単です
ok , then i will give you a better example
わかりました、それならもっと良い例をあげます
Let's start from here
ここから始めましょう
How to derive it? You see
それをどうやって導き出すか?
we derive, for example, we synthesize
たとえば、合成したり、導出したりします。
You said that the synthesis is not difficult, not difficult
合成は難しくない、難しくないって言ってたね
Because he has already synthesized it, but he doesn't want to do it
すでに合成したけどやりたくないから
OK, I'll do it from this place, ah, it works
はい、ここからやってみます、ああ、うまくいきます
Why is it useful, you see this place for the same reason
なぜ役に立つのですか、あなたも同じ理由でこの場所を見ています
You see, Acoho or water words
ほら、アコホとか水の言葉とか
If it's Acoho water, you see
アコホ水ならわかる
If this stuck in this place, a fire
ここに詰まると火災になります
It's still the same, Acoho is still Acoho, but this will change
相変わらず、アコホはアコホ、でも変わるよ
OK, if that's the case
OK、それなら
Because people dropped him from this Urea
人々が彼をこの尿素から落としたからです
They are synthesized to remove Urea's derivatives
尿素誘導体を除去するために合成されています。
I said, ah, how to do this
私は言いました、ああ、これをどうやって行うか
This is obviously in Acoho water
これは明らかにアコホ水に入っています
It should be easy to buy
買いやすいはず
Because both will change
どっちも変わるから
So it won't, so it should be no entry
そうならないので、エントリーしないはずです
This should be Rate
これはレートである必要があります
in organic people do this stuff
オーガニックでは人々はこのようなことをします
just watch normal MMA
普通の総合格闘技を見ればいい
Just take a look, right?
ちょっと見てみてくださいね？
This should be Blue, this should be Rate
これは青、これはレートである必要があります
Is there such a possibility?
そのような可能性はありますか？
I say learn to synthesize
私は合成することを学びなさいと言います
OK, this is not a very difficult thing
OK、これはそれほど難しいことではありません
So they start to synthesize
それで彼らは合成を始めます
After the synthesis is completed, you can see
合成が完了すると、次のようになります。
but we added a group
でもグループを追加しました
We added a COO group
COOグループを追加しました
Why? Because it is better to make it water soluble
なぜかというと、水溶性にした方が良いからです。
OK, look, in the water
OK、見てください、水の中です
so my consciousness is right
だから私の意識は正しい
My consciousness, well, my consciousness can just talk
私の意識は、まあ、私の意識はただ話すことができます
I am better than people without this knowledge
私はこの知識のない人よりも優れています
It's 10 times more likely, that's all I am
可能性は10倍、それが私だけです
As long as the chance of winning is 10 times, or 100 times, that's all
勝算が10倍でも100倍でもあればそれでいい
OK, I can’t say they’re all right, if you can’t make them all, then you can’t
OK、全部大丈夫とは言えません、全部作れないなら作れない
I can't help it either
それも仕方ないよ
OK, but like this
わかりましたが、このように
OK, let's force it in later
OK、後で強制的に入れましょう
look what it looks like
それがどのように見えるかを見てください
After the card is in, eh, it’s gone
カードが入ったら、え、なくなった
Yes, so this is a RUN concept
はい、これがRUNのコンセプトです
nothing
なし
Hey, let me tell you, okay?
ねえ、教えてあげましょう、いいですか？
I didn't even measure the spectrum.
スペクトルすら測定していない。
Just take one photo, and there is no equipment
写真を1枚撮るだけで、機材は必要ありません
Just shine like this, shine like this
このまま輝いて、このまま輝いて
Super published, OK, basically speaking
超出版、OK、基本的に言えば
It's just a matter of concept, it's an obvious thing
それは単なる概念の問題であり、明白なことです
Tell me, hey, it works
教えて、ねえ、それはうまくいきます
ok we'll be back
わかりました、また戻ってきます
This just this India
これはまさにこのインド
Yes, Morigata Ajaw, this place in India
そう、アジャ・モリ、インドのここです。
Didn't you just say that Dimer is okay?
さっきダイマーは大丈夫って言ったよね？
Well if Dimer can
それでダイマーができるなら
That can also be done in Ako
赤穂でもそれができる
Of course not wrong
もちろん間違ってはいません
Look inside Ako
アコの中を見てください
this is in
これは入っています
This time in Cyco Accent in that Langpora
今回はそのランポラにサイコアクセント
There is no software in Proton
Protonにはソフトウェアはありません
it is a light
それは光です
But in Ako there are only two lights
でも赤穂には梁が2本しかない
what is this
これは何ですか
This is the oversynthesis of it
これは過剰合成です
Make a catalytic reaction from this place
ここから触媒反応を起こす
come this way
こちらに来てください
OK good
いいよ
don't do a magic trick in this place
ここで手品をしないでください
look at this
これを見てください
this is more fun
これはもっと楽しいです
This place has Ako
この場所にはアコがあります
so i am
そう私は
I casually
私は何気なく
Come on, let's take this example
さあ、この例を見てみましょう
Look, this bottle is
ほら、このボトルは
It's also transparent, right?
これも透明ですよね？
Habits of transparency
透明性の習慣
This might turn off the lights
これで照明が消えるかもしれない
wait a minute
等一下 等一下
OK look
わかりました、見てください
Then this time in Cyco Accent
では今度はサイコアクセントで
I know a little bit of Ako
アコさんのことは少しだけ知っています
Super Sensitive
超敏感
Era-6M Lipstick
時代-6M的儀唇
it becomes like this
このようになります
It is OK that it combines super strong
超強力を組み合わせてもOK
basically
基本的
so let's see
それでは見てみましょう
The answer is how it looks OK
答えは、どのように見えるかです。
what about this
これはどうですか
as soon as you shine
あなたが輝けばすぐに
OK this
はい、これ
After you shine on the light, you basically talk
ライトに照らされた後は基本的に会話します
it is probably
おそらくそうだろう
no
いいえ
Why? Because it shines at 360, 350, can't see
どうして? 360、350で光って見えないから
OK, you can't see, basically
OK、基本的には見えません
good
良い
I'm doing a show now
私は今ショーをやっています
I haven't moved this can, don't say I cheated, I'll take a look
この缶は動かしてない、騙したとは言わないで、見てみるよ
what is this ? beer
これは何ですか? ビール
I put this can here
この缶をここに置きます
i open the beer
私はビールを開けます
Can't drink, can't open, can't open
飲めない、開けられない、開けられない
hold on , ok , look on
ちょっと待って、わかった、見てください
I didn't paint it
塗らなかったんだ
ok ok ok enough , enough of the booze
わかった、わかった、もう十分、酒はもう十分
it should be soon, ok
これはすぐにできるはずです、わかりました
Because of chemistry, this saves unlimited Diffusion Control
化学のおかげで、これにより拡散制御が無制限に節約されます
It's all coming soon, look
すべてはもうすぐ始まります、見てください
fast enough, ok
十分早いです、わかりました
Question 16, 16M, whatever you do
質問 16、16M、何をしても
You said that when you pass the place where the tide is drunk, you will be killed
潮に飲まれた場所を通ると殺されるって言ってたね
Detecting alcohol trucks, it's impossible
酒類トラックの発見は不可能だ
So this is free, OK
これは無料です、OK
and it breaks so it doesn't work
そして壊れて動かなくなる
but it can
でもそれはできます
no problem at all
全く問題なし
A lot of fun
とても楽しいこと
Okay, more exciting next time, let's take a look
さて、次回はもっと面白いので、見てみましょう
So the single thing is
それで、ただ一つのことは、
If you use this structure
この構造を使えば
What about the water?
水はどうですか？
just arco
ただのアルコ
water
水
As soon as we look like water, we'll be fine.
水のように見えたらすぐに大丈夫です。
water is not good
水は良くない
glow of water
水の輝き
This absorbing light is right here
吸い込む光がここにある
without this pack
このパックがなければ
This package is only available in arco
このパッケージはarcoでのみ入手可能です
why not water
なぜ水をかけないのか
I'll tell you one thing why not
一つだけ教えてあげる、なぜそうしないのか
in the water
水中で
no matter what
何があっても
Because of acidity and alkalinity
酸性とアルカリ性があるので
Everyone knows this NH
誰もが知っているこのNH
blood flow know
血流がわかる
The NH of this steak in this NH is not sour
このNHのこのステーキのNHは酸っぱくない
OK
OK
so how to say
それでどう言うか
butyric acid
酪酸
When the H drops and changes to this side
Hが下がってこちら側に変わるとき
what this becomes
これはどうなるのか
Weak acid is strong
弱酸は強い
so im sorry
ごめんなさい
When I was waiting for the first phase of PH
PHの第一期を待っていたとき
It Protonate Immediately
すぐにプロトン化します
so it doesn't shine
だから光らない
there is nothing you can do
あなたにできることは何もありません
what can you turn it into
それを何に変えることができますか
turn it into
それをに変える
This place makes it a bit more acidic
この場所は少し酸性になります
Its resistance is always weakened
耐性は常に弱まっている
it's possible in the water
水中でも可能です
Look, I just thought of this concept, right?
ほら、このコンセプトを今思いついたんですよね？
Chemistry is just like that, right?
化学ってそういうものですよね？
So how do you turn it into a stronger acid
では、どうすれば強い酸に変えることができるのでしょうか？
not easy
簡単ではありません
You can do whatever you want, as long as Mr. Lin comes over and say
リンさんが来てこう言う限り、何をしてもいいよ
At that time you just didn't design
そのときあなたはただデザインをしていなかっただけです
It's simple, just pull the electron
簡単です、電子を引っ張るだけです
It is more acidic to design a pull electron
プル電子を設計する方が酸性が高い
Let's design a pull electron
プル電子を設計してみよう
It will be more acidic for the design to pull electrons
電子を引き寄せるデザインとしてはより酸性になります
Sour its conjugate and it will become dissolved
その結合体を酸っぱくすると溶けてしまいます
it will not be protonin
プロトニンではないでしょう
Is the answer like this?
答えはこんな感じでしょうか？
The answer is really like this
答えは本当にこんな感じです
OK this is totally OK to sell the concept
OK、これはコンセプトを販売するのにまったく問題ありません
So what was published at that time
それで、その時に出版されたのは
two pages per page
1 ページあたり 2 ページ
Anyway, it’s OK to sell concepts
とにかくコンセプトを売るのはOKです
Just look at it and add a CA.
それを見て CA を追加してください。
It was only this
これだけだった
this is what
これは何
it's this one that shines like this
こうやって光るのよ
such a simple thing
そんな単純なこと
OK, I won't talk about this
わかった、これについては話さない
It's okay for you to sleep when you talk about this
この話をしたら寝ても大丈夫です
just tell you if it will be like this
こうなるかどうかだけ教えてください
OK basically
基本的にOK
How about this project?
このプロジェクトはどうでしょうか？
Since I came to National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学に来てから
Wang Yifu gave a speech just now. I went there in 2001
たった今、王逸夫氏が講演しました。私は2001年にそこに行きました
OK to go basically
基本的にはOKです
What about since 2002?
2002年以降はどうでしょうか？
because
なぜなら
all the materials
すべての材料
OK so the answer is
OK、答えは次のとおりです
From 2002 to 2008
2002 年から 2008 年まで
I'm out of my research focus
研究の焦点から外れました
What about adding
追加するのはどうでしょうか
what indole group
インドールグループは何ですか
I will stop
やめます
I'll switch lanes
車線変更します
OK actually I posted on TV Shine
OK、実際に私は TV Shine に投稿しました
With the new generation of solar cells
新世代の太陽電池で
Paypal is too much
ペイパルは多すぎる
OK basically I won't talk today
はい、基本的に今日は話しません
OK basically speaking
基本的に言えばOK
i think some people know ok
大丈夫だと知っている人もいると思います
So the answer is to switch the direction
したがって、答えは方向を変えることです
But I will not talk about this direction today
しかし、今日はこの方向性については話しません
what am i going to say
私は何を言うつもりですか
OK because after 2009
OK、2009 年以降だから
I restarted this
これを再開しました
why start this thing
なぜこのことを始めるのか
Because
なぜなら
What about 2009?
2009年はどうでしょうか？
I set up a program called
というプログラムをセットアップしました
poster-glanding team
ポスターグランディングチーム
Wow this sounds very
うわー、とてもそう聞こえます
It seems that men's things are OK
メンズ物もOKなようです
It's the social affairs team
社会部チームです
OK, is it not me?
わかりました、私ではないですか？
But the members of the social affairs line group said
しかし、社会問題ライングループのメンバーはこう言った。
two female teachers
二人の女性教師
OK so full of embarrassment
わかりました、恥ずかしくていっぱいです
basically
基本上
Then why is it called the Social Affairs Line Group?
ではなぜ社会LINEグループと呼ばれているのでしょうか？
Because we are studying the social affairs line
社会系の勉強をしているので
of this
これの
It is poster-glanding
ポスターグランディングです
Just poster-glanding this
これをポスターに宣伝するだけです
The mechanism of this synthesis
この合成のメカニズム
OK, let me give you a few examples.
OK、いくつか例を挙げてみましょう。
let's see
どれどれ
This is the so-called poster-glanding
いわゆるポスターグランディングです
This is it
これだよ
How did PGH2 come about?
PGH2はどのようにして生まれたのですか？
from fatty acids
脂肪酸から
OK after Cyclooxygenase
シクロオキシゲナーゼ後はOK
After OK and Poxidase
OKとポキシダーゼの後
It's over here by Poxidase
ポキシダーゼによってここにある
then after
後で
only two two
たった２つ２つだけ
One is Pgis which is antithrombin
1つはアンチトロンビンであるPgisです。
OK one is Somboxxan Sinceres
OK 1 つはソンボクサン シンシアスです
thrombin
トロンビン
These two are checks and balances
この2つは抑制と均衡です
checks and balances
抑制と均衡
I give an example
例を挙げます
for example
例えば
You are hurt
あなたは傷ついています
There are a bunch of these in the platelets
血小板にはこれらがたくさんあります
thrombin
トロンビン
why
なぜ
because it will be what
それは何になるから
Immediately blown into blood acid
すぐに血液酸に吹き込まれます
what makes you condense
何があなたを凝縮させるのか
OK if you have a heart block
ハートブロックがあってもOK
or why
あるいはなぜ
you need to pass
合格する必要があります
OK is antithrombin
OK、アンチトロンビンです
To this side, it becomes the front row ring number
こちら側は最前列リングナンバーとなります
then let you what
それなら何をさせてください
let you this place is accessible
この場所にアクセスできるようにしましょう
So these two are checks and balances
つまり、これら 2 つは抑制と均衡です
over here
ここに
in fact to be honest
実際、正直に言うと
Even X-ray knows
X線でもわかる
OK this
はい、これ
the antithrombin
アンチトロンビン
Its structure is known
その構造は知られている
I don't know this place
ここは分かりません
why don't you know
なぜ知らないのですか
Because of its large active center
活動中心が大きいため
So I can't get my body out
だから体が出せない
I know that felt from National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学で感じたことはわかります
what felt
何を感じたか
Where is felt
どこに感じられるか
OK I've been trying to get it but I can't
OK、取得しようとしましたが、取得できません
OK basically
基本的にOK
so this place is
だからこの場所は
it has its
それはそれを持っています
its place as
としてのその場所
we are researching this place
私たちはこの場所を調査しています
After all because it all belongs to Satocon P450
だって全部サトコンP450のものだから
There is HIM and that straight
彼がいて、そのストレートが
so straight up
とてもまっすぐに
We can use Lyman spectroscopy to study that
ライマン分光法を使用してそれを研究できます
How did it change after it entered?
入ってからどう変わりましたか？
we will study this
私たちはこれを勉強します
That's because it's related to Poscagetin
それはポスカゲチンと関係があるからです
related to color wireless
カラーワイヤレス関連
Let's ask the color wireless team
カラーワイヤレスチームに聞いてみましょう
you know
ほら
What do you want to relieve the pain?
痛みを和らげたいものは何ですか？
Everyone use the rainy forehead below to relieve the pain
みなさんも下の雨の額で痛みを和らげてください
Everyone knows the best pain reliever
誰もが最高の鎮痛剤を知っています
If you go to the hospital and say I'm dying of pain
病院に行って痛みで死にそうだと言われたら
I'll tell you about the hospital
病院についてお話します
If the doctor said you could die
医者が死ぬかもしれないと言ったら
Just give you cox
コックスを与えてください
Inhibitor for you cox
あなたのためのインヒビターコックス
block this place
この場所をブロックしてください
Make sure you don't have any pain
痛みがないか確認してください
you take one without pain
痛みを感じずに服用できます
Basically this is the most upstream
基本的にはこれが最上流です
so you see that you say cox
コックスと言っているのがわかりますか
like every time i go to say give me a cox inhibitor
コックス阻害剤をくれと言うたびにそうだ
After this time, I guarantee you will have no pain at all
この時間が経過すると、痛みはまったくなくなることを保証します
basically
基本的
Then why is there no pain? It’s not good anymore
じゃあなんで痛くないの?もうダメだよ
Because of your natural disaster or something
自然災害か何かのせいで
You don't even know what your body is doing
自分の体が何をしているのかさえ分からない
let me tell you first we have this
最初に言っておきますが、これがあります
you say this to me
あなたは私にこう言います
Because what did I have to do with it just now?
だって、今それと何の関係があったの？
has a lot to do with
とたくさんの関係があります
OK, let's study these two
はい、この 2 つを勉強しましょう
OK it all belongs to P
OK、すべてはPのものです
That Satocon P450's
そのサトコンP450
Just have a Sorayband
Sorayband を持っているだけです
Because it has Porphine
ポルフィンが入っているので
straight this place
まっすぐこの場所
In fact, we have studied a lot of Raman
実際、私たちはラマンについて多くの研究を行ってきました。
I won't talk about it, I won't talk about it
それについては話さない、それについては話さない
Let me tell you about the Raman spectrum
ラマンスペクトルについてお話します
When this sub-save comes in
このサブセーブが入ってくると
OK its spectrum changes
OK、スペクトルが変化します
changes over time
時間の経過とともに変化する
OK let's study it
よし、勉強してみよう
its Lyman spectrum
ライマンスペクトル
just these things
これらのことだけ
OK then this is not important
OK、それならこれは重要ではありません
the most important thing is
最も重要なことは
when we study this
私たちがこれを勉強するとき
When Somboxan Synthesis
ソンボクサン合成時
OK we just found out one thing
OK、一つだけわかったことがある
A lot of fun
とても楽しいこと
It has a total of five Trip Open
合計 5 つのトリップ オープンがあります
There are always five Trip Opens in it
そこには常に 5 つの Trip Open が含まれます
What about these five Trip Opens?
これら 5 つのトリップ オープンについてはどうでしょうか?
Just five tryptophan five tryptophan
たった 5 つのトリプトファン 5 つのトリプトファン
What about the five cromotropins?
5 つのクロモトロピンについてはどうですか?
Basically it's 1 2
基本的には 1 2 です
W means Trip Open OK
W はトリップオープン OK を意味します
This student's pictorial text is clearer than me OK
この生徒の絵文字は私より鮮明です OK
1 2 3 4 5
１ ２ ３ ４ ５
These five Trip Open
この5つのトリップオープン
What about these five Trip Opens?
これら 5 つのトリップ オープンについてはどうでしょうか?
One thing that can obviously be said is
一つ明らかに言えることは、
When we use these just this
これらを使うとこれだけ
What is Laman Spectrum doing?
ラマンスペクトルは何をしているのですか?
we already know that
私たちはそれをすでに知っています
Actually, what about the four blue places?
実際のところ、青い 4 つの場所はどうでしょうか。
is very polar
非常に極性が高い
This place is practically almost non-polar
この場所は事実上ほぼ無極地です
We know it has almost no polarity
極性がほとんどないことがわかっています
OK
OK
We use various spectra
さまざまなスペクトルを使用します
We all know this has no polarity
これには極性がないことは誰もが知っています
but we don't know
でも私たちには分かりません
What is the reason for this lack of polarity?
この極性の欠如の理由は何でしょうか?
because there is no water or nothing
水も何もないから
no X-ray
X線なし
X-ray is useless
X線は役に立たない
X-ray to see water
X線で水を確認する
Teacher Wang knows that looking at the water is useless
王先生は水を見ても無駄だということを知っています
OK so everyone one thing is
OK、それでは皆さん、一つだけ
We know this W65 is here
この W65 がここにあることはわかっています
Then, when Postakening came in like this
で、こんな感じでPosttakeningが入ってきたら
When PGH2 came in like this
PGH2がこうなったとき
actually it's still passing here
実はまだここを通過中
That's a fatty acid
それは脂肪酸です
So it must be very Lumpol
とてもルンポルらしいですね
There should be no water in this place
この場所には水がないはずです
it has a way to survive
それには生き残る方法がある
Then of course the other four
もちろん残りの4人も
we think there is water
私たちは水があると思う
Excuse me
すみません
How do you know if there is water or not?
水があるかどうかはどうやってわかりますか?
This is the question everyone is asking
これは誰もが抱いている質問です
OK, where is the water in Portain?
オーケー、ポルテインの水はどこにある？
where is there no water
どこに水がないのですか
one thing I didn't know
私が知らなかったことが1つあります
So I just do this challenge saying
だから私はこのチャレンジをこう言うだけです
I'm going to challenge these things
こういったことに挑戦してみます
how do i challenge
どうやって挑戦すればいいですか
let's look good
見栄えを良くしましょう
We said there is no way to propane this water
私たちは、この水をプロパンガス化する方法はないと言いました
This surrounding of water is in Trotopen
この水の周りはトロトペンにあります
we thought of it
私たちはそれを考えました
Isn't Trotopen like this?
トロトペンってこんな感じじゃないですか？
right
右
if i am here
私がここにいるなら
no matter where
どこでも
Change to x4, otherwise how to change
x4 に変更します。それ以外の場合の変更方法
Is there a way this place can Sensing water
この場所で水を感知する方法はありますか
If possible, its socket is almost the same as it
可能であれば、そのソケットはそれとほぼ同じです
Can I use Protin's Expression
Protin の Expression を使用できますか
For example, feed Ecolite as nutrients
例えばエコライトを栄養剤として与える
Can it become an Unnatural Protin after eating it?
食べるとアンナチュラルプロチンになるのでしょうか？
OK, is there a possibility? Mutant's Protin
OK、可能性はありますか? ミュータントのタンパク質
Is it possible? I'll fix this first.
可能ですか?まずこれを修正します。
is there anything
何かありますか
That’s why I didn’t talk about it just now, just pull the electrons here, right?
だから今は話さなくて、ここで電子を引っ張っていけばいいだけですよね？
Just pull the electrons here.
ここに電子を引き寄せるだけです。
Sorry, it's on the mountain
ごめんなさい、山の上です
It just happened that your Amino-S needs to be synthesized in this place
たまたま、アミノ S をこの場所で合成する必要があるだけです
so no way no way
だからダメダメダメ
then you can make it through
そうすれば乗り越えられるよ
We want the good, halloween says, from the bad, where to add acid
我々は悪いものよりも良いものを求めている、ハロウィーンは言う、どこに酸を加えるべきか
Yes, change Time to N here
はい、ここで時間を「N」に変更します
Yes, if you change Time to N
はい、時間を N に変更すると、
this place must be sour
ここは酸っぱいに違いない
We were the first to think it must be sour
酸っぱいに違いないと最初に思ったのは私たちだった
so is it possible to come from here to this place
それで、ここからこの場所に来ることは可能ですか？
Sorry, this was two and a half years ago
すみません、2年半前の話です
Just tell Vice President Wang
王副総統に伝えてください
I will talk to Chen Ping or the concept
チェン・ピンとコンセプトについて話します
Chen Ping said you Kiss this can't be synthesized
チェン・ピンは、あなたにキスしてください、これは合成できないと言った
acid
酸
I rushed in and said that there is no way to combine them, and I will show you.
私は慌てて、それらを組み合わせる方法はない、教えてあげる、と言いました。
basically
基本的
So the answer is that I organize a team
答えは、私がチームを組織するということです
just start looking
ただ探し始めてください
According to two or three months later, it is possible
2～3ヶ月後によると可能性はあります
so we just let it go
だから私たちはそれを手放すだけです
You see we still made it
ほら、私たちはまだやり遂げたわ
Let me make one, two, three, four, and five
1、2、3、4、5 を作らせてください
basically i'm peak camp
基本的に私はピークキャンプです
So this is related to organic physicochemical analysis
これは有機物理化学分析に関連しています
What volume has what peak relationship
どのボリュームにどのようなピーク関係があるか
Just do it, basically
基本的にはやるだけです
So the answer can be made
それで答えは出せる
And we can also make is only l seam
L縫いのみのお作りも可能です
no problem at all
全く問題なし
basically speaking
基本的に言えば
so made it
それでできました
The answer is can it?
答えは「できるでしょうか？」
The answer is that it is really possible after it is illuminated
答えは、点灯後は本当に可能です。
Does water have a wave circle or something?
水には波動サークルか何かがあるのでしょうか？
The answer is that one thing is really done for me.
答えは、あることが私のために本当に行われたということです。
Basically, you can see that the spectrum we made looks like this
基本的に、作成したスペクトルは次のようになっていることがわかります
I'll tell you, it's very simple
言っておきますが、とても簡単です
The result we made is
私たちが作った結果は、
n1 has the possibility of H n2 has the possibility of H
n1 は H の可能性があります n2 は H の可能性があります
It doesn't matter, this protein 98
関係ないよ、このプロテイン98
This protein 2 will turn green after G8
このプロテイン 2 は G8 以降に緑色に変わります
there are these two these two are this
この 2 つがあります、この 2 つはこれです
This is my non-protein transfer
これは私の非タンパク質転送です
Shine with protein transfer
プロテイン転写で輝きを放つ
this is n2
これはn2です
so all three have
だから3人全員が持っています
Then you say teacher, how do you know which one?
それからあなたは、先生、どっちがどっちかどうやってわかるの？と言いました。
We will synthesize n7A3 in 2
n7A3を2で合成してみます
n7A3 in 1's
n7A3 を 1 で表す
We can then compare the spectra
スペクトルを比較できます
the answer is right
答えは正しいです
so we know that
だから私たちはそれを知っています
it can really be water
それは本当に水かもしれない
That is, you can go to probe water
つまり、プローブ水に行くことができます
right in the water
まさに水の中
in the water
水中で
So it's really possible to probe
だから実際に調査することは可能だ
Then of course we will take this
それならもちろんこれを受け取ります
就wake it equalize
起きてイコライズする
OK of course it is
もちろんそうですよ
The answer to one thing is
一つのことに対する答えは、
Because we are using expression
表現を使っているので、
Do this and you will know
こうすればわかるよ
So we have five words
単語は 5 つあります
terribly sorry
大変申し訳ありません
if we are single
私たちが独身なら
what about the other four
他の4人はどうですか
we because we don't
私たちはそうしないから
know from making protein
プロテインを作ることからわかる
We're not doing that Peter Schuess way
私たちはピーター・シュースのやり方ではありません
But we're doing Peter Schuess now
でも今はピーター・シュースをやっているんだ
we use that called
私たちはそれを使用します
that that that that that
それはそれはそれは
The way of that amber coden
その琥珀のコーデンの行方
OK we used to be the easiest
OK、昔は一番簡単だった
If there is only one to become a trip
旅になるのがひとつだけなら
For the other four, change it to
残りの 4 つについては、次のように変更します。
So the double ball will change a bit, but the activity will not change much
ダブルボールは少し変わりますが、アクティビティはあまり変わりません
So we do it this way, you see we just replace every
このようにして、すべてを置き換えるだけです。
replace each one, crystal energy thing happened
それぞれを交換すると、クリスタルエネルギーのことが起こりました
When we replaced him, we found out that you see this in the water
私たちが彼を置き換えたとき、あなたは水の中でこれを見ていることがわかりました
Three, but in Porting there are two
3 つですが、Porting では 2 つあります
N2 is missing, why? Because the water inside is not Bock water
N2が抜けているのはなぜですか? 中の水がボック水ではないからです
So this N2 is gone, that is, Equilibrium is gone
つまり、この N2 はなくなりました。つまり、平衡状態はなくなりました。
If you don't see it, there are two. It doesn't matter if there are two, there must be water.
見えないなら二つある、二つあっても問題ない、水があるはずだ。
There must be water, this catalysis, but the place of W65
水、この触媒作用があるはずですが、W65の場所
If W65 is replaced by ours, no, 0
W65 を当社の製品に置き換えると、いいえ、0
just no water, really no water
ただ水がない、本当に水がない
So using this place, I can probe and say, oh! This porting is in this part of W65
この場所を使用すると、「ああ! この移植は W65 のこの部分にあります」と調べることができます。
This Si'an acid has no water, and the others have water, OK
このシアン酸には水がありませんが、他の酸には水があります、OK
I won’t tell you about other things, other places have water, OK
他のことは言わないよ、他の場所には水があるよ、OK
Then you say, hey! Then how accurate is this? It’s very simple, you see! After I put Dinatio
それからあなたはこう言います、おい! では、これはどのくらい正確ですか? とても簡単です、ほら、Dinatio を入れた後
After taking this SomboxinDinatio, it's back to three roots
このソンボシンディナティオを摂取すると、3つのルーツに戻ります
Dinatio catches all the water, he's coming back
ディナティオはすべての水をキャッチします、彼は戻ってきます
So of course it's incredible
だからもちろん信じられないほど素晴らしいよ
Which means I can really go pub water with this
つまり、これで本当にパブウォーターに行けるということです
So I throw this out
だから私はこれを捨てます
Actually sorry we lost it to Nature
本当に残念ですが、自然に負けてしまいました
Nature saved eight months
自然が8か月を救った
tell us you want
欲しいと言ってください
At least three or four examples
少なくとも 3 つまたは 4 つの例
For each example, we have to do it for at least half a year to a year
それぞれの例について、少なくとも半年から1年はかかる
Three or four need to be done for two years
2年かけて3つか4つやる必要がある
no time to wait
待つ時間がない
basically
基本的
we say we don't have time to wait
私たちは待つ時間がないと言います
he said no time to wait
彼は待つ時間がないと言った
We will recommend you to Nature Communication
Nature Communicationをオススメします
So publish Nature Communication
そこでNature Communicationを出版する
Basically they are very
基本的に彼らはとても
very surprise
非常的surprise
Say oh, you can pub
ああ、パブしてもいいよ
water in pub protein
パブプロテインの水
Let's continue to look down
これからも下を向いていきましょう
So the catastrophe temperature is in this place
破滅的な温度がここにあるということ
1. Where does protein water exist?
1. プロテインウォーターはどこにありますか?
What is its structure near the active site
活性部位付近ではどのような構造になっているのか
It's interesting
それは面白い
Whether these water molecules form a clear mass
この水分子が透明な塊を形成しているかどうか
The specificity of the structure and the resulting dynamics
構造の特異性とその結果として生じるダイナミクス
Are structural changes related to protein activity?
構造変化はタンパク質の活性に関連していますか?
How to perform hydration reaction during protein finishing?
プロテイン仕上げ時に水和反応を行うにはどうすればよいですか？
This is one of the things we are most interested in
これは私たちが最も興味を持っていることの 1 つです
Basically written in both Chinese and English
基本的に中国語と英語で書かれています
Change it to Chinese this morning
今朝は中国語に変更します
Tired OK let's see
疲れた、わかりました、見てみましょう
So in biochemical reproduction
つまり生化学的生殖においては
So basically this is why everyone can't figure it out
基本的にこれが誰もが理解できない理由です
The reason is that so far
理由は、これまでのところ、
no direct
直接はありません
carbon increase in biochemical moisture content
炭素の生化学的水分含量の増加
Analysis of protein water by X-ray is static
X線によるタンパク質水の分析は静的です
OK water quality position is the result of optimization
OK水質位置は最適化の結果です
everybody knows
誰もが知っている
basically impossible
基本的に無理
but we can really go
でも本当に行けるよ
Well this year and a half
さて、今年１年半
One and a half years since publication
出版から1年半
We've actually found two examples
実際に 2 つの例が見つかりました
OK let's give an example
OK、例を挙げてみましょう
This is a very simple
これはとてもシンプルです
just one
一つだけ
this
これ
Rhypo Nucrease
Rhypo ヌクレアーゼ
OK cuts the RNA
OKでRNAをカット
It only has a Triple Fent
トリプルフェントしかない
As far as the location of W59
W59の場所に関しては
OK, what about this one?
さて、これはどうでしょうか？
when we go to prop it
それを支えに行くとき
We also use Protin's Expression
Protin の Expression も使用します
It's better to change one
一つ変えたほうがいいよ
One I don't do anything OK
1つは何もしなくてもOK
you know we won't talk
私たちが話さないのはわかってるでしょう
tell you the result
結果を教えてください
I'll tell you the result
結果を教えます
We really prop it dynamic
私たちはそれをダイナミックに支えます
when it does have water
水があるとき
Do Equilibrium when there is no water
水のないところで平衡を保つ
This is something no one has ever seen
これは誰も見たことのないものです
OK we see it Equilibrium
OK、わかりました 均衡
What do you say
あなたは何を言っていますか
You said that your spectral solution looks like this
スペクトル ソリューションは次のようになると言いました
Excuse me, do you really have
すみません、本当に持っていますか？
have
もつ
According to us, teacher Yang Xiaoqing from the Fuda University
私たちによると、復大大学のヤン・シャオチン先生は、
he does a test
彼はテストをします
OK let's see this is his Wipe of Neucrase
OK、これが彼のワイプ・オブ・ニュークレースであることを見てみましょう
I'm looking at these two loops
私はこれら 2 つのループを見ています
In fact it is very loose
実際はとても緩いです
You see every time he is doing evolution
彼が進化を遂げるたびにわかります
every time doing this
これをするたびに
he is very loose
彼はとてもルーズです
So of course water can run in like this all the time
もちろん水は常にこのように流れ込む可能性があります
After running in, basically talk
慣らし運転後は基本的に会話
In fact we are prop in this place
実際、私たちはこの場所の支柱です
OK so you can tell one thing is
OK、それで一つ言えるのは、
basically talk
基本的に話す
it slowly water will come out
ゆっくりと水が出てきます
OK so it will come out
よし、出てくるよ
so maybe one thing
だから多分一つのこと
it does have an in and an out
それはインとアウトを持っています
in one out one out
in 一個out 一個out
action that has been doing
行ってきた行動
OK basically
OK 基本上
This is an interesting example
これは興味深い例です
just tell everyone
ただみんなに言ってください
What about the second example?
2番目の例はどうでしょうか？
We've been doing something more interesting recently
最近、もっと面白いことをやっています
is doing this Aspirogenase
アスピロゲナーゼをやっている
So why is Aspirogenase so important
では、なぜアスピロゲナーゼがそれほど重要なのか
Everyone knows one thing is
誰もが知っている一つのことは、
This is treating it as medicine
これは薬として扱っています
OK it can cure cancer
大丈夫、ガンは治るよ
then why
それでなんで
Because tumor cells
腫瘍細胞だから
basically talk
基本的に話す
It is sensitization without Aspirogenase
アスピロゲナーゼを使わない感作
OK so that means
OK、ということは
If you wear Aspirogenase outside
アスピロゲナーゼを屋外で着用する場合
If you change aspargion into aspargionase
アスパルギオンをアスパルギオナーゼに変えると
you eat it and it's over
食べたら終わりです
Why? Because it doesn't turn it into
なぜ? それはそれを変えないからです
so it dies
それで死ぬ
If you just feed it aspargion it will live
アスパルギオンを与えれば生きます
OK, so if you use aspargionase
アスパルギオナーゼを使用する場合
After cutting this off, it's basically OK
これを切り取れば基本的にはOKです
Then this aspargionase has two states
このアスパルギオナーゼには 2 つの状態があります
One is called ANSAA type
1つはANSAAタイプと呼ばれるものです
One B is Type 1, Type 2
1 つの B はタイプ 1、タイプ 2
The activity of Type 2 is Type 1
タイプ 2 のアクティビティはタイプ 1 です
About 100 times more active
約100倍活性化
Let's talk about why we don't understand
なぜ理解できないのか話しましょう
only one
唯一
it only has one
それは1つだけです
This chiptopin 68 and chiptopin 66 are in this place
このチップトピン68とチップトピン66はこの場所にあります
So we said can we pop it?
それで、ポップしてもいいですか？
OK, let's replace it as well
よし、これも交換してみよう
OK, after doing mutation
OK、突然変異を行った後
We found an incredible thing
私たちは信じられないものを見つけました
Look, the first red line
ほら、最初の赤い線
The red line is soboxen
赤い線はソボクセンです
When there was water in that soboxen just now
さっきそのソボクセンに水が入っていたとき
Then come on
それならさあ
no water, this place is waterless
水がない、この場所は水がない
B type is without water
Bタイプは水なし
So 100 times more active is without water
つまり、水なしでは100倍活性化されます
What's more, this one has water
しかも、これには水が入っているんです
But what is it where there is water?
しかし、水があるところには何があるのでしょうか？
Only 1¾
わずか1¾
So we know this place has water or no water
つまり、この場所に水があるか水がないことがわかります
You do the equilibrium first
まず平衡をとります
I won't talk much
あまり話さないよ
All I can say is why this place
私に言えるのは、なぜこの場所なのかということだけ
why is this place ok
なぜここは大丈夫なのか
its activity is so high
その活性は非常に高いです
because it has no water
水がないから
no water and no
水も無いし
All water relay system words
水中継システムの全文言
it makes this place adjustable
この場所を調整できるようになります
It is very flexible
とても柔軟です
So this place is very active
だからこの場所はとても活気があります
For now, we interpret it like this
とりあえずこんな風に解釈してみます
we just finished this one
これを終えたところです
so everyone one thing
それでみんなに一つのこと
We think one thing is to say
私たちが言えることは 1 つだと思います
the water is half active in this place
この場所の水は半分活性です
very very important role
とてもとても重要な役割
There is no water in this place
この場所には水がない
Then let's go to x-ray
それではレントゲン検査に行きましょう
Because both of these have x-ray
どちらもレントゲンがあるので
unbelievable
不可思議
but i don't believe in x-ray
でも私はレントゲンを信じない
But there is no water in x-ray
しかし、X線には水は写っていない
this place has water
この場所には水があります
ok
Ok
How accurate is the x-ray
X線検査はどのくらい正確ですか
i don't know
わからない
can only talk
話すことしかできない
the result we made
私たちが作った結果
we go to x-ray
私たちはX線検査に行きます
really like this
本当にこれが好き
This place really has no water
この場所は本当に水がない
there is water in this area
この地域には水があります
ok basically
基本的にはわかりました
So we know one thing is
それで、私たちが知っていることは 1 つあります。
where it differs is
どこが違うのかというと
there is really no water
本当に水がない
Make another equilibrium
別の平衡を作る
ok basically
ok 基本上
then we have sent this to pns
それから私たちはこれをpnsに送信しました
At least it's starting to save
少なくとも節約は始まっている
ok basically
基本的にはわかりました
just tell you
ただ教えてください
water in this place
この場所に水
play a very, very important role
とてもとても重要な役割を果たす
ok
Ok
Then you say in this place
それからあなたはこの場所でこう言います
what else can we do
他に何ができるでしょうか
Let me give you the simplest example, okay?
最も単純な例をあげましょう。
let's watch this
これを見ましょう
this so-called
これはいわゆる
In time microbial
やがて微生物
Peptide
ペプチド
One is melittin
一つはメリチン
Shaking
揺れる
There is only one Tripdopene in Milatine
ミラティーンにはトリップドペンが 1 つだけあります
at this place
この場所で
should be all
すべてであるべきです
The 26 Amino Acid
26種類のアミノ酸
There is a Tripdopene in the middle
真ん中にトリップドペンがあります
OK
OK
i can replace it
交換できます
why change
なぜ変わるのか
because it is a thorn
それは棘だから
it destroys the cell membrane
細胞膜を破壊します
But it cuts on the cell membrane
でも細胞膜を切ってしまう
it cuts on the cell membrane
細胞膜を切ってしまうのです
then it breaks a hole
それから穴が開く
It dies after a hole is made
穴が開いたら死んでしまう
OK, this shot kills basically
OK、このショットは基本的に殺します
If it is Indolissidine
インドリシジンなら
this is melittin
これはメリチンです
This is Indolissidine
これはインドリシジンです
Indolissidine was two years ago
インドリシジンは2年前
just what
いったい何
Just unblocked
ブロックを解除したばかり
It is the most useful treatment for Hong Kong feet
香港の足に最も効果的な治療法です
You see, Hong Kong foot was very difficult to treat before, right?
ほら、香港の足は以前は治療が非常に困難でしたよね？
Now just put it on Indolissidine
あとはインドリシジンを塗るだけです
Just paint it on and it'll be fine
塗るだけで大​​丈夫ですよ
If you are unlucky, you can try
運が悪い場合は試してみてください
And those feet and gray paper
そしてその足と灰色の紙
What are you doing?
あなたは何をしている？
fuck you know so touch
クソ、わかってるから触って
or good luck
または幸運を祈ります
promise to be fine soon
すぐに元気になると約束する
In the past, it was impossible for any page to be good this year.
以前は、今年はどのページも良いものになることは不可能でした。
why don't you go back and try
戻って試してみてはどうでしょうか
I promise you this thing is OK
これは大丈夫だと約束します
So when a thing is
それで、何かが起こったとき、
It destroys the entire cell membrane
細胞膜全体を破壊します
Then the microbial dies
そうなると微生物は死んでしまいます
basically in this way
基本的にはこのように
then this is better
それならこれの方が良い
there is only one
1つだけあります
So we're going to nuke here
だからここを核攻撃するつもりだ
look we look at this thing
見てください、私たちはこれを見ています
look at this place
この場所を見てください
we are simple
私たちは単純です
Because as long as we cut to this place
この場所まで切り込む限りだから
This is Haizuo phobic
これは海図恐怖症です
no water
水がない
Look when there is no water
水がないことに注意してください
our place
我々の場所
Change it to our tritophan
トリトファンに変更してください
Changed to the words of tritophan, the suppression claw of our second district
我が第二地区の制圧爪トリトファンの言葉に変わった
Seven seconds after you look in
覗いてから7秒後
this place was supposed to be like this
この場所はこうなるはずだった
grow up like this
このように成長します
Why?
なぜ？
because there is no water
水がないので
This is with water and this is without water
こちらは水あり、こちらは水なし
i can grow up now
今なら成長できる
OK
OK
so in seven seconds it goes in
7秒後には入ります
Then we use a so-called
次に、いわゆる
cover yellow green tree
蓋黃綠樹
just a guts
ただの根性
Guts are when the outside meets the inside
ガッツとは外側と内側が出会うとき
it is different emission
それは異なる放出です
OK
OK
So one thing to be
それで、一つのことは
This seven seconds it cut up
この7秒が切れた
But it takes 45 seconds
ただし45秒かかります
this will break
これは壊れます
Come in after breaking
休憩してから入ってください
So it is also a beautiful starly
それはまた美しい星空です
just tell you
ただ教えてください
Its application is Eyeless Buddha Realm
その応用は無眼仏界です
OK
OK
This is just one of the examples
これはほんの一例です
just tell you one thing
一つだけ言ってください
Then we will challenge
それでは挑戦していきます
What is your challenge?
あなたの課題は何ですか?
i want to challenge this
これに挑戦したいです
OK
OK
but i talk about this stuff
でも私はこのことについて話します
Everyone eats this bottle
みんなこのボトルを食べる
Like how is it possible
どうやってそれが可能ですか？
I want to challenge the protein channel is
プロテインチャンネルに挑戦したいのは
acroprin
アクロプリン
ok acroprin recently in Science Nature
オーケー、アクロプリンが最近サイエンス・ネイチャーに掲載されました
Two days in a row
二日連続
ok, let me tell you that he released the X-ray
OK、彼がX線写真を公開したことを伝えましょう
That's seven water
それは7つの水です
Big Dipper Water
北斗七星水
Let's talk here
ここで話しましょう
we see it this way
私たちはそれをこのように見ています
After entering, the water
入った後は水
ok if we change it to a
これを に変更すればOKです
trip top
トリップトップ
Our artificial trip top
私たちの人工旅行トップ
how about
どうですか
but everyone eats themselves
でも誰もが自分自身を食べる
For example, please, this is membrane protein
たとえば、これは膜タンパク質です
How could you come out of Isox-ray
どうやって Isox-ray から抜け出すことができたのでしょうか
I thought
私は思った
I was scolded as a bloody sprinkler, right?
血のスプリンクラーと叱られましたね。
The result was scolded
結果は叱られた
in another month
再過一個月以後
People really released his Isox-ray
人々は本当に彼の ISOx-ray をリリースしました
ok so now he can put
OK、これで彼は入れます
trunk
トランク
ok put him out of isox-ray
OK、彼をisox-rayから外してください
So we've got this now
これができました
this protocol
このプロトコル
ok we are doing it now
わかりました、今やっています
But it's a super challenge
しかし、それは超挑戦です
because acroprin is too big
アクロプリンが大きすぎるので
ok basically speaking
基本的に言えばOK
OK, what about synthesis?
さて、合成についてはどうですか？
We've been working on this
私たちはこれに取り組んできました
ok all this
わかりました、これですべて
Synthesis of ok
的合成 ok
why
なぜ
Because we want to synthesize this
これを合成したいので
brighter
より明るい
ok more sensitive
よし、もっと敏感に
what
何
So we're developing this thing right now
それで私たちは今これを開発中です
ok i'm here
わかりました、私はここにいます
let you breathe
息をさせてください
ok stop
わかりました、やめてください
this change the gear
これでギアを変えます
what about ok gear
OKギアはどうですか
The above is more fun. Let me talk about the nano-resistant materials of these semiconductors.
上記の方が楽しいので、これらの半導体のナノ抵抗材料について話しましょう。
it's a lot of fun
とても楽しいです
so i'm talking about this place now
だから私は今この場所について話しています
This place is about me from 2002 to 2009
この場所は 2002 年から 2009 年までの私に関するものです
OK self-discipline is developing
OK、自制心が養われています
After 2009 I think
2009年以降だと思います
In fact, my eyesight is enough
実は視力は十分なんです
I think this should have been commercialized
これは商品化すべきだったと思う
OK, so after 2010, I actually didn’t publish much
そうですね、2010 年以降、私は実際にはあまり出版しませんでした
what have you been doing
いかがお過ごしでしたか？
Do some kind of mass production or something
大量生産とかなんとかしてやれよ
because I think it's supposed to be
そうあるべきだと思うから
It's time to start applying
いよいよ申し込み開始です
Let's see what's interesting about this place
この場所の何が面白いのか見てみましょう
The first one, of course, is quantum dots.
もちろん、最初のものは量子ドットです。
on the mine road
鉱山道で
That mine is basically talking
あの鉱山は基本的にまだ話している
When it comes to mining roads, it's actually very simple.
鉱山道路に関しては、実際には非常に単純です。
I'll just give you an example
例を挙げてみましょう
We say vulcanized
加硫加工と言います
or petrified
または石化した
or shaved septum
または剃られた中隔
OK these things please
OK、これらをお願いします
This NASA has been using since 50 years ago
NASAが50年前から使用している
What's so strange, it's made of solar panels or something
不思議なことに、それはソーラーパネルか何かでできています
It's something everyone knows, right?
それは誰もが知っていることですよね？
But have you ever seen these things glow?
でも、これらが光るのを見たことがありますか
Did you light it? Impossible
点火したの? ありえない
isn't it? does it shine when you shine it? it's metallic
そうですよね、照らすと光りますか?メタリックです
Just like the semi-conductive metal that Dürr's luster
ちょうどデュールの光沢のある半導電性金属のように
If you shine more light on it, it will become hotter
もっと光を当てるともっと熱くなります
So why is it like this? Why isn't it glowing?
では、なぜこのようになるのでしょうか?なぜ光らないのでしょうか?
A very simple thing, let me give you an example, which involves
非常に単純なことですが、例を挙げてみましょう。
The so-called machine problem is called excitement
いわゆる機械の問題を興奮と呼ぶ
As far as the machine is concerned, let me give you the simplest example
機械に関する限り、最も単純な例をあげましょう。
For example, optimistic, red and white as CDSE or CDS
たとえば、楽観的、赤と白は CDSE または CDS です。
It doesn't matter, that is, it has formed a CDSE
それは問題ではありません。つまり、CDSE が形成されています。
The fast material of semiconductor is good
半導体の速い材料が良い
As for the fast material, if I arouse
速いネタも起こせば
Once excited, an electron
電子は一旦励起されると、
Kick from this ground state to the kickstand
この接地状態からキックスタンドまでキックします。
There is a game in semiconductors, kick to the excitation stage
半導体に勝負あり、興奮のステージへ
As soon as you kick to the trigger table, here is the fast material
トリガーテーブルにキックするとすぐに、高速マテリアルがここにあります
So after an electron from below kicks up, it stays in a hole
つまり、下から電子が飛び出した後、穴の中にとどまります。
As for this hole, the electrons next to it will always go back... keep filling it.
この穴に関しては、隣の電子は常に戻っていきます...穴を埋め続けます。
So when the electrons are filling, it seems that the hole is moving
電子が満たされているとき、正孔が動いているように見える
Electronics are filling in, you can see that we are playing that crossball
エレクトロニクスが充実してきています、私たちがクロスボールをしているのがわかります
There's a hole here, you fill it in
ここに穴があるので埋めてください
It's not that you can't move
動けないわけではない
move
動動動
so it seems
そうらしい、それっぽい
In fact, the electron is going
実際、電子は進んでいます
But the reflection seems to be moving electric
でも反射は電気的に動いているように見える
As far as the defender's electric is going
ディフェンダーの電気が行く限り
there is a movement
動きがあります
You are basically empty above
基本的に上は空です
So this electron is free to move
つまり、この電子は自由に動きます
Right, so the electrons are also going
そうですね、電子も行きますね
So this electron is also going
それでこの電子も行きます
Electric is also running here
ここにも電気が通っています
OK when will it shine
はい、いつ光りますか
it's easy
それは簡単です
this is the electron
これは電子です
OK Liang Sanbo also pay attention
OK梁山泊も注目
It is this electron that touches this electric
この電気に触れているのはこの電子です
For position
ポジションについて
down it shines
下では光ります
can i ask one thing
一つ聞いてもいいですか
When an electron and an electric
電子と電気のとき
if you think of it as a boat
船に例えると
OK think of this place as the Pacific Ocean
OK、ここを太平洋だと考えてください
There is a boat in the Pacific
太平洋に船がある
sudden lightning strike
突然の落雷
just after the light
光の直後
lightning strike in half
半分に落雷
OK, what about the two halves?
さて、二つの半分はどうなるでしょうか？
words wandering in the pacific
太平洋をさまよう言葉
what is the chance of it overlapping
重なる可能性はどのくらいですか
0 impossible things
不可能なことは0
But if you take this Pacific Ocean
でもこの太平洋を取れば
Keep chopping and chopping into seven Lianpeng
切り刻み続けて7つの連鵬に切ります
even cut into smaller smaller smaller
小さく切っても小さく小さく
If you cut it down to such a small area
こんなに狭い範囲まで切り詰めると
Will this be a reunion?
これは再会になるでしょうか？
yes so it's that simple
はい、それはとても簡単です
So we cut this block all the way
そこでこのブロックを完全にカットしました
If the way of top down
トップダウンのやり方なら
What will I do with the e-bin?
電子便はどうするのですか？
just keep hacking
ただハッキングを続けるだけ
cut to small
小さく切る
as small as the two of them
二人と同じくらい小さい
also have mutual attraction
お互いに魅力もある
mutual attraction
相互引力
This is the so-called wave radius
これはいわゆる波の半径です
We call it the Bohr radius
それをボーア半径と呼びます
just write the hydrogen atom
水素原子を書くだけです
In terms of Bohr radius
ボーア半径に関して
just below this radius
この半径のすぐ下に
it also mutual
それは相互でもある
if you feel each other
お互いを感じたら
it can overlap
重なることもある
right
右
Then this varies with your material
これは素材によって異なります
I feel like something is in a long place
長い場所に何かがあると思う
You can also learn from each other
お互いから学ぶこともできます
There is PBS
PBSもあるよ
flow chemical fiber
フロー化学繊維
that is very long
それはとても長いです
it can still know
それはまだ知ることができる
basically
基本上
like CWG is ok
CWGは大丈夫みたい
Probably about 15 or 20 nm
たぶん15nmか20nmくらい
it also knows
それはまた知っています
so we chop it chop chop chop
だから私たちはそれをチョップチョップチョップ
Cut to 15 nm
15nmにカット
or around 10 nm
または約10nm
It has the opportunity to overlap the electron and the electric
電子と電気を重ねる機会がある
If it does not coincide with the previous
前回と一致しない場合は、
promising
有望な
Suppose there is an electric
電気があるとします
electronic
電子
Electrons go around like this
電子はこうやって飛び回る
that's not like anything
それは何にも似ていない
very much like
とても好きです
Aten isn't it? Electrons go around electrics
アテンですね 電気の周りを電子が回っています
Isn't it? OK
そうじゃないですか？
So all the formulas are the same
つまり、式はすべて同じです
That is, when the Size is larger
つまり、サイズが大きい場合
Its Gap is smaller
ギャップが小さくなります
The smaller the Size, the larger the Gap
サイズが小さいほど、ギャップは大きくなります
why? because it's the same
なぜ?同じだから
Have you ever learned Particle in a box
Particle in a box を学習したことがありますか
Just tell you about Particle in a box
Particle in a box について教えてください
When we leave the table now
今テーブルを離れるとき
The longer the distance, the smaller the Energy gap
距離が長ければ長いほど、エネルギーギャップは小さくなります
Is this the same?
これも同じですか？
When you cut bigger, its Energy gap gets smaller
大きく切るとエネルギーギャップが小さくなります
Therefore, the long wavelength and short wavelength of its light are related to its
したがって、その光の長波長と短波長は、その光の波長に関係します。
What about it? It has something to do with its radius
それはどうですか? それは半径と関係があります
OK like this
このままでOK
Then why does it shine?
ではなぜ光るのでしょうか？
The reason is that we cut it to
理由は、次のようにカットしたからです。
It also knows that it can find itself
それは自分自身を見つけることができることも知っています
OK it will shine
よし、光るよ
I use this simplest explanation
私はこの最も単純な説明を使用します
if you want to explain the words in your eyes
あなたの目に映る言葉を説明したいなら
It's okay if it takes two hours, everyone.
2時間くらいかかっても大丈夫ですよ、皆さん。
just in this way you know what to say
このようにして、あなたは何を言うべきかわかるでしょう
It shines because you cut it down to the Bohr radius
ボーア半径まで削ったから光る
OK, the Boer radius varies with the material
OK、ボーア半径は材料によって異なります
it just shines
それはただ輝くだけです
The size of the emitted light wavelength
発光波長の大きさ
OK the wavelength is shorter when you're younger
OK、若いほど波長は短くなる
The larger the OK, the longer the wavelength
OKが大きいほど波長が長くなります
with this method
この方法で
According to this you know one thing is
これによると、次のことがわかります。
how do you synthesize it
どうやって合成するのですか
OK
OK
I just cut it, right?
切ったばかりですよね？
You can also use this method called top down
トップダウンと呼ばれるこの方法を使用することもできます
you can use button up
ボタンアップを使用できます
chemical synthesis
化学合成
It's very simple to let each atom like this
各原子をこのようにするのは非常に簡単です
keep accumulating, accumulating, accumulating somewhere
蓄積し続けて、蓄積して、どこかに蓄積し続ける
stop
ストップ
how to stop
どうやって止めるか
How do you know its size?
そのサイズはどうやってわかりますか?
We all use wavelengths of light
私たちは皆、光の波長を使用しています
shine down
輝く
stop it stop it
やめてやめて
OK this way
OK、このまま
If you want to stop before, you will soon
前にやめたければすぐにやめられます
stop in seconds
数秒で停止します
not now
現在不要
wait till i get on with it
私がそれに取り組むまで待ってください
minutes now
今分
used to be like this
以前はこうでした
So of course ours is easy
もちろん私たちのものは簡単です
For example, if you want a CD
たとえば、CD が欲しい場合は、
I want to do CDSE
CDSEをやりたい
Whole body of your CD
CD の本体全体
Just use a complex
コンプレックスを利用するだけ
Let's call this Oligosacid oleic acid
これをオリゴ酸オレイン酸と呼びましょう
Just cut it into a complex like this
このように複合体にカットするだけです
Then, the abbreviation is to use a high temperature
次に、略語は高温を使用することです。
because we are in high temperature
私たちは高温になっているので
we want high temperature synthesis
高温合成が必要です
So use this Oxothexate at high temperature
したがって、このオキソテキサートを高温で使用してください
you are ok
大丈夫ですね
Then SE
それからSE
OK we also want to use complex
OK、complex も使用したいと思います
OK use this complex
OK、この複合体を使用してください
I often talk about TOP, TW is this thing
TOP、TWのことをよく話しますが、これはこれです
is forcefing
強制です
with this method
この方法で
so in this way
それでこのようにして
this is picasso, this is picasso two
これはピカソ、これはピカソ2
That is, the whole district is organized in this sauver
つまり、地区全体がこのソーバーで組織されています
Then what are these picasso these
では、これらのピカソは何ですか？
as its surfactant
その界面活性剤として
Why surfactant? It's simple
なぜ界面活性剤なのか? それは簡単です。
Do you want to use chemistry to grow
化学を使って成長してみませんか
What is the most stable?
最も安定しているものは何ですか?
fast material
速い材料
If you don't restrict it, it will definitely become fast material
制限しなければ絶対に速い素材になる
How do you limit it? It's simple
どうやって制限するのですか? それは簡単です
in a template
テンプレート内で
What is this template?
このテンプレートは何ですか?
Yes, surfactants can form enveloping
はい、界面活性剤は包みを形成する可能性があります
Use the bag as a template
バッグをテンプレートとして使用する
Let it grow this thing, it's that simple
これを成長させましょう、それはとても簡単です
You can go to probi for the bag
バッグはプロビに行ってください
like a long bag or a
長いバッグや
Generally, except that there are more bags
通常、バッグが増えることを除いて
What does a long bag grow into?
長いバッグは何に成長しますか？
grow into a wild or rod
野生または棒状に成長する
so you grow into a quantum dot
それであなたは量子ドットに成長します
let's take a look
見てみましょう
So in this way you know
このようにして、あなたは知っています
I'm trying to tell you this
私はこれをあなたに伝えようとしています
Then we probably use it like this for a long time
じゃあ、このまま長く使っていこうかな
put this with this
これとこれを入れて
Cut the two together and add to 300 degrees
2つを一緒に切り、300度に加算します
up to 300 degrees and basically
300度まで、基本的には
Of course, this is actually cooking to 300 degrees first
もちろん、これは実際には最初に300度まで調理します
cast this in
これをキャストして
cast in and what you get
キャストして得られるもの
get this next to
これを隣に置いてください
These are all interfacial agents that can be used as it
これらはすべて、そのまま使用できる界面剤です。
cut it down
それを切り取る
make it only spawn in a sphere or something
球体か何かの中にのみスポーンさせるようにする
Then stop where you see the light
そして光が見えるところで立ち止まってください
It only knows about the size
サイズしか分からない
For example, 5 nil only ones are about to shine
たとえば 5 nil だけが輝き出しそう
all in yellow
全部黄色で
Wait a minute and I'll show you
ちょっと待ってください、それでは見せます
so you know what to say
だから何を言えばいいかわかるでしょう
In fact, they are all grown in this way.
実際、彼らはすべてこのようにして成長しています。
This is the easiest way ok
これが一番簡単な方法ですよ
It's a pity that the light emitted by such growth is very weak
このような成長によって発せられる光が非常に弱いのは残念です
what is the reason
理由は何ですか
because you also know one thing
あなたも一つのことを知っているから
when you get smaller and smaller
あなたがどんどん小さくなったら
How about it
どうでしょうか
We call service to volume and it gets bigger and bigger
ボリュームに対してサービスを呼び出すと、それはますます大きくなります
What is service to volume
ボリューム・トゥ・ボリュームとは何ですか
This is the interface
これがインターフェースです
to process to volume
ボリュームに処理する
In fact, the interface is more and more
実際、インターフェースはますます進化しています。
You also know how to learn this
あなたもこれを学ぶ方法を知っています
Learn without ability
能力がなくても学ぶ
what is the interface
インターフェースは何ですか
are all flaws
すべて欠陥です
interface stuff
インターフェースのもの
All interfaces are dangling bombs
すべてのインターフェースはぶら下がっている爆弾です
Why
なぜ
because everything else is fine
他は大丈夫だから
Did you face the air?
空気と向き合ったのか？
Or face liquid is not connected
またはフェイスリキッドが接続されていません
So this place is full of flaws
だからこの場所は欠陥だらけだ
If the electron hits up or electric it
電子がぶつかったり、電気を帯びたりしたら
it will be trap
それは罠だろう
will be there now
今そこにいるでしょう
It doesn't shine, just change to this
光らない、これに変えるだけ
So it doesn't work that way.
したがって、そのようには機能しません。
If that doesn't work, what should I do?
それがうまくいかない場合はどうすればよいですか?
Of course, many people do just use
もちろん、ただ使っている人も多いですが、
The so-called call share method
いわゆるコールシェア方式
It's next to it. When it grows to this place, take it out.
隣にあります、ここまで伸びたら取り出します。
Then go in and grow another layer of ZNS
次に、ZNS の別の層を成長させます
The total ZN's precursor and s's precursor are one layer longer
ZN のプリカーサーと s のプリカーサーの合計は 1 層長くなります。
ok then like this
わかりました、それではこのように
If the side is more enclosed
側面がより密閉されている場合
There's no flaws in this place, shine
この場所には欠点はない、輝け
why doesn't it come here from the electron
なぜ電子から来ないのですか
because of what in this place
この場所に何があるから
The so-called varensband of this place
この場所のいわゆるヴァレンスバンド
跟conduction band
跟伝導帯
Just how to translate varensband
ヴァレンスバンドの翻訳方法
Electrical strap and conductive strap
電気ストラップと導電ストラップ
ok, this one is higher than it
わかりました、これはそれよりも高いです
So electrons won't go out Electric won't go out
だから電子は出てこない 電気は出ない
So it is now here
それで今ここにあります
it shines in this place
この場所で輝く
At this time, the light is very strong
この時、光がとても強いです
ok so use this way
わかりましたので、この方法を使用してください
what will you get
何をもらえますか
different size you see
見ると違うサイズ
This is
これは
Its radius is 1.7nm 1.9 2.2 2.6 3.0
その半径は 1.7nm 1.9 2.2 2.6 3.0
Just 30 N Shuang
ちょうど 30 N シュアン
Let’s see who it is, the wavelength of its light is getting longer and longer
誰だか見てみましょう、その光の波長はどんどん長くなっていきます
From more than 400 to more than 600
400以上から600以上へ
It is possible to get the Hongchen Huangli combustion battery
紅城黄利燃焼電池を入手可能
In total this is done in seconds
これは合計で数秒で完了します
This can be done in about two or three minutes
これは2、3分程度で完了します
Organic health
オーガニックの健康
If you want to make red dust Huang Li combustion battery
赤粉黄李燃焼電池を作りたい場合
you wait slowly
ゆっくり待ってください
You have to do different things, the light is so strong
違うことをしなければならない、光がとても強い
probably several years
おそらく数年
But it does it for you in three minutes
でも、それは 3 分で完了します
so you get what you want
それであなたは欲しいものを手に入れます
What's more, it's not over yet
さらに、まだ終わっていない
because it is a version without these molecules
これらの分子が無いバージョンなので
Only FORNONG Only the vibration of biomass
FORNONG だけ バイオマスの振動だけ
So its full width at half maximum when it is shining is very narrow.
そのため、光っている時の半値全幅は非常に狭いです。
so narrow
とても狭い
ok let's see
わかりました、見てみましょう
Of course I'll show you the sex first
もちろん先にセックスをお見せします
So when I was coming yesterday, I asked my students to say
それで、昨日私が来たとき、生徒たちにこう言いました。
Make a batch for me tonight
今夜私のためにバッチを作ってください
So he immediately put together a batch
それで彼はすぐにバッチを組み立てました
mentor this is it
メンター、これです
OK let's see how this goes
さて、これがどうなるか見てみましょう
I wrapped it in a plastic bag
ビニール袋に包みました
Because it's pretty poisonous
かなり毒があるので
Basically I don't want to take it out
基本的には外したくないんですが
ok let's see
わかりました、見てみましょう
I just take this light, it's beautiful
この光を撮るだけで、とても美しいです
did you see
あなたは見ましたか
Have you seen the red dust yellow green blue tissue paper?
赤い粉、黄緑、青のティッシュペーパーを見たことがありますか？
OK, it's really beautiful, that's all
OK、本当に美しい、それだけです
The student made it for me last night
昨夜生徒が私のために作ってくれました
look how fast you can make these things
どれだけ早くこれらのものを作れるか見てください
like this
このような
OK so you see it's shining every box occipital lobe
OK、後頭葉の隅々まで輝いているのがわかりますね
Probably above 0.7 0.6
おそらく 0.7 0.6 以上
definitely above
間違いなく上にあります
OK it's that strong
OK、それは強いです
OK so of course you know one thing
OK、もちろんあなたは一つのことを知っています
even blu-ray i'm now
ブルーレイでも私は今
I know people like Mr. Lin
私はリンさんのような人を知っています
They just make a bunch of blue ones
彼らは青いものをたくさん作るだけです
Molecule of what
何の分子
Look, it's Super Blue
ほら、スーパーブルーだよ
This super strong Blue's words
この超強いブルーの言葉
Quantaneers is definitely 1
Quantaneersは間違いなく1です
OK look how strong it is
OK、どれだけ強いかを見てください
I, you already see a little blue here
私、ここにはすでに少し青いのが見えます
OK this doesn't seem to be visible
OK、これは表示されないようです
No because of course because of being blocked
いいえ、もちろんブロックされているためです
This super strong blue light
この超強力なブルーライトは
this is basically
これは基本的にです
So of course one thing is to say
ですから、もちろん一つ言えることは、
you use this way you know what to say
あなたはこの方法を使います、あなたは何を言うべきか知っています
it can definitely be done
それは間違いなくできる
with this method
この方法で
But in this way there is a
しかし、このようにして、
There is only one shortcoming
欠点が1つだけあります
you said you made this
あなたはこれを作ったと言いました
What are you going to develop next?
次は何を開発するつもりですか？
I think just one is very simple is to put these two
非常に簡単なのは、これら 2 つを置くことだけだと思います
Cut it off and say to light it in this place
切って、この場所で点火してと言う
Then this is called TAP1
これをTAP1と呼びます
You can also change the different put this electron put it
この電子の配置を変更することもできます
Move out, look, let me move out for you to see
出て行って、ほら、あなたが見てわかるように出て行かせてください
you see i can also say
ほら、私も言うことができます
For a TAP2, these two are stepped
TAP2 の場合、これら 2 つは段階的です
stepwise you see after stimulating it
段階的に刺激した後に見えてくる
Electronics are here Electricity has come here
電子機器がここにある 電気がここにある
OK so e electric thus in this place
OK、だから電気だからこの場所に
it becomes short wavelength at 900
900度では短波長になります
900 NM
900NM
Look, it doesn't matter how you adjust it.
ほら、どのように調整しても問題ありません。
I can go all the way from here to blue
ここから青までずっと行けるよ
It is no problem to transfer to INFARATE
INFARATEへの乗り換えは問題ありません
OK let alone these things
OK、そんなことは言うまでもありません
because it has only the motion of procreation
それは生殖の運動だけを持っているからです
OK so it doesn't have what we call
OK、それは私たちが呼んでいるものではありません
Energy Gaprow
エネルギーギャップ
OK where are you shining
OK、あなたはどこで輝いていますか
You know when it's tuned right it can shine very brightly
正しく調整すると非常に明るく輝くことができます
I'll see it right away
すぐに見ます
But this place still doesn't work
しかし、この場所はまだ機能していません
you see it doesn't work like this why not
このままではうまくいかないのはわかりますか？
Because the electric on this outer layer
この外層には電気が流れているので、
OK is still flawed on the outside
OKはまだ外側に欠陥があります
So outside you can paint a TAP1
屋外ではTAP1をペイントできます
cut it down
それを切り取る
If these two use this to cut it down, it will be very strong
これを二人で斬り込めばかなり強いだろう
If you are unlucky, I will show you
運が悪いなら見せてあげるよ
You see, if there is only one layer of CDSE, the light shines
ほら、CDSE が 1 層しかない場合、光が輝きます。
Li Guang is here
李広がここにいます
shine here
ここで輝いてください
Let the light shine here when you are on the second floor
OK、ここ2階に光を当てましょう
It's already 900, but it's very weak
もう900だけどかなり弱い
I put two layers outside to patch up a layer of ZNS
ZNSの層をパッチするために外側に2つの層を置きます
After chopping it down, the light is so strong
切った後の光はとても強いです
This light energy has already reached almost 1 in one ear.
この光エネルギーはすでに片耳でほぼ1に達しています。
at 900
900で
Which one can you put in the organic health can reach 900
オーガニックヘルスにどれを入れると900に達しますか
It's light energy, one ear and one ear, it can't be type
それは光のエネルギーです、片耳と片耳、タイプすることはできません
It doesn't matter if the 900 can't see it, use night vision goggles
900が見えなくても大丈夫、暗視ゴーグルを使用してください
Night vision goggles for you
あなたのための暗視ゴーグル
We use night vision goggles and say it's too strong for the eyes
私たちは暗視ゴーグルを使用していますが、目には強すぎると言われています
OK From night vision goggles it should be super strong
OK 暗視ゴーグルからすると超強力になるはずです
Just 900 OK basically it's not a problem
900 OK 基本的には問題ありません
OK good
いいよ
Where is the biggest problem with this method
この方法の最大の問題点はどこですか
Why are you using Core Shield?
なぜコアシールドを使用しているのですか？
you have learned one thing
あなたは一つのことを学びました
Yes, if you have learned Welding and Solding today
はい、今日溶接とはんだ付けを学んだ場合は、
Welding and Soldering, right?
溶接とかはんだ付けとかですよね？
like that you want that for that line
その行にそれが欲しいように
When connecting the wires and connecting the soldering, right?
配線を接続するときとハンダ付けするときですよね？
if you use that
それを使えば
If you use Constant to answer with sweat, you can open it with one poke.
コンスタントを使って汗をかいて答えると一突きで開けられます。
It opens with one poke, this is called Solding
一突きで開く、これをソルディングといいます
Why because Crystal doesn't match
クリスタルが合わないから
Crystal Latest is its golden grid not Match
Crystal 最新はゴールデン グリッドで一致しません
Ok, if it’s the same Match, it’s called Wielding
OK、同じ試合の場合、それは Wielding と呼ばれます
We call it worthy of sweating, then it will be very tight
汗をかく価値があると私たちは言います、そしてそれは非常にきつくなります
these are the problems
これらが問題です
When you say I'll pack another one
もう一つ詰めるって言ったら
If you only wrap one, it will fall off after a while.
1つだけ巻くと、しばらくすると剥がれてしまいます。
Ok because it Crystal is Mismatch
クリスタルは不一致なのでOK
This is the problem, so the current practice is not to do this
これが問題なので、現在の慣例ではこれを行うことはできません
Ok, didn’t I just talk about CDS-11 and cut another ZNS
OK、CDS-11 について話して、別の ZNS をカットしただけではありませんでしたか
Ok don't do it now how do you do it now
分かった、今はやらないで今どうする？
I used to do this, but now I use alloys
以前はこれを使用していましたが、今は合金を使用しています
Alloy is just mixing it up, whatever it is, just mixing it up
合金はそれを混ぜるだけです、それが何であれ、ただ混ぜるだけです
Ok why ZNS
OK、なぜZNSなのか
Because we know that ZN CDS-11 will be faster Match
ZN CDS-11 の方が高速であることがわかっているためです。
Then ZN slowly came in Didget, so it will form a box outside
その後ZNがディジェットにゆっくりと入ってきたので外でボックスを形成します
Then it’s gradual, it’s like quartz and glass can’t be cut, right?
それから徐々に、石英やガラスが切れなくなるのと同じですよね？
you put a Gracier in
グレイシャーを入れましたね
Eleven on one side and glass on the other
片面に11個、もう片面にガラス
it can be connected together
一緒に接続することができます
In the same way, how about using this method?
同様に、こんな方法も使ってみてはいかがでしょうか？
It's much better than before
以前よりずっと良くなりました
Actually, I'm sorry I lied to you just now.
実は、さっき嘘をついてごめんなさい。
That's how it was done just now
たった今そのようになりました
then why do you do this
じゃあなぜこんなことをするのか
because what's the benefit
だって何のメリットがあるの
Because it has nothing to do with Size
サイズとか関係ないから
How much Zn is in it matters
どれだけの亜鉛が含まれているかが重要です
So at this time I can stretch it to 10 minutes
現時点では 10 分まで延長できます
to do it for a few seconds is great though
素晴らしいことですが、数秒だけやってください
But how do you stop for a few seconds
でも、どうやって数秒間止まるの？
Do mass production like this and you have problems
このように大量生産すると問題が発生します
This way you can make blue
こうすれば青も作れます
This powder I just showed you is a solution
先ほど紹介したこのパウダーが解決策です
OKpowder like this
OKこのようなパウダー
If you don't believe me you can see that we can
私の言うことが信じられないとしても、私たちにはできることがわかります
make this blue make green
これを青にして緑にする
Being popular won’t lie to you, right?
人気があるって嘘つかないよね？
It is made, you can see that the amount made is so large
作られました、作られた量がとても多いことがわかります
make it every time
毎回作る
about two grams
約2グラム
two grams of something
何か2グラム
Sorry, now a gram is 25,000 yuan
申し訳ありませんが、現在 1 グラム 25,000 元です
so still useful
まだ役に立ちます
Twenty-five thousand yuan is just my cost
2万5千元は私の費用だけです
If you want to go to frame light VG to sell
フレームライトVGに売りに行くなら
Two grams will cost you about 40,000 to 50,000.
2 グラムの価格は、控えめに見てもおそらく 40,000 ～ 50,000 ドルです。
The most conservative 40,000 to 50,000
最保守四五萬
Not only... I don't know how much
それだけではありません...どれくらいかわかりません
basically
基本上
Let's take a look
見てみましょう
So its light emission is probably very narrow.
したがって、その発光範囲はおそらく非常に狭いと思われます。
General organic dyes emit light
一般的な有機色素は発光します
It's probably... If it's a green it's probably like this
たぶん…緑ならこんな感じかな
It shines about 1⁄ of its light
光の約1/2で輝きます
What's the benefit?
メリットは何ですか?
is RGB
RGBです
If it is RGB, it can be done without FILTER
RGBであればFILTERなしでも可能です
this is the best part of it
これが一番いいところだ
Its IdeaCase
そのアイデアケース
Each if 30 Nm
各30Nmの場合
Not even FILTER
フィルターすらない
Not even green light
青信号すらない
You also know we lose a lot of light
私たちが多くの光を失っていることもご存知でしょう
It's because of the green light film
グリーンライトフィルムのせいだよ
So its Country is so good that it explodes
だからその国は爆発するほど素晴らしい
Now its Country doesn't work anymore
今ではその国はもう機能しません
So everyone knows that this is a
したがって、これが
Then you said CDs are poisonous, right?
じゃあCDには毒があるって言いましたよね？
You can also use non-toxic
非毒性のものを使用することもできます
We now use ZNCINH2
現在は ZNCINH2 を使用しています
In this way we can also do anything
そうすれば私たちも何でもできる
It can be done without any problem in this space.
このスペースなら問題なく出来ます。
Sorry, the biggest problem with this technique is
申し訳ありませんが、この手法の最大の問題は
Can only do green light, not red
緑色の光のみを使用でき、赤色は使用できません
Why?
なぜ？
Because this place costs a lot of ZN
ここはZN高いので
The more words go to the shorter wavelength
より多くの言葉がより短い波長に向かう
so we can't make red light
だから赤信号は出せない
But Liguang we can do well
でも、麗光ならうまくやっていけるよ
there is a problem here
ここに問題があります
OK we make it like this
OK、このように作ります
15.3489 grams can be made at one time
一度に15.3489グラム作ることができます。
Wow this is posted
おお、これが掲載されている
OK, if this is currently for sale
OK、これが現在販売されている場合
Of course you have to sell to others
もちろん他人に売らなければなりません
people can do it right away
人々はすぐにそれを行うことができます
so to wrap
それで包むために
so packaging wait a minute i can talk
だから梱包するからちょっと待っててね、話ができるから
you sell this
あなたはこれを売っています
No company in Taiwan knows what to do
台湾のどの企業も何をすべきか分からない
OK so how are you going to pack what he's doing
OK、それでは彼がやっていることをどのようにまとめますか
this is a science
これは科学です
This is the real knowledge
これが本当の知識です
This is no longer a patent
これはもう特許ではありません
why no patents
なぜ特許がないのか
20 years of development
20年の開発
The previous patent has long since expired.
以前の特許はとうの昔に期限切れになっています。
OK so this patent is a patented method
OK、この特許は特許取得済みの方法です
Not in the patent how to synthesize
合成方法は特許に記載されていない
OK, supposedly this looks a lot like
OK、おそらくこれはよく似ています
What's so strange about the one that looks like a thread?
糸のように見えるものは何がそんなに奇妙なのでしょうか？
Look, turn off the lights and turn on the lights
ほら、電気を消して、電気をつけて
this is so beautiful
これはとても美しいです
did you see
あなたは見ましたか
this is full force
これは全力です
OK so the answer is it's gold
OK、答えはゴールドです
do not forget
忘れてはいけない
It's more expensive than gold
ゴールドよりも高価です
OK basically
基本的にOK
you know what to say
あなたは何を言うべきか知っていますか
it's a scary thing
それは怖いことです
OK we hope to use 100 grams in the future
将来的には 100 グラムを使用したいと考えています
A Batch to do
やるべきバッチ
OK
OK
this is what we are trying to do now
これが私たちが今やろうとしていることです
because it's hard, really hard because
それは難しいから、本当に難しいから
We are not from a chemical background
私たちは化学の出身ではありません
It's super dangerous to watch him do this kind of thing, let me tell you basically
彼がこのようなことをしているのを見るのは非常に危険です、基本的に言っておきます
So of course you will go in the future
もちろん将来的には行くでしょう
If it’s really commercial, it’s one kilogram
本当に商用なら1キロです
You need one kilogram for each background, and I will give you a basic explanation
背景ごとに 1 キログラムが必要です。基本的な説明をします。
OK, so what can we do with chemistry?
では、化学を使って何ができるでしょうか?
In fact, our chemistry is doing some
実際、私たちの化学はいくつかのことを行っています
It's powerful in doing this multiplication
この乗算を行うのに強力です
How do you do some chemical multiplication?
化学増殖はどのように行うのでしょうか?
does it work
それは機能しますか
OK, this is us
OK、これが私たちです
we make this thing out
私たちはこれを理解します
You want it to have application value
応用価値を持たせたい
Of course, the application has a value that shines
もちろんアプリには光る価値がある
As far as the monitor, we'll talk later
モニターに関してはまた後ほど。
But is there anything else?
しかし、他に何かありますか？
yes, too many
はい、多すぎます
Let me give you an example, like we are in...
例を挙げましょう。私たちがいるようなものです...
it's been a long time
おひさしぶりですね
This was eight years ago, OK
これは8年前のことです、わかりました
we develop this, you see
私たちはこれを開発しています、わかりますか
This is the one that shines, OK
輝くのはこれだ、OK
What to use next to it?
その隣で何を使おうか？
used to adjust these so-called obsessions
これらのいわゆる強迫観念を調整するために使用されます
That fan can contain fake, fake ion
そのファンには偽の、偽のイオンが含まれている可能性があります
As for the false ion, it cannot carry two packages like this
疑似イオンはこのように2つの荷物を運ぶことはできません
It needs to connect two by two, Tang Lunbao
2 つずつ接続する必要があります、タン・ルンバオ
Why? Because it's a problem with entropy
なぜか? それはエントロピーの問題だからです
I won't go into too much detail, it's a question of randomness
あまり詳しくは述べませんが、これは偶然の問題です
It needs to be connected two by two, Tang Lunbao
2つずつ接続する必要があります、タン・ルンバオ
So answer first, we can do one thing
だから最初に答えてください、私たちにできることは 1 つあります
look
見て
Let's use it to detect armor
鎧の検出に使ってみましょう
It's very simple. Let's make another
とても簡単なのでもう一つ作ってみましょう
in a minute
すぐに
to synthesize a green and a red
緑と赤を合成するには
it's so easy no problem
とても簡単なので問題ありません
So we synthesized a green one to do rice filling
そこで、ご飯を詰めるために緑色のものを合成しました
wrap it in this place
この場所に巻きます
So when armor cuts in
鎧が食い込むと
It may be red and green cut together
赤と緑を一緒にカットしてもよい
Also follow red with red, also follow green with green
赤に続いて赤、緑に続いて緑
It doesn't matter, the probability of red and green is 1.2
関係ありません、赤と緑の確率は1.2です
So as long as red and green are cut together, there will be energy transfer
赤と緑が一緒に切断されている限り、エネルギー伝達が起こります
green turns red
緑が赤に変わります
OK we see the green ones disappear and the red ones grow
OK、緑色のものが消えて赤色が成長するのがわかります
is it really like this
本当にそうなのか
OK the answer is yes
OK、答えはイエスです
OK look
わかりました、見てください
So the answer is when red and green
答えは赤と緑のときです
you know it will grow to
まで成長することを知っていますか
The green one will disappear when the armor is dropped
緑色のものは鎧を落とすと消えます
OK until halfway it doesn't move why
途中まではOKなのに動かないのはなぜ？
Because the others are green green red red it does not move
他は緑緑赤赤なので動きません
So this is also saying that the theory is right.
したがって、これは理論が正しいとも言えます。
OK, let me tell you that it was originally this color
OK、言っておきますが、元々はこの色でした
The more red the color becomes
色が赤くなるほど
so you see it's useful
便利だということがわかりますね
OK basically
OK 基本上
If you don't believe me let's see another
信じられないなら別のを見てみましょう
This is what I cooperated with Fang Junping and the others
これは私が方俊平たちと協力したものです
OK basically
OK 基本上
it was a long time ago
ずっと前のことだった
This was at least eight or nine years ago
これは少なくとも8、9年前のことです
you see we can go
わかりますか、私たちは行けます
After we synthesized this thing
これを合成した後
Teacher Fang and the others synthesized this so-called
ファン先生と他の人たちは、これをいわゆる
called
呼ばれた
This is Gout
これは痛風です
juta gujami
ジュタ・グジャミ
this is very simple
これはとても簡単です
Guta Gujami is the one with eggs
卵を持っているのはグタ・グジャミです
help me the most over there
そこで一番助けてください
OK because the egg needs to
OK、卵が必要だから
something to find sperm
精子を見つけるためのもの
OK, if the sperm and egg are going to combine
OK、精子と卵子が結合するなら
next to the embryo of your egg
あなたの卵子の胚の隣に
must have this thing
これを持っているはずです
So let's take this as an egg
では、これを卵として考えてみましょう
agree again
再同意一次
Let's take this as an egg
これを卵としてみましょう
Take this Guta Gujami
このグタ・グジャミを受け取ってください
use it with a SS linkage
SSリンケージと併用してください
then in this place
それからこの場所で
this reverting action
この元に戻すアクション
become SH
SHになる
cut it
それを切ります
then i can say
それなら言えます
cut with this semiconductor
この半導体でカット
It's all cut with a flow machine
すべてフローマシンでカットされています
OK and G also use streamers
OKとGもストリーマーを使用
ok then why
わかりました、それではなぜですか
Because if the flow machine cuts it
フローマシンがカットしてしまうと
about 20 kcal
約20kcal
The energy is 20 kcal, this stick
エネルギーは20kcal、このスティック
Flow and G are the most stable
流れとGが最も安定
Flow and G is 41 kcal
流量・Gは41kcal
so why
なぜ
All G's Neoplas use stream cutting
所有的G的Neoplas都用流砍
OK, that's easy to remember
わかりました、それは覚えやすいです
If you want to test
テストしたい場合は
Flowing G years Flowing G years
流れるG年 流れるG年
Flow and G are the best OK
流れもGも最高OK
So Liu and G cut is the best
だからリューとGカットは最高だよ
basically
基本的
This stream we use
私たちが使用するこのストリーム
So after chopping it up
それで、切り刻んでから、
just treat it as a soft paper
柔らかい紙として扱ってください
so we find gold
それで私たちは金を見つけます
We use C2 circle
C2サークルを使用します
It's the gold of the sea urchin
ウニの黄金です
look
見て
Cut with sea urchin gold
ウニゴールドカット
Everything is included in this place
この場所にすべてが含まれています
Our NEOPARTY are all cut in this place
私たちのNEOPARTYはすべてここでカットされます
this place where the spun cut to gold
紡がれて金に変わるこの場所
I said
私は言いました
Maybe it has this place
もしかしたらこんな場所もあるかもしれない
very simple
とてもシンプルな
Let's take that bone off
その骨を外しましょう
We use MANOS
マノスを使用しています
MANOS will be cut everywhere
マノスはどこでもカットされます
You can see that MANOS will be cut everywhere
MANOSが随所でカットされているのがわかります
So the answer it's really specific
答えは本当に具体的です
then you say this
それからあなたはこう言います
Then why we are developing
ではなぜ開発を行うのか
because it's too poisonous
毒が強すぎるから
CD is too poisonous
CDは毒すぎる
so cd now
だから今すぐCDを
No
いいえ
This semiconductor of CD
CDのこの半導体
no one is using what
誰も何を使っていないのか
The Bio-Medical Impossible
バイオメディカルの不可能
The reason is too poisonous
理由が毒すぎる
OK so now instead
OK、それでは代わりに
The most used one is Materials Science
最もよく使われるのは材料科学です
OK that Materials Science
OK、材料科学です
everyone knows
みんな知ってる
I won't talk about this
これについては話しません
I jump over there are too many
多すぎるので飛び越えます
OK we see
わかりました
monitor
モニター
Future Trends
今後の動向
OK because you can draw this number
この数字を引くことができるので OK
This was announced last week
これは先週発表されました
It's called REC2020
その名も「REC2020」
it's 2020
2020年です
Specifications for all displays Highest quality
すべてのディスプレイの仕様 最高品質
This is the Color specification
こちらはカラー仕様です
What about the Color specification?
カラー指定はどうなるのでしょうか？
Currently it looks like there is only one reachable
現在、到達可能なのは 1 つだけのようです
frame root way
フレームルートウェイ
Why? Because it RGB is the best
理由は、RGB が最適だからです。
This is Sony made RGB
これはソニー製のRGBです
basically speaking
基本的に言えば
Made it with frame root
フレームルートで作りました
How many ways are there to frame the roots?
根を構成する方法は何通りありますか?
one is you know
1つはあなたが知っています
It is probably Sony's type that uses this on both sides.
おそらくソニーはこれを両面に使うタイプだと思います。
Just use Blu to make the green frame root
Blu を使用して緑のフレームのルートを作成するだけです
White light comes out from the red frame
赤い枠から白い光が出ます
The other CM
もう一つのCMは
The root B volume of the box is to use FIM
ボックスのルート B ボリュームは FIM を使用します
This FIM is the same
このFIMも同じです
green and red
緑と赤
Then the following is with Blu-ray
では、以下はBlu-rayの場合です
because blu ray is the best
ブルーレイが最高だから
Blue LED is the best
青色LEDは最高です
Use 460 to dial 520 and 630
460 を使用して 520 および 630 にダイヤルします
OK, this is white light
OK、これは白い光です
This approach is OK
このアプローチはOKです
Then there is the Micro chip
次にマイクロチップです
Just put it DD now
今すぐDDしてください
the red and green
赤と緑
D to what?
Dは何に？
Micro chip aspect
マイクロチップの側面
That Micro chip is LED to what?
そのマイクロチップは何のためのLEDですか？
Blue, ah, what is blue when it shines
青、ああ、光ると青って何だろう
is white light
白い光です
OK, there are these three ways
はい、この 3 つの方法があります
That's probably the most
那大概現在最
The biggest trend is probably this
最大のトレンドはおそらくこれ
Film does the most
映画が最も効果を発揮する
OK, so actually we have chosen Film
OK、実際にはフィルムを選択しました
doing ok
大丈夫です
That
それか
Kuan Sheng Dao can do it very well
クアンシェンダオはそれがとても上手です
the hardest part
一番難しい部分
How to cut together with Polymer
ポリマーと一緒にカットする方法
become this Film
この映画になる
Oh that's a science
ああ、それは科学だ
We spent almost two years
私たちはほぼ2年を費やしました
OK everyone, no need to take pictures
はい、皆さん、写真を撮る必要はありません
Because of this I just write one
ということで一つだけ書きます
Because we're going to announce OK basically talk
発表するから基本話OK
So everyone, one thing is very simple
それで皆さん、一つのことは非常に簡単です
You see we can use this kind of Film
この種のフィルムを使用できることがわかります
make a green and red
緑と赤を作ります
OK green and red OK basically
基本的に緑と赤OK
Ah, if he doesn't shine
ああ、彼が輝かなかったら
Then this color OK basically speaks
じゃあ基本的にはこの色でOK
that's in this place
それはこの場所にあります
We make a Film
私たちは映画を作ります
Come on, let's take a look at this Film for you
さあ、この映画を見てみましょう
This Film is what we made OK
この映画は私たちがOKしたものです
you see you use blue
青を使っているのがわかりますか
Use blue, this is all blue
青を使用してください、これはすべて青です
look at blu ray
ブルーレイを見てください
fat is white
脂肪は白い
Because it's only green and red
緑と赤だけだから
Ah, adding blue is white
ああ、青を足すと白になる
OK turn off the lights is like
OK、照明を消してください、みたいな感じです
Because this blu-ray is actually
というのも、このBlu-rayは実は
I spark blue light
青い光を輝かせます
but he is white
でも彼は白人です
Ah, if you are unlucky
ああ、運が悪いと
I don't want the whole paper
紙全体は要らない
don't focus
集中しないでください
If the whole paper is illuminated, it will look like this
紙全体を照らすとこんな感じになります
just white light
ただの白い光
OK, it's white
はい、白です
So this is its niche
これがニッチです
It can produce a white light
白色光を生成できる
Send this this display
この表示を送信してください
Then let you do all the following actions
次に、次のすべてのアクションを実行させます
OK, it can be done even without filter
OK、フィルターなしでもできます
Why? Because each one is
なぜ? それぞれがそうであるからです。
Both are very, very sharp bandwidth
どちらも非常にシャープな帯域幅です
OK, basically
OK,基本上
What about the bright paper point, and its application in luminescence
ブライトペーパーポイントとその発光への応用についてはどうでしょうか
just said passive
ただ受動的に言っただけ
That is, you directly use the blu-ray to pump to get it
つまり、ブルーレイを直接使用してポンピングして取得します。
if you want to be active you have to take the initiative
アクティブになりたければ、率先して行動しなければなりません
That is QLED
それがQLEDです
Sorry about the LEDs on Quadrant Road
Quadrant Road の LED についてはごめんなさい
Quadrant Road's LED so far
これまでのQuadrant RoadのLED
Taiwan's development
台湾の発展
that's too far behind
それは遅すぎます
OK, basically
OK、基本的には
because i'm doing chemistry
私は化学をやっているので
I'm not doing engineering
私はエンジニアリングをやっていません
In fact, I have been calling for it for five or six years.
実は私は5、6年前からそのことを訴え続けてきました。
ok , basically talk
わかりました、基本的に話します
Or Taiwan has done too little
あるいは台湾はあまりにも何もしなかった
That's 18% done recently
それは最近 18% 完了しました
OK, I think 18% this
OK、これは 18% だと思います
Including public and educational personnel are very useful
公共関係者や教育関係者も含めて非常に役に立ちます
That's 18% OK, basically
基本的には 18% でOKです
You just remember 18%
18% だけ覚えています
ok , basically talk
わかりました、基本的に話します
Then why couldn't it be done before?
なぜ以前はそれができなかったのでしょうか？
You look good, let me tell you, everyone
元気そうだね、みんなに言わせてよ
this
これ
No Fundamental
基本的ではない
you don't want to do anything
何もしたくないのですか
OK, this is developed to be 8 temperature ratio
OK、これは 8 つの温度比になるように開発されました
on MIT
MITで
With this Broadic
このブロードディックを使用すると、
This is in the electrical department
ここは電気科です
This is the electrical department
こちらは電気科です
this is from the chemistry department
こちらは化学科からです
The whole combination of motor and chemistry
モーターと化学の完全な組み合わせ
you have a way
あなたには方法があります
OK, there is also a physics department
そうですね、物理学科もありますよ
There is also a physics department here
ここには物理学科もあります
then why
それでなんで
Because the reason why it couldn't be done before is because
なぜなら、今までできなかった理由は、
we only know now
私たちは今しか知りません
because when you use electron light
電子光を使うと
You used a bunch of electronics and electricity to come out
あなたは出てくるためにたくさんの電子機器と電気を使いました
This electron is too electric
この電子は電気的すぎる
too many electrons
電子が多すぎる
too much for a physical benefit
肉体的な利益を得るには多すぎる
Called the reverse OJ Process
逆OJプロセスと呼ばれる
is that it will wipe it all off
それはすべてを消し去るということです
Just the opposite OJ
ちょうど反対のOJ
wait a minute i'll talk about this
ちょっと待ってください、このことについて話します
Just the opposite OJ Process
ちょうど逆の OJ プロセス
OJ Process Logically speaking it should be
OJ プロセス 論理的に言えば、次のようになります。
one becomes two
一つが二つになる
it is now two become
今は2つになりました
Gone
消えた
OK so when a thing is
OK、何かが起こったとき
that now they are smart
今では彼らは賢くなった
they are here
彼らはここにいます
smooth it
滑らかにしてください
Flatten two Bank Gap
2つのバンクギャップを平坦化する
Let many electrons
電子をたくさん放出しましょう
you can come here, come here
ここに来てもいいです、ここに来てください
The whole thing is Dilocalize
すべてはディローカライズです
so it can be accessed from
からアクセスできるようになります
1% to 18%
1%～18%
OK look at this
はい、これを見てください
This is the political and economic world in 2013
これが2013年の政界・経済界です。
OK
OK
The current problem is unstable
現在の問題は不安定です
If the stability is overcome
安定を乗り越えれば
I'm sorry, we all have been doing it for so long, probably we don't need to do it
ごめんなさい、私たちは皆長い間そうしてきたので、おそらくそれをする必要はありません
basically talk
基本的に話す
Our laboratory is now approximately
私たちの研究室は現在約
we follow
私たちはフォローする
With the cooperation of Ocean University, we can probably make it invisible
海洋大学の協力があれば見えなくすることもできるだろう
OK but not high
OKだが高くはない
but this
しかしこれは
This is a question about the Five-Eyed Buddha Realm
五眼仏界についての質問です。
if this is right if bangwit30nm
これが正しい場合、bangwit30nm の場合
Mineral energy is one
ミネラルエネルギーはひとつ
OK, if the stability is enough, who can compare with him?
OK、安定性が十分であれば、誰が彼と比較できるでしょうか？
You two compare
お二人は比べてください
OK, so this is basically what Taiwan should have developed long ago
OK、基本的にこれは台湾がずっと前に開発すべきだったものです
It's a pity that none of them came out. The other one is the solar battery.
どれも出なかったのが残念ですが、もう一つは太陽電池です。
OK, the solar battery is basically
OK、太陽電池は基本的には
That's already a problem with the solar battery.
それは太陽電池の問題です。
because of that
そのための
The leanant next to it is too long
隣のリーナントが長すぎる
Electricity can't be transmitted
電気は伝わらない
Now use the inorganic method to develop it in Toronto, use the inorganic method, use the short chain or inorganic method
今はトロントで開発するために無機法を使用します。無機法を使用します。短鎖または無機法を使用します。
He can do the same with 8.55%
彼は8.55%でも同じことができる
Bowendy and
ボウエンディと
Bobic
ボビック
OK you know one thing is
OK、わかっていることは 1 つあります
How can this be done without combining electrical physics and chemistry?
電気物理学と化学を組み合わせずに、どうやってこれを実現できるでしょうか?
OK so this has to be integrated
OK、これは統合する必要があります
It just doesn't work if you don't integrate
統合しないと機能しない
Don't shoot birds randomly, it's impossible
ランダムに鳥を撃たないでください、それは不可能です
You don't have this kind of random shooting
こんなランダムな射撃はありません
It's impossible for you to shoot wildly.
乱暴に撃つことは不可能です。
OK so one thing for everyone and this is to visit Demental
OK、それでは皆さんに一つだけお願いがあります。それは Demental を訪問することです。
You're going to move forward, can you find a way, okay?
あなたは前に進むつもりです、方法を見つけることができますか？
So let me tell you why this loose to the solar cell is
それでは、なぜ太陽電池が緩むのか説明しましょう。
is a one
は 1 つです
Future goals Let me give you a very simple example, you see, this is OJ Process
将来の目標 非常に簡単な例を挙げましょう。これが OJ プロセスです。
Look, a Fortone is punched up, this one has electric
見てください、Fortone はパンチアップされています、これは電気を持っています
OK this is no battery yes this electronics if I think solar
OK、これはバッテリーではありません、はい、この電子機器はソーラーだと思います
You also know that Mr. Lin and the others know each other very well.
リンさんと他の人たちがお互いのことをよく知っていることもご存知でしょう。
pair a solar cell
太陽電池をペアリングする
OK if your dye is like dye brightening
染料がブライトニングのようなものであれば OK
You go from 700C light to 300 to 400
700℃の軽い温度から300℃、400℃まで上がります。
You inspire 400 and you also get 700
400 を鼓舞すれば、700 も得られます
Yes Excite 500 to 700 you from 500 to 700
はい、500から700まであなたを興奮させます500から700まで
All the energy in between is wasted.
その間のエネルギーはすべて無駄になります。
Because it's better to let it come down here before going out, right?
だってここで降ろしてから出かけたほうがいいですよね？
So but it's so loose that it's not the same as you get excited to this place
だからだけど緩すぎてここに興奮するのとは違う
I think it’s good to stimulate 400, here it’s 400
400刺激すると良いと思います、ここは400です
Let's say it's 800 here
ここが800だとしましょう
From 400 to this place it can be done with a very simple action
400からここまでは非常に簡単なアクションで行えます
that is
あれは
When this place comes down, when this place goes up, OJ process
ここが下がったら、ここが上がったら、OJプロセス
this down, this up
これが下、これが上
You can use this place once resonance
共鳴したらここを使えるよ
After coming down, this tiredness will change to two
下って来たこの疲れは、登る時には２倍になります。
That is to say, I stimulate an energy
つまり、エネルギーを刺激するのです
But it becomes two electrons on top
でも上には電子が2つになる
ok, this is called up conversion
OK、これはアップコンバージョンと呼ばれます
ok, so use this way
はい、この方法を使用してください
In theory you can reach 66%
理論的には66%に達することができます
basically speaking
基本的に言えば
This is where everyone tends to go wrong
ここは誰もが間違いやすいところです
ok, basically since that Nucia brought it up
OK、基本的にはヌーシアがそれを持ち出したからです
So far I can't really prove how much
今のところ実際にどれくらいなのかは証明できません
But now with current technology
しかし、今のテクノロジーでは
Personally, I think this will definitely break through in the future.
個人的にはこれは今後必ずブレイクすると思っています。
ok, how to break through
さて、どうやって突破するか
it's an interesting thought
興味深い考えですね
just tell everyone about this
このことをみんなに伝えてください
Okay, I probably won't talk about it
わかりました、それについてはおそらく話さないでしょう
because talking too much
しゃべりすぎるから
In addition, it is like shining
また、輝いているような
Sorry, gold can shine too
申し訳ありませんが、金も輝くことができます
You see, the gold that is stepped on quickly does not shine
ほら、すぐに踏まれた金は光らない
right
右
Then when it is greater than 1.5 nm to 50 nm
次に1.5nmを超えて50nmになると
We're called, you all know it's called Surface Plasma Justice
私たちは呼ばれています、皆さんはそれが表面プラズマジャスティスと呼ばれていることを知っています
Right, gold has color, everyone knows
そう、金には色がある、誰もが知っている
right , but it doesn ' t shine
そうです、でも光りません
But when you are as small as 1.5nm
しかし、1.5nm程度の大きさになると、
what has become, quantize
どうなったか、量子化する
Discrete phenomenon
離散現象
it will glow
それは光るだろう
This is what our Sense made
これが私たちのセンスが作ったものです
you see it glows red
赤く光っているのがわかりますか
In red light in this place
この場所では赤信号で
what shall we do this time
今度は何をしましょうか
what is our bread
私たちのパンは何ですか
Packet shift derivative
パケットシフト導関数
OK we wrap gold with shifted derivatives
OK、シフトされたデリバティブで金をラップします
How do you say that eating is not boring? Use the shift derivative package
食事が退屈ではないとはどのように言えますか? シフト派生パッケージを使用してください
Because we already know that there are 4 SH in the shift derivative
シフト導関数には 4 つの SH があることがすでにわかっているため、
it definitely has a chance
それは間違いなくチャンスがある
This is your Nulling OK
これがあなたのヌリング OK です
basically it's small
基本的に小さいです
So it can be used as Template
テンプレートとして使用できるので、
we wrap it up together you see
私たちはそれを一緒にまとめます。
look how useful it is
それがどれほど便利かを見てください
Basically you see, using the shift derivative package comes out as
基本的に、シフト派生パッケージを使用すると次のようになります。
It 1.2 Neyometer
それは1.2ネイヨメートル
it shines
それは輝く
Space 1 to 0.1 to 0.3
スペース 1 ～ 0.1 ～ 0.3
It's easy if you're unlucky
運が悪ければ簡単だよ
Is there a shift derivative in this?
これにシフト導関数はありますか?
Look, we'll just use one
ほら、1 つだけ使いましょう
So the N station of Insulin's Digest
インスリンダイジェストのNステーション
Go chop it down and it won't shine when it comes out
切り落として、出てきたら光らないよ
Insulin
インスリン
After dropping this Insulin and that Decomposed
このインスリンを落とした後、それが分解されました
it doesn't shine
光らない
So of course Insulin is on top of that
もちろんインスリンもその上にあります
We published this in NQ1 in 2011
これは 2011 年の NQ1 に掲載されました
OK now it has been stuffed 148 times
OK、これで 148 回詰められました
Basically someone must use it
基本的に誰かが使わないといけない
because i never tan myself
私は日焼けしたことがないので
So this 148 is posted by others
つまり、この 148 は他の人が投稿したものです
So the answer is definitely useful
したがって、答えは間違いなく役に立ちます
We can use it as image
画像として使用させていただきます
Then this image red image
それからこの画像の赤い画像
the one in the muscle
筋肉の中のもの
That sale is very useful
そのセールはとても便利です
Basically I am now a lot of people like us to
基本的に私は今、私たちと同じような人がたくさんいます
So they should also be doing this approach
したがって、彼らもこのアプローチを行う必要があります
basically speaking
基本的に言えば
especially insulin you know
特にインスリンはご存知の通り
Diabetes is America's number one disease
糖尿病はアメリカで最も多い病気です
Why is everyone so fat
なんでみんなそんなに太ってるの
So the answer is that there is no way
したがって、答えは「方法はありません」です
I don't talk about anything else
それ以外のことは何も話さない
like these
これらのように
what do we do some fuseale
フューザーレどうする？
Just now, Vice President Wang, you said
今、王副総統、あなたは言いました。
i do everything
私はすべてやる
do nothing wrong
何も悪いことはしない
basically speaking
基本的に言えば
You just make a different size
違うサイズを作るだけです
What is the fuseale including this shave dependent doing?
この剃り依存を含めたフュザーレは何をしているのでしょうか？
In fact, we do a lot of this phenomenon
実際、私たちはこの現象を頻繁に行っています
even we can use fine silver alloy
上質な銀合金でも使えます
toon its prasma band
プラズマバンドをトゥーンする
To do opv, we also do a lot of this
opv を行うために、これもたくさん行います
I won't talk about this
これについては話しません
That's actually
それは実際に
if you give me an hour
1時間くれたら
I can put this into perspective
これを大局的に考えることができます
but there is no time now
でも今は時間がない
We do a lot of business with refugee machinery
私たちは難民向けの機械と多くの取引を行っています
So just now the student of mine
それでちょうど今、私の生徒が
my former students
私の元生徒たち
Chen Junan told me that he was doing New Long
チェン・ジュナンは「New Long」をやっていると私に言いました。
Do Stem Cell in doing New Long
New Longを行う際にStem Cellを行う
In fact, we also do a lot of this
実際、私たちもこのようなことをたくさん行っています
But we do his Imaging
しかし、私たちは彼のイメージングを行います
We do a lot of things like Imaging
私たちはイメージングなどのことをたくさん行っています
i can basically talk
基本的に話せます
What about the last one?
最後のものはどうですか？
Let me tell you one thing is this
一つ言っておきますが、これは
This is the last one
これが最後です
This is a wheat field in England
ここはイギリスの小麦畑です
English wheat fields, right?
イギリスの小麦畑ですよね？
This British wheat field is really good
このイギリスの小麦畑は本当に美味しいです
when i see this
これを見ると
i just know
私はただ知っています
It turns out that the Kangbang I studied is exactly the same
私が研究していたカンバンが全く同じであることが判明
basically talk
基本的に話す
Then I'm going this way now
じゃあ今はこっちに行きます
I'm going to Brain Research now
今からブレインリサーチに行ってきます
Because the answer is that I personally think one thing is
答えは、私が個人的に考えていることは 1 つあるからです。
our future generations
私たちの将来の世代
The next generation can already live to be 100 years old
次世代はすでに100歳まで生きる可能性がある
But what's the point of living a very unhappy life, right?
しかし、とても不幸な人生を送ることに何の意味があるのでしょうか？
So the answer to one thing is
したがって、あることに対する答えは、
Your Brain is the most important
あなたの脳が最も重要です
i didn't lie to you
私はあなたに嘘をつきませんでした
I really think Brain Research
Brain Researchは本当にそう思います
Basically, we must go in the future
基本的には将来に行かなければなりません
because our brains
なぜなら私たちの脳は
nothing has changed in a thousand years
千年経っても何も変わっていない
But our knowledge has skyrocketed ten million times
しかし、私たちの知識は1,000万倍に急増しました
this is our biggest problem
これが私たちの最大の問題です
So how to do Brain Research
では、脳研究をどのように行うか
i just matter
私はただ重要です
Then I am researching Slautonium and Milatonian
それからスラストニウムとミラトニアンの研究をしています
this piece
この作品
because it's my specialty
それは私の専門だから
I just said what kind of specialty is this?
先ほど言いましたが、これはどのような専門ですか？
well in this place
まあこの場所で
I just stop at this place
ただこの場所に立ち寄るだけです
OK
OK
I just said that
私はちょうどそれを言いました
actually, I
実は、私
Because there are very few Ph.D.
博士号取得者が非常に少ないからです。
Look at the doctoral class in recent years
近年の博士課程を見てみる
Only these few people in five years
5年間でこの数人だけ
So I'm all on my post-out
だから私はポストアウトに全力を尽くしています
OK all my money Sug in my post-out
OK 全額返金してください。
basically talk
基本的に話す
OK that's about it
はい、それくらいです
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
clap your hands
手をたたいてください
Hope you all have one
皆さんも持っているといいですね
still enjoy
まだ楽しんでいます
enjoy beauty
美しさを楽しむ
good i think
良いと思います
Would you like to have a drink first?
まずは一杯いかがですか？
I still have a lot of experience
まだまだ経験はたくさんあります
You see how Energetic he is
彼がどれほどエネルギッシュであるかがわかります
ok is there any problem
OK、何か問題はありますか
for this I
このために私は
wait a minute my wife tell me
ちょっと待ってください、妻が教えてくれました
you say
あなたは言う
every time you speak
あなたが話すたびに
like a movie star
映画スターのように
But you come home a worm
でも君は虫になって帰ってくる
sure so
確かにそうです
I'm sure
私は確信しています
thank you for your speech
スピーチをありがとう
I want to ask you about the first half
前半についてお聞きしたいのですが
because of my
私のせいで
Kaohsiung gas explosion incident
高雄ガス爆発事件
because it has that explosive
爆発物があるから
Later I went to refer to some chemistry
その後、化学を参照しに行きました
Seems like it could also be done in this optomechanical way
この光学機械的な方法でも実現できるようです
To see if there is chemistry that try
試してみる化学があるかどうかを確認するために
Or that try to get into the ingredients of these explosives
または、これらの爆発物の成分に侵入しようとするもの
I'll ask for advice
アドバイスを求めます
Why like this way
なぜこのように
In fact, when they were dealing with incidents similar to those in Kaohsiung
実は、高雄市と同様の事件が起きたとき、
It does not detect whether there are chemical components of violent substances
暴力物質の化学成分の有無は検出しません
actually i tell you
実は私はあなたに言います
If you want to speak from a spectroscopic point of view
分光学的な観点から話したい場合
if specific few
具体的に少ない場合
For example, if you measure IR vibration spectrum or Lyman spectrum
たとえば、IR振動スペクトルやライマンスペクトルを測定すると、
These things if you want specific
具体的に知りたい場合は、これらのこと
specific few
特定の少数の
In fact, these can be used in the analysis of data
実際、これらはデータ分析に使用できます。
can do not a problem
問題なくできます
this can definitely be done
これは間違いなくできる
So one thing for everyone is to say
そこで皆さんに言えることは 1 つだけです
We are actually from Taiwan...
実は私たちは台湾出身なんです...
His advance is measured after a plan
彼の進歩は計画の後に測られる
What is that data for?
そのデータは何のためにあるのでしょうか?
That's where we're not very advanced
そこが私たちがあまり進んでいないところです
why i give an example
なぜ例を挙げたのか
like our LCMAS
私たちのLCMASのように
Incredible, including the chemistry department
化学科も含めてすごいですね
The opera you typed out will tell you
入力したオペラが教えてくれる
I don't know, I don't know what
分からない、何なのか分からない
Our data bank is completely inadequate
私たちのデータバンクはまったく不十分です
Now students and people know one thing
今、学生と人々は一つのことを知っています
What are you going to screen for?
何のためにスクリーニングするつもりですか？
Look at that Half or MIT
ハーフかMITを見てください
that data bank
そのデータバンク
how many people are going to do what
何人で何をするつもりですか
How big is the data bank
データバンクの規模はどれくらいですか
The accumulation of how much money and the accumulation of people
どれだけのお金の蓄積と人の蓄積
We never do software stuff
私たちはソフトウェア関連のことは決して行いません
I can tell you about the question you asked
あなたがした質問についてお話します
In terms of explosives, data bank
爆発物に関してはデータバンク
absolutely doable
絶対に実行可能
It's a pity we don't do this kind of thing
私たちがこのようなことをしないのは残念です
We have instruments coming out and don't know what
楽器は出てくるけど、何が何だか分からない
this is our biggest problem
これが私たちの最大の問題です
OK
OK
Thanks
ありがとう
What is the problem
何が問題ですか
The crazy question is okay
おかしな質問でも大丈夫です
crazy question
クレイジーな質問
I'm always full of crazy ideas
私はいつもクレイジーなアイデアでいっぱいです
I didn't lie to you
私はあなたに嘘をついていませんでした
right
右
but crazy idea
しかしクレイジーなアイデア
one out of ten is enough
10人に1人で十分です
it's obvious
明らかです
A person's life
人の人生
you have to go crazy
あなたは狂わなければなりません
somehow
どうにか
Is it already
もうですか
the light therapy device
光線療法装置
under that of Taiwan
台湾の下に
in treatment
治療中
Did you say light therapy?
光療法って言いましたか？
Buddha as much as that Thorpe
あのソープと同じくらい仏陀
Is this most likely skin cancer?
これは皮膚がんの可能性が高いでしょうか？
What about social traps?
社会的な罠についてはどうですか？
OK, this is probably the most light therapy
OK、これはおそらく最も軽い療法です
submerged
水没した
Because of the light
光のせいで
sorry for something
何かごめんなさい
biggest problem with light
光に関する最大の問題
high energy of light
高い光エネルギー
I say visible light
可視光と言うのは
visible light to that
それに対する可視光線
when in infrared
赤外線の場合
energy is still too high
エネルギーがまだ高すぎる
So generally speaking in terms of infrared
一般的に赤外線に関して言えば、
Can penetrate at most
せいぜい貫通できる
about 0.6 cm
約0.6cm
already amazing
もうすごい
so here's the problem
ここで問題が発生します
longer wavelength
より長い波長
It should be deeper
もっと深いはずだ
OK basically
OK 基本上
But it doesn't shine, basically
でも基本的には光らないんです
So you know what MRI like we come out
MRI がどのようなものになるか知っていますか
that long wavelength
その長い波長
it can penetrate this no problem
これは問題なく貫通できます
But the shorter words
しかし、短い言葉ほど
It's the problem here
ここが問題だ
so light therapy
だから光療法
Sorry to tell you one thing is to say
申し訳ありませんが、一つ言っておきたいのは、
You're probably going to do a dive.
おそらくダイビングをすることになるでしょう。
OK that's all except for you to have the surgery
OK、あなたが手術を受けること以外はすべてです
I'll do light therapy later
後で光療法をします
Otherwise it is Target Oriented
それ以外の場合はターゲット指向です
So Target is
したがって、ターゲットは
is the target
ターゲットです
OK target
OKターゲット
And the target has no light
そしてターゲットには光がありません
No, they use monooxygen now.
いいえ、現在は一酸素を使用しています。
monoxide, right?
一酸化物ですよね？
So you target after that place
だからあなたはその場所の後ろをターゲットにします
you can be like we actually are
あなたは実際の私たちと同じようになれる
i didn't talk
話さなかった
you can
あなたはできる
You can take that and we call it Endopoxide
それをエンドポキシドと呼びます。
OK it can
わかりました、できます
It can be released into single oxygen
単一の酸素に放出される可能性があります
That is also possible
それも可能です
It can automatically do that without lighting
照明なしで自動的にそれを行うことができます
but you want a target
でもターゲットが欲しい
you don't have a target
あなたには目標がありません
Because everything kills the impossible
すべてが不可能を殺すから
OK
OK
any left
少し残っている
No, we thank Professor Zhou
いいえ、周教授に感謝します。
ok thank you thank you thank you all
わかりました、ありがとう、ありがとう、みんなありがとう
Thank you.
ありがとう。